Chapter 160: Gan Jiuzhen

Han Li closed his eyes and made a hand seal as he began to meditate, but a short while later, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and a wary look flashed across his face.

He reached forward to grab the small vial before tucking it back into the front of his robe, then rose to his feet and withdrew his spiritual sense.

After that, he quickly concealed his aura as well before hiding behind one of the nearby hardy willow trees.

Moments later, a figure flew past overhead, traveling into the distance in an extremely stealthy manner. In fact, the figure wasn't even giving off any spiritual power fluctuations, and it was as if a mortal had just passed through.

Blue light flashed through Han Li's eyes as he took a glance at the passing figure, and a perplexed look appeared on his face.

The figure was none other than the woman in the red dress who was accompanying him on this journey.

The woman clearly hadn't come for him, so he initially decided not to pry into this matter. However, she was flying rather slowly and intentionally concealing her aura, making her appear rather suspicious, and Han Li couldn't help but feel a little apprehensive.

What is that woman doing going out alone this late at night?

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to produce a High Zenith Invisibility Talisman.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of purple light lit up from his fingertip, and his body gradually faded into invisibility.

Even though the talisman had an aura concealment effect, Han Li didn't follow along too closely, making sure to trail along several thousand feet behind the woman.

The woman was naturally completely oblivious to this, and she continued to fly onward, flying straight out of the oasis after around 15 minutes.

Han Li followed her all the way to the edge of the oasis, and after confirming that she didn't seem to be harboring any ill intent, he decided that this was as far as he would go.

Hence, he drew to a halt before preparing to return to the lake.

However, right at this moment, a burst of dazzling light suddenly appeared in the night over 10,000 feet up ahead, and three massive shadows emerged to stop the woman in her tracks.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and as it turned out, the three giant shadows were a trio of mountainous white snow toads.

The snow toads were all of a pristine white color, and there were thick layers of frost covering their limbs and faces. Each of them also had a glowing ice crystal on their lower abdomen, presenting a particularly eye-catching sight in the night.

Han Li was rather surprised to see this. These toads were extremely massive, yet they had somehow been able to conceal themselves in such a way that even Han Li hadn't been able to detect them in advance with his spiritual sense.

A burst of deep croaking rang out as the three snow toads opened their giant mouths to reveal their dark purple tongues, which were emanating wisps of glacial qi.

Aside from the snow toads, there were also two figures standing atop the head of the middle toad.

One of them had an effeminate appearance and skin that was as fair as snow. They were wearing a tight-fitting long robe, but their chest was completely flat, and it was rather difficult to say whether they were male or female. As for the other figure, it was a hideous man with a portly frame and an unsightly face.

"Do you remember us two brothers, Gan Jiuzhen?"

The figure with the effeminate appearance was pointing at the woman in the red dress from afar as he spoke, and there was an indescribable note of femininity in his high-pitched voice.

"I don't have a habit of remembering nameless scoundrels suffering from gender identity crises," the woman in the red dress harrumphed coldly in response, and her voice was filled with undisguised disgust.

The effeminate man's face immediately became brightly flushed, seemingly so enraged that he was unable to even speak.

"It doesn't matter if you don't know our names. All you have to know is that this day next year will be your death anniversary!" the hideous man declared in a cold voice.

Gan Jiuzhen seemed to have lost patience with this war of words, and a derisive look appeared on her face beneath her veil as she took the initiative to lash out at her assailants.

With a flick of her wrist, crimson light began to surge over the crimson bracelet that she was wearing, as if it had suddenly sprung to life.

A draconic roar rang out as a ball of fire erupted out of the bracelet, transforming into a fiery dragon that was over 1,000 feet in length before pouncing over the night sky toward the two men standing atop the snow toad.

The effeminate man's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he bent down to gently pat the snow toad beneath his feet.

A string of deep croaking rang out as the three giant snow toads opened their mouths in unison, releasing a vast expanse of translucent ice that hurtled toward the fiery dragon, stacking layer upon layer on top of itself to form a massive mountain of ice as it did so.

A resounding boom rang out as the fiery dragon crashed into the mountain of ice, and flames erupted in all directions alongside countless ice crystals, which exploded into glittering ice powder that spread through the air.

As a result of the collision, the fiery dragon was unable to maintain its draconic form any longer, and it erupted into a sea of flames that crashed into the mountain of ice.

Fire and ice were erupting in all directions, creating a huge cloud of white water vapor that obscured a large section of the sky.

Han Li watched the unfolding battle from afar for a moment, then turned to depart, not wanting to get swept up in this mess.

However, right as he turned around, he suddenly felt a burst of violent spiritual power fluctuations hurtling toward him, and he reflexively crossed his arms to form a barrier in front of himself.

Immediately thereafter, he was struck by a tremendous burst of invisible form, which sent him flying toward Gan Jiuzhen while also forcibly stripping away the concealment effect of the High Zenith Invisibility Talisman.

While in mid-air, he turned to find that three more giant shadows had appeared right at the spot where he had been situated just a moment ago. It was another set of three snow toads that were virtually identical to the ones standing before Gan Jiuzhen.

A hint of foreboding welled up in his heart upon seeing this, and azure light flashed from his body as he steadied himself not far away from Gan Jiuzhen.

"I see that you recruited an ally. If it isn't for the fact that one of these babies of mine has undergone a golden eye mutation, I wouldn't have been able to discover him," the effeminate man said with a seductive smile.

Only upon hearing this did Han Li notice that the snow toad beneath the two men was indeed a little different from the other ones in that its pupils carried a faint golden hue.

Han Li took a glance at the two men, then said, "I'm only passing by, and I have no intention of getting involved in this battle."

Meanwhile, Gan Jiuzhen raised a hand, and the sea of fire that was clashing with the mountain of ice reverted back into the form of a fiery dragon before flying back to her at her behest, circling around her in a wary fashion.

She took a glance at Han Li, and a hint of bewilderment flashed through her eyes, but she didn't say anything to him as she directed her gaze back to the two men, focusing her attention on the battle at hand.

"I don't care if you're just passing by or an ally of hers. Now that you've entered our Six Toad Fire Melting Array, you'll have to die here with her! The path to the afterlife is a very lonely one, so you two can keep each other company on the way there!" the hideous man cackled in a sinister manner.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the six snow toads surrounding Han Li and Gan Jiuzhen began to glow with white radiance in unison, and a burst of violent fluctuations surged through the surrounding area.

In the next instant, a massive crystalline silver wall appeared out of thin air, trapping Han Li and Gan Jiuzhen within it.

As soon as the crystalline wall appeared, Han Li immediately felt the surrounding air temperature plummet.

At the same time, a string of crackling rang out from the surrounding space, and a series of hexagonal snowflakes began to appear. As it turned out, even the air was beginning to freeze solid.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and a layer of azure light appeared over his body as his immortal spiritual power flowed out of his dantian, forming a burst of warm energy that spread over him to keep the biting chill at bay like a layer of warm clothes.

However, he quickly discovered that his efforts were completely futile.

The glacial energy in the air was interspersed with wisps of law powers that could easily bypass this layer of immortal spiritual power, and his True Extreme Membrane also wasn't very effective at keeping out the cold.

Han Li noticed that the glacial energy was seeping through his skin before making its way toward his dantian, and he was just about to summon his Essence Fire Raven to ward off the biting chill when a layer of crimson flames suddenly appeared over his body to instantly expel the glacial energy.

He turned to discover that Gan Jiuzhen's entire body was basked in flames, and a trail of fire was extending from her wrist, connecting her flames to his.

Furthermore, she wasn't concealing her aura any longer, and as a result, Han Li discovered that she was a mid-True Immortal cultivator.

Right at this moment, Gan Jiuzhen's voice suddenly rang out beside Han Li's ears. "Fellow Daoist Liu Shi, I don't care if you really are just passing through by chance, or if you intentionally followed me here. I only have one question for you right now: are you willing to join forces with me?"

"If you're asking for my help, then this Six Toad Fire Melting Array must be quite difficult to deal with," Han Li replied via voice transmission with slightly furrowed brows.

"This is an ice-attribute array that's capable of melting even true flames. Hopefully that gives you an idea of what we're dealing with here," Gan Jiuzhen replied in a cold voice.

Right as Han Li was hesitating about how to proceed, he noticed that the layer of crimson flames around him was slowly being whittled away, and the heat that was being released was also receding.

"These two set up this array specifically to target me, so I won't be able to resist its effects for very long. Once the glacial qi freezes our meridian and dantians, we'll be completely at their mercy."

As Gan Jiuzhen was speaking, she continued to draw upon more of her immortal spiritual power in order to bolster the flames around herself and Han Li. Despite the dire situation that they were in, her voice was as calm and collected as ever, as if she were talking about something extremely mundane.

"Alright, I'll help you," Han Li replied.

As soon as their alliance was forged, the effeminate man began to chant an incantation.

The six snow toads opened their mouths in unison and began to emit an extremely high-pitched screeching sound.

Their long tongues were fluttering incessantly in their mouths as bursts of silver glacial were released, forming two walls of mist that converged from both sides before fusing into the crystalline wall that Han Li and Gan Jiuzhen were trapped in.

A string of loud crackling rang out as the crystalline wall became thicker and thicker while constantly closing in around Han Li's duo, causing the surrounding air temperature to plummet even further.

Han Li was even able to see wisps of glacial qi that were visible to the naked eye closing in around him, constantly whittling away at the layer of crimson flames that he was enveloped within.

"Fellow Daoist Liu, if I focus solely on helping you keep out the glacial qi, do you have a way to break through this array?" Gan Jiuzhen asked via voice transmissions while making a series of hand seals to strengthen her flames.

Chapter 161: Perilous Battle

"If you trust me, then I can give it a shot," Han Li replied without any hesitation.

Gan Jiuzhen wasted no time with words as she sped up in her hand seals, and the flames around her instantly began to burn more fiercely.

Han Li noticed that the trail of fire that connected the two of them had grown thicker, and the crimson flames around him had also begun to burn with greater ferocity, further protecting him from the cold.

Blue light flashed within his eyes as he quickly scanned his gaze over the crystalline wall around them. He then abruptly sprang up before charging forward, and thanks to the layer of flames around him, his speed wasn't impacted much by the glacial qi in the air.

All of a sudden, he drew to a halt in front of a certain part of the crystalline wall, following which a layer of golden scales appeared over his arm as he threw a punch at the space up ahead.

A resounding boom rang out as Han Li's fist slammed heavily into the crystalline wall.

The entire crystalline wall trembled violently while releasing bursts of blinding white light, but not only did it remain intact, not even the slightest crack had appeared on its surface.

Right at this moment, a burst of silver light shot out of the crystalline wall, then rapidly expanded to swallow up Han Li in a flash, freezing him alongside the layer of crimson flames around him.

"It seems like I was right," Gan Jiuzhen murmured to herself, and she wasn't very surprised to see what had happened to Han Li.

It seemed that she had already anticipated that this would happen, and she had intentionally used Han Li as cannon fodder to test out what would happen if the crystalline wall were attacked.

However, right at this moment, a loud thump rang out as bright golden light erupted out of Han Li's body, instantly shattering the ice around him.

Gan Jiuzhen was rather taken aback to see this, following which she praised in a heartfelt voice, "Given how powerful your physical body is, you must be a dual cultivator who focuses on refining both magic power and the physical body. It seems like I underestimated."

"Don't blame me for turning on you if you try this again," Han Li replied in a cold voice.

However, Gan Jiuzhen merely nodded in response with a calm expression, seemingly feeling as if she had done nothing wrong.

Outside the crystalline wall, the effeminate man's brows furrowed slightly as he exclaimed in incredulity, "Once someone is sealed by the glacial qi, their dantian and magic power will all be frozen! How was he able to escape?"

"If I'm not mistaken, that man is most likely a Profound Immortal. It seems like we made a mistake by going after him, but it's too late to turn back now. In any case, this seems like the perfect opportunity to try out that technique," the hideous man said as a hint of cold killing intent flashed through his eyes.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately drifted over to the crystalline wall before laying a hand onto it.

As he did so, he began to chant an incantation, and a faint buzzing sound rang out as a vast expanse of azure light appeared over his body.

The azure light resembled countless glowing azure wings that extended out of both sides of his body, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

Inside the crystalline wall, a hint of unease welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and Gan Jiuzhen's brows also furrowed slightly.

Immediately thereafter, the crystalline wall began to glow with bright silver radiance, intertwining with the azure light to form a series of circular arrays, each of which was around the size of a millstone.

The hideous man let loose a forceful yell, and all of the glacial qi within the crystalline wall instantly formed countless sharp ice spears that were roughly 10 feet in length each, all of which hurtled directly toward Han Li's duo.

The ice spears shrieked through the air as they reached Han Li and Gan Jiuzhen in the blink of an eye.

Han Li clenched his hands into tight fists before swinging them rapidly through the air, unleashing hundreds of golden fist projections to clash against the ice spears.

Meanwhile, Gan Jiuzhen summoned a huge crimson sword with a flick of her wrist.

She was making a hand seal with one hand while swinging her sword in the other, conjuring up a vast expanse of crimson sword projections that resembled a bright red sun. Balls of crimson flames were flying incessantly out of the crimson radiance to meet the spears of ice.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the golden fist projections and crimson fireballs were shattered one after another, but the ice spears didn't break. Instead, they were merely knocked back, and after pausing momentarily in mid-air, they began to hurtle toward their targets once again.

Han Li continued to swing his fists through the air to keep the ice spears at bay, and at the same time, he was scouring his surroundings with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

He discovered that every single one of these ice spears seemed to have been imbued with an extremely thin thread of law powers, and that was what granted them such incredible durability and penetrative power. Even with the body of a Profound Immortal, he definitely didn't want to be struck by those spears.

However, what was quite perplexing to him was how these two men were able to use so many law threads at once when they were clearly both only at the early-True Immortal Stage.

On top of that, a hint of surprise and recognition also flashed through his eyes at the sight of the huge crimson sword that Gan Jiuzhen was wielding.

This was the exact same weapon that Wyrm 3 had wielded on Red Moon Island, so unless Wyrm 3 had been slain and had their treasure taken, or had lent their sword to this woman, then she was none other than Wyrm 3.

He was rather taken aback by the notion that the Transient Guild member that had led everyone on the mission to kill Gongshu Hong would be a woman.

At the same time, the crystalline wall was continuing to get thicker and thicker under the effeminate man's continued efforts. The glacial qi inside was also becoming denser and denser, and Han Li and Gan Jiuzhen were slowly being cornered.

"We can't keep going like this, Fellow Daoist Liu. At this rate, we'll either be overwhelmed by these ice spears or get frozen to death by the glacial qi," Gan Jiuzhen said to Han Li through voice transmission with a grim look in her eyes.

"Do you have a way out of this?" Han Li asked.

He was naturally aware of this as well, and he had already instructed his Essence Fire Raven to remain in his body and protect his internal organs against the infiltration of glacial qi, so he was going to be fine for the time being, but the situation would undoubtedly turn quite grim if he were trapped in here for an extended period of time.

"I have a way to break this array, but I'll need you to protect me while I make preparations," Gan Jiuzhen said.

"Alright, I can do that," Han Li replied.

After arriving at the realization that Gan Jiuzhen was most likely Wyrm 3, he had already decided that he would conceal his powers in order to avoid exposing his own identity as Wyrm 15, so he was naturally glad to follow this arrangement.

Thus, he knocked back the oncoming wave of ice spears with his fists, then positioned himself in front of Gan Jiuzhen before sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing the set of nine flying swords.

The radiant white swords flashed through the air, leaving chaotic trails of white sword projections in their wake.

After releasing the swords, Han Li made a string of hand seals, and the flying swords immediately began to buzz incessantly before transforming into a vast expanse of white sword threads, which intertwined to form a sword net that was several hundred feet in size, encompassing both Gan Jiuzhen and himself within it.

Gan Jiuzhen immediately stowed her giant crimson sword away upon seeing this, then sat down onto the ground with her legs crossed.

After that, she flipped a hand over to summon a dark red square jade pendant, which had several fearsome beasts engraved upon it and was giving off an indescribable primordial aura.

A cold look appeared in the eyes of the hideous man outside the crystalline wall upon hearing this, and he communicated something to the effeminate man through voice transmission, following which the effeminate man responded with something, also via voice transmission.

The two of them then switched to different hand seals in unison, and the bodies of the six snow toads around the crystalline wall began to glow brightly as they continued to emit the same high-pitched screech.

At the same time, the layers of frost covering their skin began to melt away, revealing their glittering and translucent black bodies underneath.

Simultaneously, the hideous man's body also began to glow brightly, while his hand that was pressed against the crystalline wall turned as black as ink. A series of black veins then began to extend out of his hand in all directions, instantly crawling over the entire crystalline wall.

A hint of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and with a flick of his wrist, several balls of Heavy Water Veined Lightning fell out of his sleeve before landing in his grasp.

However, before he had a chance to unleash them, his entire body abruptly stiffened, and he was completely immobilized.

The dark red jade pendant in Gan Jiuzhen's hand had already begun to glow with crimson light, clearly having reached a critical stage in its activation, but all progress was halted there as well.

Han Li quickly realized that he had been frozen by the power of ice laws within this space, which had become drastically more potent all of a sudden.

He immediately instructed the Essence Fire Raven in his body to help him regain his mobility, but all he could hear in response were the raven's anguished cries within his consciousness.

It was clear that it had also been immobilized by the power of ice laws and was powerless to help him.

Meanwhile, all of the ice spears in the surrounding area had already turned black, and they began to hurtle toward Han Li and Gan Jiuzhen while giving off even more powerful law fluctuations.

A grim look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

With his Profound Immortal body, he would perhaps be able to withstand the assault for a while, but Gan Jiuzhen was in an extremely perilous situation.

If she were to be killed, then he would have to face the two enemy immortals and snow toads on his own, which was far from an appealing prospect.

With that in mind, he began to burn through his blood essence in order to stimulate the immortal spiritual power within his body. Even so, he was only able to draw upon less than a thousandth of the total immortal spiritual power that he possessed, and he directed it into the ball of Heavy Water Veined Lightning in his hand.

A flash of lightning appeared, and the ball of Heavy Water Veined Lightning fell out of Han Li's sleeve.

A thunderous explosion rang out as a black sun appeared no more than a foot away from Han Li. Contained within the black sun was a vast expanse of silver light that inundated Han Li's entire body.

An instant later, Gan Jiuzhen was also swallowed up by the explosion of black and silver light.

A string of rumbling thunderclaps rang out as countless tiny black particles erupted in all directions, forming a spherical shockwave that expanded rapidly, causing the surrounding space to tremble and quake.

In the face of the violent explosion, all of the oncoming ice spears were finally shattered, and the entire space was plunged into complete chaos.

Chapter 162: A Gift

The surrounding crystalline wall began to tremble violently as it struggled to contain the powerful shockwave, and a burst of deafening rumbling rang out.

The six mountainous snow toads also shuddered violently, and black blood began to seep out of all of their eyes as their auras quickly fell into decline.

Before the explosion had even completely subsided, several draconic roars suddenly rang out in rapid succession from within the crystalline wall.

Immediately thereafter, a vast expanse of fiery radiance erupted out of the black and silver light as three fiery wyrms formed by crimson flames emerged. Each wyrm was over 1,000 feet in length, and scorching flames were pouring out of their mouths as they pounced toward the surrounding crystalline wall.

A resounding boom rang out as the crystalline wall shuddered violently, and it instantly began to melt away as plumes of black smoke rose up from its surface.

A loud sizzling sound rang out, and before long, the three crimson fiery wyrms had already melted a large hole into the crystalline wall. Upon flying out of the wall, the three wyrms intertwined to form a churning river of crimson fire that swept directly toward the pair of enemy cultivators.

At this point, the hideous man had already flown back onto the head of the golden-eyed snow toad, and the two men hurriedly made a series of hand seals with alarmed looks on their faces as they witnessed the destruction of their array.

In the next instant, the six snow toads opened their mouths in unison to blast forth a vast cloud of black glacial qi, which formed a wall of ice in mid-air to oppose the river of flames.

Meanwhile, Han Li also flew out of the crystalline wall, and he appeared in a rather sorry state with his robes in complete tatters. However, aside from some slight jostling to his internal organs, he remained largely unharmed.

He raised his head to look up at the scorching river of crimson flames up above, and a complex look flashed through his eyes.

The fiery river didn't just contain the power of fire laws. Instead, it was imbued with the power of blood laws, the aura of which was very similar to that of the deceased Gongshu Hong.

He turned to discover that Gang Jiuzhen's dress had also been torn in many places, revealing large sections of her fair and delicate skin. The red veil that was covering her face had also disappeared, and her gorgeous features were looking a little pale.

Despite this, her eyes were filled with cold killing intent, and the square jade pendant clutched in her hand continued to glow brightly whiles the runes inscribed upon it flashed incessantly, but its crimson color had significantly faded compared with before.

At this point, Han Li could basically confirm beyond a reasonable doubt that this woman was indeed Wyrm 3.

Back on Red Moon Island, Wrym 3 had declared that she had some matters to take care of following Gongshu Hong's demise, and it seemed that these matters had mostly involved collecting the treasures left behind by Gongshu Hong.

A string of loud crackling rang out incessantly as plumes of black mist rose up from the point where the river of fire was clashing against the wall of ice, resembling a dark cloud that obscured the night sky.

At this point, the two cultivators standing atop the toad's head were looking far less comfortable and composed than before.

Their cultivation bases were inferior to Gan Jiuzhen's, and now, the Six Toad Fire Melting Array that they had been relying heavily upon had been broken. The two of them exchanged a glance, and both of them were beginning to consider fleeing the battle.

The three snow toads on the other side had also arrived on the scene, but the glacial qi surging out of the mouths of the six toads was only just enough to keep the river of crimson flames at bay.

Gan Jiuzhen gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and she opened her mouth to expel a ball of blood essence, causing her complexion to pale even further.

She then pointed a finger at the ball of blood essence, and it transformed into a miniature dragon before instantly vanishing into the jade pendant in her hand.

Yet another draconic roar rang out, and the crimson light glowing from the jade pendant became even brighter as a fourth crimson fiery wyrm flew out from within before joining the river of fire, granting it a boost in power and momentum.

At the same time, the color of the jade pendant had faded even further.

With the inclusion of the fourth fiery wyrm, the river of flames was expanded even further, and a fearsome aura began to spread through the surrounding area.

The two cultivators standing atop the toad's head immediately felt their heart rates elevating drastically, while the blood in their veins also began to churn and surge in an uncontrolled manner.

The two of them were understandably alarmed by this turn of events, and they hurriedly diverted a part of their immortal spiritual power to quell the unrest in their bodies. As a result, there was less immortal spiritual power to support the six snow toads, and the glacial qi surging out of their mouths instantly became diminished.

The surging river of flames instantly overwhelmed the diminished glacial qi, inundating the snow toads and the two men in the blink of an eye.

Two agonized howls rang out from within the flames, and flashes of light began to appear from the treasures being frantically summoned by the two cultivators, but it didn't take long before those flashes of light and their anguished screams subsided.

Han Li withdrew his nine flying swords upon seeing this, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing wisps of immortal spiritual power out of his fingertips to collect all of the heavy water particles that had scattered throughout the area following the explosion of the Heavy Water Veined Lightning.

Moments later, all of the commotion within the sea of crimson flame finally subsided.

Gan Jiuzhen made a hand seal with one hand, then reached out with her other hand, and the vast expanse of crimson flames instantly reverted back into four crimson wyrms that rose up into the heavens before vanishing into the jade pendant in her hand.

All that remained in mid-air was a pair of severely ravaged bodies that were tumbling down toward the ground.

As for those snow toads, their bodies couldn't compare with the body of an immortal, and they had been incinerated to the point that there was nothing of them left.

Gan Jiuzhen flipped a hand over to produce several pills that she devoured, then made a beckoning motion, and two storage bracelets rose up into the air before falling into her grasp.

However, she didn't even look at them before tossing one of them to Han Li, who caught the storage bracelet without any hesitation.

"Fellow Daoist Liu, there's a question that's been on my mind this entire time. Have we met somewhere before this trip?" Gan Jiuzhen asked as she turned to Han Li with a hint of scrutiny in her eyes.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he replied in a calm voice, "If I had met someone as stunning as you before, I would be sure to remember you, but I don't recall any previous encounters between us."

Gan Jiuzhen's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this, and it was clear that she didn't really believe what Han Li was saying.

However, she had no intention of pursuing this matter any further, and she said, "In any case, I owe you my thanks for today. I don't like to owe anyone any favors, so you can have this Azure Wind Lock Immortal Talisman as a gift."

She swept a sleeve through the air as she spoke, and a purple talisman flew out toward Han Li.

Han Li raised a hand to catch the talisman, and he took a glance at it to find that it was riddled with extremely profound silver runes, indicating that it was a high-grade talisman that had been written in beveled silver text.

The talisman contained an abundance of spiritual power, and it appeared to have been of an even higher caliber than the High Zenith Invisibility Talisman and the Armor Origin Talisman.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Gan." Han Li cupped his fist in a salute, then stowed the talisman away for further examination later.

"I'll ignore the fact that you followed me here this time, but don't blame me for turning on you if this happens again," Gan Jiuzhen declared, then promptly turned and departed.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he watched Gan Jiuzhen's departing figure, and he didn't linger here any longer, quickly flying back the same way he had come to return to the ark.

The battle had taken place very far away from the ark, so no one else had noticed anything, and the two Body Integration Stage elders of the Chengquan Trading House had been seated on the deck this entire time.

Han Li took a moment to conceal himself, then returned to his room on the ark in a stealthy fashion.

The night quickly passed by, and the flying ark continued on its journey at first light the next day.

It naturally didn't take long before the man with the Kou surname discovered Gan Jiuzhen's disappearance.

Aside from Han Li, no one on the ark knew what had happened that night, and Han Li naturally wasn't going to tell anyone about what had transpired.

The man with the Kou surname was a little perplexed and dismayed, but there was nothing he could do. After all, they hadn't arrived at their destination yet, and he hadn't issued the reward for the mission, so essentially, Gan Jiuzhen had protected the ark for a large stretch of their journey free of charge.

In contrast with the Lost Grave Forest, the Black Rock Desert was extremely desolate, with not even a single living creature to be seen.

The flying ark was traveling at top speed, and not even the concealment restrictions had been activated as all of the spiritual power was contributing toward further acceleration.

The ark was flying so quickly that it was nothing more than a white shadow in the air, and even though there were no signs of any demon beasts in the area, Han Li was still requested by the man with the Kou surname to stand on lookout duty with the two Body Integration Stage elders.

Close to half a day passed by very quickly, and the flying ark was venturing quite deep into the Black Rock Desert.

Han Li was standing on one side of the ark, surveying the ground down below, and just a moment ago, he had clearly felt the gravitational force in the area beginning to increase.

The flying ark was somewhat affected by this, and the white light glowing from its surface began to flicker slightly, while its speed was also negatively impacted.

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li released his enormous spiritual sense, sending it several thousand feet deep into the ground.

There's a vast abundance of Origin Magnetic Profound Iron here. No wonder it's able to generate such tremendous suction gravitational force.

Aside from that, he had also verified that there were no dark beasts lurking in the area, unless they were hiding even deeper underground.

Han Li continued to probe even deeper underground with his spiritual sense, and a surprised look quickly appeared in his eyes.

Due to the presence of the underground ore veins, there were all types of chaotic underground energies and gravitational forces intertwining deep beneath the earth, preventing his spiritual sense from being able to extend down any further.

Instead of forcing the issue, he made a compromise and began to spread his spiritual sense outward instead.

A short while later, Han Li abruptly raised his head and cast his gaze forward, seemingly having spotted something.

However, after a moment of contemplation, he decided not to raise the alarm, but blue light was flashing in his eyes as he took a closer look.

Moments later, one of the Body Integration Stage elders on the other side of the ark suddenly sprang to his feet, having detected the presence of some black lizards up ahead with his spiritual sense.

Having already made this trip many times, he was quite familiar with the Black Rock Desert, and he immediately identified these black lizards to be a type of dark beast known as Darkback Iron Lizards, which were quite commonly seen in the Black Rock Desert. Their bodies were as hard as iron and steel, but they weren't particularly powerful, and the ones up ahead were roughly around the Foundation Establishment Stage.

The only concern that he had was that these lizards were social creatures that often resided in packs that numbered in the hundreds of millions, and their sheer numbers alone could prove to be very difficult to deal with.

Furthermore, according to his knowledge, these creatures shouldn't have been active during the day.

Chapter 163: Beast Tide Crisis

A hint of befuddlement flashed through his eyes, but he wasn't particularly concerned, seeing as these were just a few low-grade Darkback Iron Lizards.

The other Body Integration Stage elder soon noticed the Darkback Iron Lizards up ahead as well, but just like the other elder, he decided that they posed no threat.

However, as the flying ark continued onward, the expressions of the two Body Integration Stage elders were becoming more and more uneasy.

Initially, the Darkback Iron Lizards had only emerged in batches of a few at a time, but they quickly began coming out in droves, and they were also becoming more and more powerful. At this point, there were already some lizards at or above the Core Formation Stage.

"Fellow Daoist Liu, I get the sense that something isn't quite right," the Body Integration Stage elder on the left hand side said in a grim voice.

A thought seemed to have occurred to Elder Liu upon hearing this, and judging from his reaction, it wasn't an encouraging thought.

The spiritual sense of the other people on the ark wasn't able to reach as far and wide as that of the two Body Integration Stage elders, but they were also beginning to notice the large numbers of Darkback Iron Lizards in the area, and everyone was becoming more and more uneasy.

The man with the Kou surname flew over to the two elders, then asked in an urgent voice, "What's the deal with all these lizards, seniors?"

The two elders exchanged a glance with one another, following which one of them replied, "We don't know what's going on at the moment, but these Darkback Iron Lizards are supposed to be dark beasts, and we've never seen them active during the day. As long as we get out of this area quickly, there shouldn't be any problems."

"Full speed ahead! We have to get out of here as quickly as possible!" the man with the Kou surname instructed as he turned to one of his subordinates.

Meanwhile, Han Li had remained silent this entire time, surveying his surroundings with his hands clasped behind his back.

The man with the Kou surname was rather displeased with Han Li's detached attitude, but he couldn't openly criticize Han Li for his attitude, and all he could do was shake his head slightly in displeasure.

Out of the two Body Integration cultivators that he had hired, one of them had suddenly disappeared for some unknown reason, while the other one was clearly unfamiliar with the area. At this point, he could only pray that no major mishaps occurred, and that they could get out of this dangerous area as quickly as possible.

As the flying ark continued onward, the gravitational force coming from down below was becoming more and more pronounced.

The ark was a treasure of a decent caliber, but its enormous size and weight meant that it inevitably slowed down in the face of the increased gravity.

What was even more concerning was that the number of Darkback Iron Lizards up ahead was increasing exponentially, and some of them had even begun roaring at the flying ark, looking as if they were going to pounce.

Upon spotting several larger lizards that possessed Nascent Soul Stage powers, the two Body Integration Stage elders were finally unable to maintain their composure any longer.

The man with the Kou surname could also see that something was clearly amiss, and he suggested, "Given the current situation, I suggest we turn back and wait for a few days before attempting to cross this Black Rock Desert again. It'll only be a delay for a few days, and safety is paramount."

Both of the Body Integration Stage elders were also tempted by this proposition.

They hadn't been traveling through the Black Rock Desert for a very long time, so if they were to turn back now, they should've had enough time to get out of the desert before nightfall.

However, right as Elder Liu was about to respond, an unforeseen turn of events suddenly began to unfold.

A burst of rumbling rang out up ahead, and the earth in a radius of several dozens of kilometers began to tremble violently. Even the flying ark was somewhat affected, swaying slightly as if it were experiencing turbulence.

Everyone on the ark cast their eyes forward with astonished looks on their faces.

Far away in the distance, a series of thick black pillars were erupting into the heavens, much like an array of black mountains abruptly rising up from the ground.

The black pillars then collapsed into countless black particles, all of which began surging toward the flying ark like a black sea.

Through their spiritual sense, the people on the ark could detect that these black dots on the horizon were all Darkback Iron Lizards of different sizes.

In the blink of an eye, the entire landscape up ahead was completely inundated by this surging black wave, to the point that barely anything else was visible.

"We've run into a beast tide!" Elder Liu exclaimed with an alarmed expression.

Everyone instantly turned deathly pale as this realization dawned on them, and Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly.

The book that he had read concerning the Black Rock Desert had mentioned this type of beast tide, and it was an extremely perilous phenomenon. In some circumstances, these beast tides could even wear down an immortal until they died.

A layer of cold sweat instantly beaded up on the forehead of the man with the Kou surname, and he desperately yelled, "Turn the ark around! Hurry!"

The entire ark was instantly plunged into chaos, with everyone stumbling around on deck in a blind panic.

Dazzling white light erupted out of the ark as it was forcibly drawn to a halt, following which it quickly turned tail to flee back the same way it had come from.

However, it wasn't able to get very far before an earth-shattering boom rang out up ahead, and the earth opened up to release another massive pillar of Darkback Iron Lizards that obstructed their escape.

The ark was caught in between countless lizards, which were closing in from both the front and the rear.

There were still openings on either side of the ark, but the two swarms of lizards in front of and behind the ark were rapidly spreading, quickly forming an encirclement that completely surrounded the ark from all directions.

Everyone's faces had paled even further upon seeing this. No matter how sturdy the ark was, there was no way it would've been able to last very long in the face of such a formidable beast tide.

"What do we do, seniors?"

The man with the Kou surname was sweating and trembling uncontrollably as he turned to the three Body Integration cultivators on the ark.

The expressions of the two Body Integration Stage elders had turned extremely grim, and at this point, they had no choice but to fight for their lives.

Given their cultivation bases, if they were to abandon the ark and flee on their own, perhaps there was a 50% chance that they would be able to escape alive. However, as elders of the Chengquan Trading House, which was one of the three largest trading houses in the entire immortal region, they were bound by duty to protect the trading house's interests in times of peril. If they were to flee here, then they would be condemned and hunted across the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed, but he remained calm and collected. He took a few glances on either side of the ark, following which an intrigued look appeared on his face.

"Have you discovered something, Fellow Daoist Liu?" Elder Liu hurriedly asked upon seeing this.

"If you take a closer look, it seems like these lizards aren't targeting us," Han Li replied.

The two Body Integration Stage elders faltered slightly upon hearing this, then turned to inspect their surroundings, and sure enough, the lizards were fighting among themselves, ferociously biting and clawing at one another.

Furthermore, everyone quickly noticed that the two swarms of lizards were slightly different in appearance. The lizards up ahead had some dark red patterns on their bodies, while the ones behind the ark were completely black in color, indicating that they were different species.

"I see what's happening now. These two swarms of lizards are fighting over this territory! No wonder they've appeared during the day," Elder Liu mused as an enlightened look appeared in his eyes.

"In any case, seeing as we're not their target, we have to think of a way to get out of here as soon as possible. Otherwise, we'll still get swept up in their conflict regardless," the other elder said in a grim voice.

The man with the Kou surname immediately nodded in response, and after issuing a series of instructions, the flying ark began to glow with dazzling white light as it flew toward the left.

At this point, the two swarms of lizards had already completely clashed and were engaged in a fierce battle.

Blinded by their bloodlust, they were lashing out at anything that wasn't one of their brethren, and the giant flying ark was no exception.

A protective light barrier instantly appeared around the ark, advancing arduously as it warded off attacks from countless iron lizards.

Han Li and the two Body Integration Stage elders immediately sprang into action upon seeing this.

Elder Liu began to chant an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals, and a burst of black flames instantly surged out of his body.

The black flames then transformed into countless fiery black threads at his behest, and the fiery threads intertwined to form an enormous net that was several thousand feet in size before sweeping toward the masses of surrounding iron lizards.

All of a sudden, the fiery black net exploded violently, causing the entire space to tremble as waves of fire surged forth in all directions, instantly forming a sea of black flames that was several kilometers in size.

All of the iron lizards that came into contact with the sea of fire instantly had their bodies blown into pieces before falling out of the sky as chunks of charred flesh.

Meanwhile, the other elder made a hand seal with one hand, and blue light flashed around him, following which a pair of massive blue lightning pythons sprang forth. Each of the pythons was several hundred feet in length, and both of them had dazzling blue lightning crackling around them as they pounced toward the lizard tide.

Upon making contact with the iron lizards, the blue lightning pythons instantly exploded, sending countless thick bolts of lightning erupting in all directions.

All of the iron lizards struck by the lightning instantly exploded, sending countless destroyed bodies raining out of the sky.

As for Han Li, he had turned to his trusty set of nine flying swords, which had transformed into countless sword threads that were slicing through large swathes of iron lizards with ease.

The three of them were each standing on one side of the ark, doing their best to slay the oncoming iron lizards.

However, there were simply far too many of these creatures, and despite their best efforts, they were only able to keep some of the iron lizards at bay, with countless more still able to crash into the ark.

A string of loud thumps rang out incessantly, and the ark resembled a small raft in a turbulent sea, just barely holding onto dear life in the face of the lizard tide.

The protective light barrier around the ark was also trembling violently, much to the panic and horror of everyone on the ark.

All of a sudden, a grating roar that resembled the harsh sound of metal grinding on metal rang out up ahead, and it was clearly audible even through the commotion of the unfolding battle.

Everyone on the ark felt a burst of sharp pain in their heads, as if they had just been pricked by steel needles, and their faces had paled even further.

The hearts of the two Body Integration Stage elders also shuddered upon hearing this roar.

Over 10,000 feet up ahead, a giant iron lizard that was around 500 to 600 feet in size had emerged out of the ground. Its body was completely black, and there were several thick black hooked spikes on its back, while sharp fangs were jutting out of its mouth, giving it an extremely fearsome appearance.

Chapter 164: Hidden Powerful Being

An enormous aura was emanating from the body of the giant lizard, indicating that it possessed Body Integration Stage power.

Before everyone had a chance to react, another thunderous roar rang out from behind them.

The earth exploded as another giant lizard of roughly the same size as the Body Integration Stage lizard emerged, and it was just as fearsome in appearance, with bright patterns all over its back and a pair of long dark red horns on its head.

Furthermore, it was also giving off a Body Integration Stage aura!

"Those are both iron lizard kings! No wonder there are so many of them here," Elder Liu murmured to himself as his pupils contracted drastically.

The eyes of the man with the Kou surname suddenly lit up as he asked, "Does that mean that if these iron lizard kings die, then the battle will be over?"

"That may be the case, but the two of them are quite evenly matched, so I'm afraid there won't be a decisive outcome anytime soon. Under normal circumstances, Elder Qi and I would perhaps be able to slay the lizard kings, but given the current situation..." Elder Liu's voice trailed off here, and he heaved a faint sigh at the sight of the countless iron lizards around the ark.

Right at this moment, the two lizard kings exchanged a glance from afar, then sprang up into the air as fast as lightning.

The two massive creatures clashed violently amid a resounding thump in the air not far away from the ark, then engaged one another in a ferocious tussle.

Violent shockwaves were sent sweeping through the air in all directions, interspersed with bursts of dazzling black and red light.

All of the smaller iron lizards nearby were instantly sent flying, and some were even torn to shreds by the shockwaves.

In the face of the powerful shockwaves, the protective light barrier around the ark was trembling violently, and the ark itself was forcibly diverted away from its original path.

The man with the Kou surname took a glance at the gradually thinning light barrier, and he urged in a panicked voice, "The ark isn't going to be able to last much longer! You have to think of something, seniors!"

However, the two Body Integration Stage elders were only able to do their best to keep the waves of iron lizards at bay, and even that was proving to be a tall order for them, so there was no way for them to do anything else.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly raised a hand before flicking a finger through the air.

A burst of blinding white light abruptly erupted out of nowhere, causing everyone to instinctively close their eyes.

Furthermore, a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations had surged out of the white light to completely disable the spiritual sense of everyone on the ark.

In the next instant, Han Li vanished from the spot amid a flash of silver lightning, then reappeared an instant later directly above the heads of the two giant lizard kings several thousand feet away.

Golden light flashed from his fists as he sent them crashing down upon the heads of the lizard kings, and the two giant creatures didn't even have any time to react before their heads were shattered with ease like a pair of eggs, sending huge volumes of blood and intracranial fluids splattering in all directions.

The two giant lizards didn't even have a chance to cry out before they were reduced to a pair of corpses that fell out of the sky before slamming heavily down onto the ground.

Meanwhile, silver lightning flashed from Han Li's body once again, and in the next instant, he had already returned to the ark.

All of this had transpired within the span of no more than a second, and all of the white light vanished immediately thereafter, as if it had never even appeared in the first place.

Everyone on the ark was completely rooted to the spot.

"What was that white light just now?" someone asked.

No one had an answer, and even the two Body Integration Stage elders were feeling completely dumbfounded.

All of a sudden, one of the Body Integration Stage elders realized that all of the iron lizards in the area had suddenly stopped fighting. Furthermore, the bloodlust in their eyes had faded, replaced by a look of shock and panic.

In the next instant, several loud roars rang out from within the hordes of iron lizards, and the two opposing armies quickly separated before scurrying away and fleeing back into the earth. In the blink of an eye, more than half of the iron lizards in the area had disappeared, and the landscape finally became visible again.

"Look! The two iron lizard kings are dead!"

Someone on the ark had spotted the pair of iron lizard king bodies laying on the ground several thousand feet away, and at this moment, the pair bodies were being carried away by some slightly smaller iron lizards.

Everyone was astonished to see this, including the pair of Body Integration Stage elders.

"Regardless of what happened here, I think our best course of action would be to get out of here as quickly as possible," Han Li said.

The man with the Kou surname hurriedly nodded in response. "You're right, Senior Liu. Full speed ahead!"

The flying ark began to glow with bright white radiance as it continued onward at full speed, quickly flying out of the area.

They weren't pursued by any iron lizards, and everyone heaved a collective sigh of relief upon seeing this.

"What happened just now?"

"I don't know. After that flash of white light, both of the iron lizard kings were killed!"

"If you ask me, there must've been a hidden powerful being on the ark, and they must've been the one that killed the two iron lizard kings, but they didn't want to blow their cover, so they used that white light to disguise their actions."

"That's preposterous! If you ask me, some immortal must've just so happened to have been passing through. There's no way any ordinary person would've been able to kill two Body Integration Stage demon beasts in the blink of an eye!"

"If it really was just some immortal passing by, then why did they release that white light as a smokescreen?"

Everyone on the ark was discussing what had just happened, and the atmosphere had become a little peculiar.

The two Body Integration Stage elders were also subtly examining everyone on the ark, as if they were trying to figure out who this hidden powerful being was.

However, they didn't dare to pry excessively.

Given how that person was able to kill those two iron lizard kings so quickly, they had to have been at least a Grand Ascension cultivator, or even a legendary True Immortal, and they certainly didn't dare to risk irking such a powerful being.

Meanwhile, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on the deck of the ark, and he occasionally came under scrutiny from those around him, but he paid those prying eyes no heed.

The rest of the trip was very smooth, and they emerged from the Black Rock desert that night without coming under any further attacks, much to everyone's relief.

After flying out of the Black Rock Desert, they were greeted by the sight of a vast grassland.

Time slowly passed by, and everyone's curiosity toward the identity of that mysterious powerful being gradually faded as the days of monotonous travel continued.

Over half a year passed by in the blink of an eye, and the ark was flying over a bleak desert.

Their destination, Bright Hill City, was already very close, situated just on the other side of this desert.

The journey had been quite smooth, and the ark had encountered some perilous situations, but none as dire as the one they had run into in the Black Rock Desert.

At this moment, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed in his room.

He was making a rapid series of hand seals as a ball of heavy water was slowly fusing with the arcs of silver lightning in front of him.

Soon, a black ball emerged, and it was another ball of Heavy Water Veined Lightning.

An elated look appeared on his face as he stowed the ball of lightning away.

Along this journey, Han Li had been refining Heavy Water Veined Lightning whenever he had some spare time, and at this point, he had already exhausted close to half of his supply of heavy water to produce over 30 balls of Heavy Water Veined Lightning.

He took a moment to adjust his robes before rising to his feet, then emerged onto the deck and cast his gaze toward the yellow desert down below.

The desert was called the Boundless Sand Sea, and it was extremely vast, but the demon beasts here were very weak and sparse, so it was a very safe area.

Even the two Body Integration Stage elders weren't standing on lookout duty on the deck.

This journey had taken a long time, but once he arrived at Bright Hill City, he would have access to teleportation arrays that would significantly speed up his travels.

The man with the Kou surname just so happened to be nearby, and he immediately approached Han Li before extending a greeting, in response to which Han Li gave a slight nod.

The man with the Kou surname was looking rather excited as he said, "We're less than a day away from Bright Hill City now, Senior Liu. Thank you for your efforts over the course of this journey."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Kou. I took on this mission, so it's only right that I fulfill my duty," Han Li replied with a smile.

"What are your plans after reaching Bright Hill City, Senior Liu?" the man with the Kou surname asked.

"I..." Han Li's voice abruptly trailed off here as he suddenly turned his gaze to the right.

Several shadows had appeared on the distant horizon in that direction, alongside an extremely faint howling sound.

He immediately released his spiritual sense, upon which a grim look appeared on his face.

"What's wrong, Senior Liu?"

The man with the Kou surname followed Han Li's gaze while also releasing his spiritual sense, and his expression instantly changed drastically as he yelled, "It's an astral wind storm! Stop the ark and dig a hole for the ark to hide in! Hurry!"

None of the books that Han Li had purchased mentioned this so-called astral wind storm, but judging from the reaction displayed by the man with the Kou surname, it had to have been something quite dangerous.

The ark erupted into complete pandemonium as others quickly began to notice the approaching storm on the horizon, and those who were familiar with the climate in the area were extremely alarmed.

The ark gradually drew to a halt, following which the two Body Integration Stage elders flew out of their rooms.

Elder Qi flipped a hand over to produce a large yellow flag, and the flag swelled drastically to several dozen times its original size at his behest, radiating dazzling yellow light as it did so.

The elder swept a sleeve through the air, and a thick pillar of yellow light shot forth before hurtling into the desert sand down below.

The earth in a radius of several dozen kilometers trembled violently as the earth abruptly split open before parting in either direction.

Moments later, a massive black rift appeared on the ground, resembling a dark abyss that was several thousand feet deep.

Meanwhile, the black shadows in the distance were quickly approaching, revealing themselves to be a series of giant black clouds, within which a thunderous howling sound was ringing out incessantly.

Ferocious gusts of wind were whipped around the ark, sending vast volumes of sand flying up into the sky.

"Hurry!" the man with the Kou surname urged.

The ark immediately descended into the massive rift in the ground, quickly vanishing into it.

Elder Qi then swept the flag that he was holding through the air, and the rift closed itself from above, forming a massive underground cavern around the ark.

Meanwhile, ferocious gusts of yellow wind swept over the desert up above like a flight of massive wind dragons that obscured the entire sky.

The sand of the desert was whipped up into a frenzy by the wind, and the entire area had been plunged into complete chaos.

The gusts of wind resembled the whip of a giant that was repeatedly lashing against the ground with devastating impact, and even though the flying ark was several thousand feet beneath the ground, everyone could still clearly hear the thunderous commotion ringing out up above.

Chapter 165: Familiar

The man with the Kou surname was standing next to Han Li, and he said in a relieved voice, "It's a good thing that Senior Liu noticed it very early. Otherwise, we would've been in grave peril."

"What is this astral wind storm that you speak of, Fellow Daoist Kou?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"The astral wind storm is a type of natural phenomenon that only arises in this desert, and it's a very rare occurrence, but once it does arise, it'll wreak havoc over the area in a radius of hundreds of thousands of kilometers.

“The only way to deal with this disaster is to hide deep underground and wait for the storm to pass before returning to the surface," the man with the Kou surname explained, and he was clearly extremely wary of this form of natural disaster.

"I've crossed this desert no fewer than 100 times, and this is only the second time I've encountered this disaster. At the time, I witnessed a flying ark that was unable to make it underground in time being instantly pulverized into dust by the storm," Elder Qi said with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"Apparently, this desert was once a city, but for some reason, an astral wind storm suddenly swept over the city one day, instantly razing it to the ground, and that's how this desert came to be," Elder Liu added.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

"We're no more than a day away from our destination, but it looks like we'll have to wait a few more days until this astral wind storm passes before we continue onward," the man with the Kou surname sighed.

He then departed to examine whether any of the goods on the ark had been damaged.

Meanwhile, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed and closed his eyes to meditate.

The desert above Han Li and the others was currently being ravaged by the astral wind storm, but all was peaceful and tranquil hundreds of thousands of kilometers away from the Boundless Sand Sea.

Along a vast mountain range that stretched for tens of thousands of kilometers were countless lush forests, interspersed throughout which were a series of cities, towns, and villages.

At the center of the mountain range was an azure city that took up a massive area. Its walls were over 1,000 feet tall, and inscribed in large golden characters above the city gates were the words "Bright Hill City".

The city appeared to have been no smaller than Black Wind City, and it was filled with tall buildings that differed in construction style compared with the ones in Black Wind City in that these ones were more unrefined and rough around the edges, but appeared more imposing and majestic.

One thriving street after another was visible in the city, stretching as far as the eyes could see.

At the center of Bright Hill City was a massive white pagoda, standing out as a particularly eye-catching landmark, even compared with all of the tall buildings around it.

This was where the teleportation arrays in the city were situated, and people were regularly entering and exiting the building, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

Right at this moment, two figures emerged from the entrance of the giant pagoda side by side.

One of them was an elderly man with a head of white hair coupled with a white beard. He was wearing a five-colored brocade robe, and despite his apparently advanced age, he was looking very sharp and full of vigor.

Beside him was a handsome young man in a tight-fitting black robe with a cold look in his eyes.

"Brother Fang, if I recall correctly, there aren't going to be any more teleportation arrays along the rest of your journey. On top of that, the Black Wind Sea is situated in the westernmost region of the continent, and I've heard that it's a very difficult place to access," the brocade-robed elderly man said.

"Given how much time has passed, we don't even know if he's still in the Black Wind Sea. As a safety precaution, I'll have to trouble you to verify his location again," Fang Pan said as he took a glance up at the sky.

"Very well."

The brocade-robed elderly man nodded in response, then flipped a hand over to produce a plate treasure. He brought his index and middle fingers together before pointing them directly at the plate, then began chanting an incantation.

As he did so, the plate began to radiate dazzling golden light, and a speck of flickering crimson light emerged extremely close to the center of the plate, much to the elderly man's surprise.

"Has he already left the Black Wind Sea?" Fang Pan asked, clearly already expecting this outcome.

"Not only that, but he's currently very close to this city," the brocade-robed elderly man replied with an incredulous expression.

Fang Pan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Oh? Is he located to the west of us?"

"That's right, but for some reason, he seems to have stopped," the brocade-robed elderly man replied with a perplexed expression.

"Come with me," Fang Pan said as he flew out of the city as a streak of light, and the elderly man hurriedly followed along.

A short while later, the two of them appeared on the summit of a tall mountain several hundred kilometers away from the city, watching the astral wind storm that was ravaging the landscape far away in the west.

"It looks like he's taking shelter from some type of natural disaster. There's no need to wait any longer, let's go straight to him," Fang Pan said.

The brocade-robed elderly man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. "We've already tracked him for so long, why the hurry now? Given his current location, his next destination will surely be Bright Hill City, so why don't we make some preparations here and ambush him once he arrives?"

"You can wait here if you like, but I'm not going to wait even a moment longer!" Fang Pan declared as he abruptly sprang up from the mountain summit, then instantly vanished into the distance.

The brocade-robed elderly man shook his head as he heaved a faint sigh, then also vanished from the spot amid a flash of five-colored light.

……

Meanwhile.

Inside the underground cavern, the sound of the howling wind ringing out up above was clearly audible, and everyone, including Han Li, was seated with their eyes closed in silent meditation.

All of a sudden, his brows suddenly furrowed tightly as his eyes abruptly sprang open.

Just now, the blood essence in his body had suddenly become extremely agitated, churning through his veins in a frenzy, to the point that he was feeling an unnatural heat coursing through his veins.

Is something approaching me?

A strong sense of unease welled up in his heart.

After a moment of contemplation, he instantly rose to his feet, and everyone around him was startled by this sudden movement as they also opened their eyes to observe him with wary expressions.

He paid no heed to everyone's reactions as he abruptly vanished from the spot amid a flash of azure light.

The other people in the underground cavern with him didn't even get a chance to say anything, and they could exchange bewildered glances with one another.

After flying out of the underground cavern, the violent astral winds came surging toward him from all directions like countless sharp blades.

Han Li's entire body was enveloped within a layer of azure light, but that still wasn't enough to prevent the coarse sand from lashing against his face.

His eyes narrowed slightly as he turned toward a certain direction, then began to fly through the astral winds as a streak of azure light.

Inside the violent storm, visibility was virtually zero, and even though it wasn't very difficult for Han Li to traverse through the storm, his speed was significantly limited, so he wasn't able to get very far even after flying for an entire hour.

Right as he was about to accelerate to full speed and fly out of the area encompassed within the storm in one go, he suddenly detected two powerful auras appear within several thousand feet of him without any warning.

He immediately drew to a halt and swept his gaze across his surroundings, upon which he discovered a pair of indistinct humanoid figures situated in the storm to his right.

Only after the two of them had flown a further several hundred feet did they gradually become clearly visible to Han Li, revealing themselves to be a young man in black and a brocade-robed elderly man.

Each of them was enveloped in a light barrier that kept the storm at bay, and the swirling sand was only able to leave some faint white marks on the light barriers.

Han Li took a quick glance at the two figures, and his heart sank slightly as he asked, "Why are you getting in my way, fellow daoists?"

Both of them were mid-True Immortal cultivators, and it was clear that they hadn't approached him with friendly intentions.

Furthermore, for some reason, the two of them felt vaguely familiar to him, but he couldn't recall where he had seen them before no matter how hard he tried.

The brocade-robed elderly man was quite taken aback by this question, and he turned to the young man in black with a perplexed expression.

However, the latter's gaze remained fixed firmly on Han Li as he harrumphed coldly, "You think you can fool us with that disguise of yours, Han Li?"

Han Li was quite alarmed at the fact that he was being referred to directly by name, and a dark look appeared on his face as he asked, "Who are you?"

"I don't think he's putting on an act, Brother Fang. It seems like he really doesn't know who we are. Could it be that he lost his memories?" the brocade-robed elderly man asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Who cares if he's putting on an act or not? We'll just have to kill him, then search his soul, and everything will become clear," Fang Pan replied in a cold voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he abruptly vanished from the spot amid a flash of black light.

All Han Li saw was a blur flash past his eyes before the young man reappeared directly in front of him, and he was lashing out with a long black saber.

Han Li hurriedly raised a fist to oppose the saber, yet all of a sudden, Fang Pan vanished yet again.

As a result, Han Li's fist struck nothing but empty air, causing the space up ahead to shudder violently as he stumbled forward out of sheer momentum.

Immediately thereafter, he spotted a streak of black light out of the corner of his eye, and the runes on the blade of the black saber had begun flashing as it slashed at him from below at an extremely awkward angle.

It was too late for him to dodge the attack, so he could only take it head-on, and a layer of golden scales immediately appeared over his skin, alongside his True Extreme Membrane .

A loud clang rang out as Han Li retreated several thousand feet through the air, leaving a trail of blood in his wake.

After steadying himself, a grim look appeared on his face. The unremarkable-looking slash unleashed by the black-robed young man had managed to slice through both his True Extreme Membrane and his golden scales.

The slash had run out of steam after that and wasn't able to inflict any substantial harm, but Han Li was still quite alarmed by its power.

However, the black-robed young man's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, indicating that he was dissatisfied with the outcome of that attack.

As for the brocade-robed elderly man, he didn't participate directly in the battle. Instead, he was holding a round array plate in one hand while tracing the index finger of his other hand through the air incessantly, as if he were inscribing something.

Furthermore, a series of triangular yellow flags were flying incessantly out of his sleeve before vanishing into thin air.

Han Li's gaze roamed over his two assailants for a moment before a white longsword appeared in his grasp amid a flash of white light.

The black-robed young man took a step forward, immediately traveling close to 1,000 feet through the air, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake as he lashed out at Han Li with his saber again.

Han Li raised an arm to block the attack, managing to keep the saber at bay, yet before he had a chance to do anything else, a startling turn of events abruptly unfolded before his eyes.

The afterimages left behind by Fang Pan were still lingering in the air, and one of them suddenly sprang forth amid a flash of black light, wielding an identical black saber that it lashed out at Han Li's abdomen.

This second figure was identical in appearance to Fang Pan, and it was also giving off a mid-True Immortal Stage aura!

Chapter 166: The Laws of Speed

Is this an avatar? No, it's something else...

Despite his surprise, Han Li's reactions remained as sharp as ever.

Seven specks of white light instantly appeared on his chest and abdomen, and one of his arms abruptly swelled drastically in size as he swung his fist at the second figure.

A resounding boom rang out as the second figure was sent flying back by the tremendous force behind the punch, but right at this moment, Han Li suddenly felt a chill run down his spine, and he had only just managed to turn his head slightly before he struck by a sharp blade on the shoulder near his neck.

Several of the scales on his shoulder were broken, and blood splattered in all directions as he was sent plunging forward through the air by the force of the attack.

He had only just managed to steady himself slightly when he caught sight of a third black-robed young man behind him, and this one was also completely identical to the other two in both aura and appearance.

Han Li hurriedly used his momentum to tumble through the air, then steadied himself over 1,000 feet away as he activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

At the same time, the set of nine white flying swords also flew out before revolving through the air around him, forming a dense net of sword threads that protected him from all directions.

A hint of mockery appeared on the faces of the three black-robed young men in unison upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, the three of them pounced at Han Li from three different directions, and the runes on the surface of their black sabers were flashing brightly, causing the surrounding space to twist and warp.

Bright blue light was glowing in Han Li's eyes as he scrutinized the three figures intently, assessing all of the visual information that he could gather, including their movement trajectories, their actions, and even the looks on their faces.

In doing so, he discovered that all three of them seemed to have been real.

This is a clone technique that he's unleashing through the use of the laws of speed!

An enlightened look appeared on his face as he arrived at this realization, but his brows only became even more tightly furrowed with this revelation.

A sharp clang rang out, and one of the flying swords was struck, causing it to draw to a shuddering halt.

As a result, a gap appeared in the sword net, and before it could be filled, a saber projection shot through, hurtling directly toward Han Li's chest from behind.

Han Li swung around violently before launching a fist through the air to strike the saber projection head-on.

Immediately thereafter, a string of erratic clanging rang out, and he spotted a black-robed man wielding a long saber flashing incessantly around him, picking apart the defenses of his sword net bit by bit.

Thanks to his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, Han Li was able to track his opponent's movement with his eyes, but his flying swords were always just a little too slow to react, and it didn't take long before the sword was cast into complete disarray.

Furthermore, the other two clones of the black-robed young man were constantly lurking, lashing out at Han Li's vital regions whenever the opportunity arose.

Before long, around a dozen deep gashes had already been sliced into Han Li's body.

Thankfully, his physical body was extremely hardy to begin with, and his physical constitution was bolstered even further thanks to his True Extreme Physique, so even though he was frequently struck, none of the attacks proved to be lethal.

However, he knew that the situation was about to take a turn for the worse soon as the brocade-robed elderly man had already reached the final stage in setting up his array.

A faint buzzing sound rang out as the space within a radius of several thousand feet around Han Li shuddered. A burst of earthy yellow light swept through the area, and the astral wind storm was halted in its tracks, as if it had been sealed by some type of invisible force.

Han Li immediately made a hand seal without any hesitation upon seeing this, and a burst of thunderous rumbling instantly rang out as countless arcs of silver lightning sprang out of his body, instantly forming a silver lightning array around him.

An urgent look appeared on the brocade-robed elderly man's face upon seeing this, and he immediately pointed a finger at the array plate in his hand, upon which dazzling yellow light erupted within the array, sending a burst of even more overwhelming pressure surging toward Han Li.

As a result, the activation of Han Li's lightning array was also slowed down.

Fang Pan certainly wasn't going to pass up such an opportunity, and cold killing intent flashed through the eyes of his three clones as they converged from three different directions, unleashing a string of powerful saber projections that closed in rapidly on Han Li.

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly as he activated his Lightning Bird bloodline to its limits, and a flash of blinding silver light appeared in the air, following which Han Li abruptly vanished along with the lightning array.

Almost at the exact same moment, a vast expanse of earthy yellow light surged forth from all directions in a frenzy.

The flurry of saber projections also arrived, completely shredding the area around the spot where Han Li had just been standing a moment before, forming a violent black tornado that instantly destroyed all of the silver light lingering in the air.

Immediately thereafter, the three Fang Pans in the air fused back into one, glowering at the spot that Han Li had just vanished from with a dark expression.

The brocade-robed elderly man also deactivated his array before arriving by Fang Pan's side, then gently sniffed the air as he remarked, "I can smell quite a bit of his blood lingering in the air. In order to prevent us from spoiling the activation of his lightning array, he took an attack from you and your clones head-on, so I'm sure he's carrying some severe injuries right now."

After a moment of contemplation, Fang Pan said, "Not only did he not die 300 years ago, he's attained the body of a Profound Immortal now, so I doubt that attack would've inflicted any meaningful damage. Brother Feng, I'll have to trouble you to track him again. We can't afford to let him get away."

The brocade-robed elderly man nodded in response, then began to initiate his tracking technique...

Meanwhile, a rumbling thunderclap suddenly rang out in the air above a sand dune several hundred thousand kilometers away.

A bolt of silver lightning that was as thick as a water tank came crashing down from the heavens, and Han Li stumbled out of the bolt of lightning in a disheveled manner before falling onto the ground.

As soon as he landed on the ground, he immediately released his spiritual sense to scour the entire area within a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers, and only after verifying that there was no danger nearby did he flip a hand over to produce a pair of pills that he promptly swallowed.

He then closed his eyes to meditate, and moments later, his aura gradually returned to a tranquil state, but his expression was still as dark as ever.

He still had no idea who his two assailants were, but given how intent they were on killing him, he had a rough idea of who they could be.

The first possibility was that they were hunting him for the reward offered by the Ubiquitous Pavilion, while the second possibility was that they had something to do with how he had lost his memories of the past 300 years.

What was most perplexing to him was how they had seen through the disguise that he had adopted using the mask of the Transient Guild.

Regardless of what their objectives were, this wasn't something that he could verify in the current situation. Not only were they both superior to him in terms of cultivation base, their abilities made them extremely difficult to deal with.

One of them had mastered the laws of speed, while the other seemed to be a master of arrays and restrictions, so it definitely wasn't wise for him to fight fire with fire.

As these thoughts were running through his mind, he rose his feet, then flipped a hand over to produce the jade slip that contained the map of the Primordial Wave Continent.

After taking a brief glance at the map, he stowed the jade slip away, then began to fly toward a certain direction as a streak of azure light, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Half a day later, Han Li was flying through the air above a short mountain range, and he descended toward a forest down below with a grim look on his face.

After landing on the ground, he immediately sat down with his legs crossed, and he took a pill to recover his energy, then released his spiritual sense as he closed his eyes to meditate.

However, no more than 15 minutes later, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and a bewildered look appeared on his face.

"How did they manage to catch up to me so quickly?" he murmured to himself as he immediately rose to his feet.

Two powerful auras had suddenly appeared at the edge of his spiritual sensory range, and they were approaching him at an incredible speed.

Han Li immediately shot up into the sky as a streak of azure light once again, vanishing from the forest in a flash.

……

Two days later.

A streak of indistinct azure light suddenly appeared in the sky above a vast, primitive forest, and a tall figure emerged from within, then plummeted toward the lush forest down below in an unsteady manner.

A resounding boom rang out as a massive tree was struck by the figure, causing it to explode violently, sending countless branches, leaves, and scraps of wood flying in all directions.

Countless birds and beasts in the forest immediately began to flee the area in a panicked frenzy, further contributing to the commotion.

The figure that had struck the giant tree was none other than Han Li, and he sat up from the remnants of the tree, then wiped the forest dew from his face with his hand.

He had adopted another disguise, giving him the appearance of a square-faced middle-aged man.

His eyes held a sharp gleam, but the weariness on his face was very apparent.

During the past two days of constant fleeing, he had exhausted almost all of his immortal spiritual power, yet he was still unable to shake Fang Pan and the brocade-robed elderly man off his trail, and they seemed to be determined to kill him.

I can't just keep running like this. At the very least, I have to figure out who they are, Han Li thought to himself as he quickly devoured several pills.

With that in mind, he closed his eyes to meditate, recovering his immortal spiritual power as quickly as he could.

Around 15 minutes later, he reopened his eyes, detecting a burst of powerful spiritual sense within the range of his spiritual sense once again.

However, this time, he didn't continue to flee. Instead, he slowly rose to his feet, then flew up into the air above the forest as he cast his gaze toward the horizon.

A streak of azure light was hurtling rapidly toward him from that direction, and after just several seconds, it was no more than 10,000 feet away from him.

Within the streak of azure light was Fang Pan, who was holding his long black saber with a cold look in his eyes, while the brocade-robed elderly man was nowhere to be seen.

Judging from the cold killing intent in Fang Pan's eyes, Han Li could already tell that his disguise had failed, and he asked, "Why are you so determined to hunt me down?"

Fang Pan faltered slightly upon hearing this, but he had no intention of answering Han Li's question. Instead, he conjured up a series of indistinct afterimages in the air as he prepared to pounce.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately activated the true spirit bloodlines in his body.

Chapter 167: The Nascent Soul Sealing Vendetta

A low roar rang out as a burst of dazzling golden light erupted out of Han Li's entire body.

Enshrouded within the golden light, his body was rapidly expanding while strands of golden fur sprouted out of his skin, and he transformed into a giant golden ape that was several dozen feet tall in the blink of an eye.

At the same time, Fang Pan had already split up into three identical clones that were closing in around the giant ape in a triangular formation. The long sabers in their hands were gleaming with black light, forming a dense black saber net in the air that surrounded Han Li from all directions.

The golden ape threw its head back and let loose a long roar as it swung its arms violently through the air, releasing a burst of tremendous force that caused the surrounding space to tremble and quiver.

In the face of this burst of immense force, the black saber net was quickly destroyed, and even the air around the golden ape had become extremely heavy.

The three clones formed by Fang Pan swayed slightly, then withdrew their sabers in unison as they abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, azure light flashed behind the giant ape, and three saber-wielding Fang Pans appeared at the same time before slashing their sabers viciously at Han Li.

In the instant that the three sabers began their descent, they abruptly fused into a single saber projection with black light swirling around it, producing a sharp screeching sound as they sliced through the air, causing the nearby space to become blurry and indistinct.

The attack was so fast that the giant ape had no time to take evasive measures, but it was still able to conjure up a True Extreme Membrane over its body.

A loud metallic clang rang out as the black saber projection struck the golden ape on the back with devastating force, and the saber projection was instantly shattered as a burst of black and golden light erupted forth, sending a powerful destructive aura erupting in all directions that caused the air to buzz and tremble.

The golden ape was instantly sent flying forward, and its True Extreme Membrane had been torn open, while a gash had appeared on its back.

The gash wasn't very deep, but it was still bleeding profusely, staining its golden fur red.

Fang Pan was also involuntarily sent flying back over 1,000 feet from the force of the impact before stabilizing himself in mid-air.

He took a glance at the giant ape, which had landed on the ground not far away, and a slightly grim look had appeared on his face. It was clear that he wasn't expecting the golden ape to be able to take that attack head-on with such minimal injuries.

Just like Fang Pan, Han Li was also feeling rather bewildered.

Thankfully, he had taken on his Giant Mountain Ape in time. Otherwise, that attack would've dealt far more severe damage. At the same time, it seemed that he had found a way to deal with Fang Pan's attacks, despite Fang Pan's speed advantage.

After a moment of contemplation, Fang Pan split up into three once again before pouncing at Han Li.

This time, the three figures blurred as they sped through the air before splitting up even further, conjuring up dozens of clones, both substantial and insubstantial, in the blink of an eye. At the same time, thousands of black saber projections were sent raining down upon the giant ape.

The golden ape paid no heed to the injury on its back as it swung its massive fists rapidly through the air, unleashing countless fist projections in all directions.

A burst of tremendous power erupted forth, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently, forming rings of powerful shockwaves that swept through the air in all directions.

The dozens of clones conjured up by Fang Pan were struck by the ferocious shockwaves, and most of them instantly disintegrated, leaving only three substantial clones behind, all three of which had survived thanks to the protective light barriers around their bodies.

Before the giant ape had a chance to do anything else, a peculiar grin suddenly appeared on the faces of the three Fang Pans in unison, following which all three of them abruptly vanished from the spot.

The golden ape faltered slightly upon seeing this, seemingly having recalled something.

All of a sudden, a burst of bright yellow light erupted out of the ground beneath its feet, and a series of rope-like bursts of yellow light surged up from the earth. The bursts of yellow light twisted and writhed like spirit snakes for a brief moment, then wound themselves around the giant ape's entire body while giving off powerful law fluctuations.

Immediately thereafter, a giant yellow umbrella appeared out of thin air. The umbrella was over 1,000 feet in size, and all of the bursts of rope-like yellow light were connected to the interior of the umbrella. At this point, the golden ape had already been wrapped up in a yellow cocoon, making it resemble the umbrella's shaft.

The golden ape was greatly alarmed by this, and it let loose a thunderous roar as the muscles on its body writhed and squirmed frantically as if they were living creatures. Dazzling golden light was radiating from its entire body as it struggled with all its might.

However, these ordinary-looking bursts of yellow light were extraordinarily sturdy, and Han Li was unable to break free even with the incredible strength of the Giant Mountain Ape.

All of a sudden, the huge yellow umbrella closed itself around the giant ape, trapping it within.

Immediately thereafter, spatial fluctuations erupted above the umbrella, and the brocade-robed elderly man appeared as he chortled, "I've finally got you now! Even if you have three heads and six arms, you won't be able to break free from my Earth Net Umbrella!"

"Well done, Brother Feng!"

Fang Pan appeared beside the giant umbrella in a flash, then raised a hand as he began to chant an incantation.

An inky-black chain appeared out of thin air, and it was gleaming with black light with faint black mist swirling around it.

Furthermore, it was giving off a special type of law fluctuations.

The golden ape within the giant umbrella was extremely alarmed as he sensed the aura emanating from the chain. This was an aura that he was extremely familiar with, the aura of the Origin Separation Law Chains that had bound his nascent soul for over 300 years!

"You were the one who sealed my nascent soul!" the giant ape roared within the umbrella.

"Looks like you finally remembered! The three of us had to go great lengths to take you down, and we thought that our secret had perished with you, but to my surprise, you were still alive," the brocade-robed elderly man above the giant umbrella said.

Bright golden light erupted from the golden ape's body once again as it struggled and thrashed violently within the giant umbrella.

"Cease your futile struggles!" the brocade-robed elderly man said with a cold smile as he thrust a palm downward.

A burst of dazzling yellow light instantly erupted out of the surface of the giant umbrella, and a flurry of yellow runes surged forth in a frenzy before revolving around the umbrella, causing it to tighten even further.

At the same time, Fang Pan had completed his incantation, and he was rapidly making a series of hand seals.

The black light glowing from the black chain quickly brightened as countless black runes appeared around the chain, and those runes were rapidly expanding in size while giving off faint spatial fluctuations.

Right as Fang Pan was about to complete his preparations, a resounding boom rang out within the yellow umbrella, following which an incredible scene unfolded.

Lights of all types of different colors suddenly erupted out of the bulging yellow umbrella, and yellow light surged over the umbrella's surface as it bulged even further.

A bewildered look appeared on the brocade-robed elderly man's eyes upon seeing this, yet before he had a chance to do anything, he suddenly threw up a mouthful of blood, and his complexion instantly paled.

In the next instant, a resounding boom rang out as the yellow umbrella was violently torn apart.

The spiritual light on the surface of the umbrella quickly faded, while a golden figure emerged from within before rapidly expanding to over 1,000 feet in size while rising up into the air.

It was a giant golden ape with three heads and six arms, and the bursts of yellow light that were previously wound around its body were already nowhere to be seen.

The giant ape quickly made a string of hand seals with all six of its hands, and countless arcs of dazzling silver lightning emerged to form a huge lightning array around it.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Fang Pan was furious as he opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence into the black chain before him.

"You're not getting away!"

The black light radiating from the chain brightened even further as it abruptly swelled to several times its original size, then vanished from the spot before appearing directly in front of the giant ape, then passed straight through its chest and abdomen.

Almost at the exact same moment, dazzling silver light erupted within the lightning array, and the giant ape abruptly vanished, causing the chain to strike nothing but empty air.

Fang Pan was glowing at the slowly fading remnants of silver light in the air, and he was gritting his teeth in fury.

He took a deep breath to compose himself, then made a beckoning motion to withdraw the black chain.

The brocade-robed elderly man also flew over to him with a dark expression as he said, "I didn't think that he would be able to forcibly break free from the Earth Net Umbrella's law powers."

Fang Pan stowed the black chain away, then said, "That's only a secondary concern. The main problem we have to deal with is that lightning array of his. If we can't find a way to counteract it, he'll just keep running away, and we'll never be able to hunt him down! Brother Feng, you're an expert in arrays and restrictions, do you have any way to stop him?"

"Having already observed his lightning array twice, I have a rough idea of how it works. It's something that combines the power of space and the power of lightning, and it's actually not so difficult to counter it, but special talismans must be prepared, and I don't have any such talismans on me right now," the brocade-robed elderly man replied with slightly furrowed brows.

"Is there no other way? If we can crack the secret that he's holding, we should be able to break through our bottlenecks with no problems at all," Fang Pan said in a meaningful voice.

"There are other ways to counteract his lightning array. I once learned a secret technique called the Blood Incinerating Breath, which requires one to burn through their blood essence to unleash. It's a secret that can sever the spiritual power flow of all arrays, and it should be able to stop his lightning array from taking effect," the brocade-robed elderly man replied.

Fang Pan's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he said, "Perfect! Once we catch up to him next, use that secret technique to prevent him from getting away."

"The problem is that using the secret technique is quite taxing on the body, and I most likely won't be able to help you deal with Han Li," the brocade-robed elderly man said in a slightly hesitant voice.

"Rest assured, all you need to do is prevent him from getting away, and I'll take care of the rest," Fang Pan chuckled.

He raised a hand as he spoke to release a burst of azure light that enveloped both himself and the brocade-robed elderly man, then sped into the distance at an incredible speed, vanishing into the distance in a flash.

…………

Chapter 168: Pursuit

High up in the sky above a snowy mountain range hundreds of thousands of kilometers away, countless arcs of lightning appeared out of thin air before intertwining to form an array.

A giant figure appeared within the array amid a flash of silver light, and it was a huge golden ape with three heads and six arms.

As soon as the giant ape appeared, it rapidly shrank down, reverting back to its human form while the silver lightning array disintegrated around it.

He flipped a hand over to produce a pill before swallowing it, then flew toward a certain direction at full speed as a streak of azure light without pause.

This type of long-distance teleportation was extremely taxing on the Lightning Bird's power of lightning, and at the moment, he didn't know whether there was a distance limit on how far away Fang Pan and the brocade-robed elderly man could sense him from. If he were to be caught with all of the power of lightning in his body completely exhausted, then he would have no course for retreat.

However, he wasn't able to fly very far before he felt his blood begin to churn within his veins, and it was clear that Fang Pan's duo was using the same tracking technique once again.

Hence, he immediately began to fly in a different direction without any hesitation.

At the same time, he was digesting the pill that he had just taken as quickly as he could while carefully inspecting every single inch of his own body with his spiritual sense, trying to find out exactly where a mark had been planted on him.

However, no matter how much he searched, he wasn't able to find anything.

Even though Han Li was fleeing as quickly as he could, Fang Pan was too fast for him to shake off, and close to a day later, they were gradually beginning to close in on him.

This time, Han Li had no intention of facing them in battle at all, and in the instant that they appeared in his field of view, silver light instantly began to erupt out of his body.

Countless arcs of silver lightning appeared one after the other, yet right as it was about to form a lightning array, Fang Pan's voice rang out like thunder from several hundred kilometers away. "You're not getting away!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, bright azure light that contained countless dancing azure began to glow over his palm, and he thrust his palm into the body of the brocade-robed elderly man beside him.

An azure halo instantly appeared around the brocade-robed elderly man, within which countless azure runes were surging incessantly.

The elderly man instantly vanished into thin air, then reappeared not far away from Han Li.

At this point, Han Li was no more than half a second away from completing his teleportation. A silver lightning array had already taken shape around him, and he was just about to be inundated by silver light when a vast expanse of crimson flames suddenly appeared on the brocade-robed elderly man's body, instantly transforming him into a crimson sun.

Blinding crimson light spread through the entire area within a radius of several kilometers, and as soon as the lightning array around Han Li came into contact with the crimson light, it immediately disintegrated, much to Han Li's alarm.

Right at this moment, a bright saber projection appeared in Han Li's field of view, and initially, it was extremely far away, but it was upon him in the blink of an eye like a bolt of lightning, piercing directly toward his heart at an incredible speed.

Han Li's pupils contracted drastically upon seeing this, and bright azure light began to glow from his body as he sped toward the side.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared several hundred feet away from his original spot. A huge gash had been sliced onto his arm, exposing the bone within, and blood was gushing out profusely.

However, he had no time to tend to the wound as he instantly adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form amid a flash of dazzling golden light. At the same time, countless golden scales appeared over his entire body.

Meanwhile, Fang Pan appeared behind the saber, then reached out to grab it.

Immediately thereafter, he began darting from side to side, and four identical Fang Pans appeared on either side of him.

Each of them was wielding a bright long saber as they charged directly at Han Li at lightning-fast speeds while unleashing five dazzling saber projections.

All of a sudden, the five Fang Pans overlapped with one another, and the five saber projections also combined into one. At the same time, it abruptly accelerated to several times its original speed, leaving layers of overlapping afterimages in its wake as it pierced directly toward the giant ape's heart.

Everything around the saber projection seemed to have become extremely slow, as if everything were moving in slow motion in comparison.

The dream-like saber projection pierced into the golden ape's body before emerging on the other side, but it had missed the giant ape's heart by a small margin.

The golden ape threw up a mouthful of blood as a stunned look appeared on its face, and it then slammed a palm heavily down onto its own chest.

The giant ape was sent flying back by the force of its own blow, throwing up another large mouthful of blood that transformed into a burst of crimson light before fusing into its body.

Its skin instantly turned as red as blood, and at the same time, a massive crimson rune appeared on both his chest and his back, radiating dazzling crimson light.

The giant ape's body instantly exploded into a ball of crimson light, which instantly shot out of the area encompassed within the crimson light released by the brocade-robed elderly man.

Countless arcs of silver lightning then sprang out of the ball of crimson light, forming a lightning array in the blink of an eye.

Following a flash of lightning, Han Li was once again nowhere to be seen, leaving the brocade-robed elderly man to look on with his mouth agape in astonishment.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and before either of them had a chance to react, Han Li had already vanished from the spot.

The five Fang Pans fused as one once again, and he was glowering at the spot where Han Li had just vanished from with a furious expression.

Meanwhile, the brocade-robed elderly man chanted an incantation to snuff out the crimson flames burning on his body. His complexion was quite pale, and he hurriedly summoned a pill before devouring it.

"Damn it! He got away again!" Fang Pan spat through gritted teeth with a hint of agitation on his face.

Now that Han Li was aware of the elderly man's secret technique, he was definitely going to be even more cautious from this point onward, and it was most likely not going to be feasible to use the same secret technique on him again.

"I didn't think that he would be so cunning. What do we do now?" the brocade-robed elderly man asked, and his complexion still hadn't returned to normal.

Fang Pan was silent for a moment, then said, "Let's catch up to him first."

He then swept a hand through the air to release a burst of azure light that enveloped both of them.

Meanwhile, hundreds of kilometers away, a lightning array emerged before quickly disintegrating.

The crimson light faded, and Han Li stumbled out from within, looking as pale as a sheet.

There was still a wound on his chest near his heart that was bleeding profusely, and a hint of lingering fear flashed through his eyes as he looked down to inspect the wound.

If he hadn't moved himself to the side at the last moment, his heart would've already been pierced through and completely destroyed.

His eyes narrowed slightly as he thought back to that dream-like strike.

It was clear that Fang Pan had been hiding his true power prior to that point, and even Han Li had almost fallen prey to the surprise attack.

The only silver lining on the situation was that it clearly required some time for Fang Pan to unleash those nascent soul sealing chains of his.

With that in mind, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a green talisman, which he pressed against the wound on his chest.

The talisman released a burst of gentle green light that surged into the wound, and his bleeding immediately stopped, while the wound itself also quickly healed.

He then consumed an Origin Return Pill, and while digesting the pill, he flew toward a certain direction as a streak of azure light.

Unsurprisingly, it took only less than a day before Fang Pan's duo caught up to him again.

Thanks to the effects of the Origin Return Pill, Han Li had already mostly recovered from his injuries.

Having learned his lesson from last time, he immediately teleported himself away using his lightning array as soon as Fang Pan and the brocade-robed elderly man entered his spiritual sensory range.

Fang Pan was naturally both infuriated and frustrated by this.

If he couldn't even get close to Han Li, then there was no way for him to do anything.

However, at this point, there was naturally no way that he would just give up and let Han Li go.

……

Several days later, a streak of azure light was flying rapidly through the air above a black forest.

There was a thick blanket of dark clouds in the sky above the forest, and huge bolts of lightning would come crashing down from the clouds occasionally, giving the area the appearance of a forest of lightning when viewed from afar.

Within the azure light, Han Li wore a grim expression as he sped through the air while dodging the lightning that was crashing down from above.

Meanwhile, Fang Pan and the brocade-robed elderly man had just arrived at the edge of the forest close to 100,000 kilometers away. The two of them took a slightly concerned glance at the forest of lightning up ahead, but seeing no other choice, the two of them immediately flew in to continue their pursuit of Han Li.

……

Half a month later, a streak of azure light was flying like the wind over a crimson mountain range.

The entire mountain range down below was covered in scorching flames, releasing plumes of black smoke that obscured the entire sky.

The streak of azure light was traversing through the world of fire and smoke in a straight line without taking any evasive measures.

Hundreds of thousands of kilometers away, Fang Pan and the brocade-robed elderly man were flying along in hot pursuit with dark looks on their faces.

……

As the chase continued, over a month passed by in the blink of an eye.

Right at this moment, countless arcs of silver lightning appeared to form a lightning array in the sky above a massive swamp.

A loud thunderclap rang out, and Han Li appeared at the center of the array with his brows tightly furrowed.

He had been fleeing non-stop for close to two months at this point, and despite his large stash of pills, he was still rapidly exhausting the power of the Lightning Bird in his body. Even though he was intentionally limiting the number of times he was using his lightning array, it was still less than half as effective as it had been at its peak.

As a result, the distance that he was able to teleport with the array was decreasing with each successive use, and this time, he was only able to teleport no more than 250,000 kilometers.

Fang Pan and the brocade-robed elderly man had clearly detected this as well, and they were speeding up in their pursuit, much to Han Li's dismay.

If things were to continue like this, he would eventually be worn down and killed by his two pursuers.

Through the observation that he had conducted during this period, he had discovered that the one who had been tracking him this entire time wasn't Fang Pan. Instead, the tracking technique was being used by that brocade-robed elderly man.

Not only was that man able to track him, he was able to counteract his lightning array and possessed an Acquired Immortal Treasure capable of trapping someone inside. Hence, he was a huge thorn in Han Li's side that had to be eliminated.

With that in mind, he quickly hatched a plan, then began flying in another direction.

Moments later, the sound of splashing waves rang out up ahead, and a massive sea appeared before him. The seawater had a faint red hue, and it was giving off a sharp rusty smell.

He looked down at the churning seawater for a moment with a contemplative expression, then continued to fly deeper into the sea. Moments later, he drew to a halt near a crimson island that was several dozen kilometers in size.

"This place will have to do," he murmured to himself, then took a deep breath before raising both hands up into the air.

Dozens of balls of blue spiritual light flew out in all directions in unison, then vanished into the seawater down below.

Chapter 169: Retaliation

The balls of blue spiritual light that Han Li had just released were dozens of array treasures, each of which was several inches in size.

In the next instant, balls of blue light rose up from the surrounding sea, forming a series of profound arrays of different sizes, all of which began to revolve on the spot.

Meanwhile, Han Li flicked his fingers through the air, and a series of near-transparent azure threads shot out of his fingertips before vanishing into the surrounding arrays, causing them to fuse with one another before vanishing once again.

Close to an hour later, all of the surrounding arrays had vanished, following which Han Li made a hand seal, and countless arcs of silver lightning erupted out of his body to form a lightning array beneath him.

Han Li vanished from the spot amid a flash of lightning, then reappeared around 150,000 kilometers away, but he was still situated in the same crimson sea.

Meanwhile, countless kilometers away, Fang Pan and the brocade-robed elderly man were enshrouded within a streak of azure light as they sped through the air like lightning.

The brocade-robed elderly man was holding a golden array plate with one hand while chanting an incantation.

Once every few moments, he would unleash the tracking technique again in order to receive the latest updates on Han Li's location.

"He just teleported again," the brocade-robed elderly man reported.

"In which direction?" Fang Pan asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Northeast, but this time, he was only able to teleport less than 150,000 kilometers," the brocade-robed elderly man replied.

"Great! It looks like he won't be able to last much longer." Fang Pan was ecstatic to hear this, and he immediately began flying in the northeastern direction.

This time, they spotted Han Li in the distance no more than four hours later.

Han Li's face was extremely pale as he took a panicked glance behind him, and he conjured up his lightning array once again, but this time, he was only able to teleport himself less than 100,000 kilometers away.

Fang Pan was even more encouraged to see this, and he took a pill to recover his immortal spiritual power before speeding up even further.

Close to three hours later, Fang Pan caught up to Han Li once again.

Han Li frantically accelerated to his top speed, but he was still quite a bit slower than Fang Pan. The distance between the two of them was rapidly shrinking, and soon, they were separated by only a few hundred kilometers.

With a wave of his sleeve, arcs of silver lightning appeared over Han Li's body once again.

Fang Pan's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this. He knew that at this rate, he would be able to hunt down Han Li eventually, but he had already been pursuing Han Li for close to two months, and he had run out of patience long ago, so he wanted to end this as quickly as possible.

"Hurry, Brother Feng!" Fang Pan yelled as countless glowing azure runes arose from his hand, following which he thrust his palm into the brocade-robed elderly man's body.

An azure halo appeared around him once again, and in the next instant, the elderly man reappeared in very close proximity to Han Li.

A vast expanse of crimson flames had already appeared over his body, releasing dazzling crimson light that instantly encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of close to 10 kilometers.

At this point, Han Li still hadn't conjured up his lightning array yet, so there was no way that he could get away.

Fang Pan's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he made a grabbing motion to summon a bright saber into his grasp. At the same time, countless azure runes appeared around him, and his speed increased once again by roughly twofold.

Right at this moment, a burst of silver lightning erupted out of Han Li's body, and he transformed into a silver Lightning Bird that was several hundred feet in size, with thick bolts of lightning crackling and revolving incessantly around it.

The Lightning Bird spread its wings, and it vanished on the spot amid a flash of silver lightning before reappearing hundreds of kilometers away.

"Your struggles are futile!" Fang Pan harrumphed coldly as he appeared beside the brocade-robed elderly man, then grabbed onto his shoulder with one hand.

A burst of azure light appeared around him to envelop both of them, then transformed into a blurry azure shadow that set off in pursuit of the Lightning Bird, appearing directly behind it in the blink of an eye.

The Lightning Bird flapped its wings, and it fled another several hundred kilometers amid a flash of silver lightning, yet Fang Pan's duo were just as fast and remained hot on its heels.

Silver lightning flashed incessantly from the Lightning Bird's body as it unleashed its lightning movement ability over and over again, and each time, it was just a little bit faster than Fang Pan's duo, allowing to escape capture.

Thus, the chase continued, with a bolt of silver lightning and an azure shadow traveling rapidly over the surface of the sea.

The azure shadow remained as bright as ever, yet the arcs of silver lightning around the Lightning Bird were becoming dimmer and dimmer.

With another flash of silver lightning, the Lightning Bird appeared near a crimson island.

At this point, the arcs of silver lightning around it had become extremely dim, and it was flying directly forward, seemingly no longer able to unleash its lightning movement technique.

Even so, it was still extremely fast, but far slower than the speed its lightning movement technique had allowed it to reach.

The gap between the azure shadow and the Lightning Bird was rapidly shrinking, and Fang Pan's duo was ecstatic to see this.

However, the brocade-robed elderly man's brows suddenly furrowed slightly as he called out, "Hold on..."

However, Fang Pan's attention was completely fixed on the Lightning Bird up ahead, and he sped up once again, closing the gap between himself and the Lightning Bird to less than 1,000 feet.

Layers upon layers of saber projections were released by the saber in his hand, and he was just about to lash out when his surroundings suddenly turned into a complete blur.

The Lightning Bird up ahead had vanished, and he found himself situated in a blue space.

As soon as he entered this blue space, he immediately felt a burst of vortex-like suction force surging forth from beneath him. The suction force wasn't very powerful, but it was constantly acting upon him, forcing him to decelerate.

A string of afterimages appeared in his wake as he abruptly shot forward, trying to break out of the blue space, but a dull thump suddenly rang out as a burst of strange ripples suddenly appeared in the space up ahead, and a watery blue barrier appeared to stop him cold in his tracks.

Fang Pan immediately lashed out with the black saber in his hand, releasing a massive black saber projection that struck the barrier up ahead with a resounding boom, leaving a long crack on its surface.

A cold sneer appeared on Fang Pan's face upon seeing this, and he raised his saber to strike the barrier once again, only for the barrier to instantly return to its original state amid a flash of blue light.

The brocade-robed elderly man arrived by his side, and his brows were slightly furrowed as he said, "This is a high-grade water-attribute array that can draw upon the vast power of water of the sea to constantly replenish itself. It's renowned for being difficult to break through, and brute force along won't be enough to break it."

"He's become even more troublesome to deal with than 300 years ago," Fang Pan spat through gritted teeth.

"Having said that, it seems like he's close to exhausting all of his power of lightning, and he set up this array as a last resort to try and slow us down. Once we break through this array, it won't take us long to hunt him down," the brocade-robed elderly man said.

"I'll be counting on you, Brother Qian," Fang Pan replied with a nod.

With that, the brocade-robed elderly man rose up into the air, hovering directly above the center of the blue space as he began to make a series of hand seals while chanting an incantation.

A burst of red light flashed around him, and crimson flames were ignited over his body.

However, right at this moment, silver lightning suddenly began to crackle above his head, and Han Li swooped in from outside the array.

While it was true that he had expended a huge amount of his power of lightning, he hadn't completely run out, and he had only made it appear as if that were the case in order to lure Fang Pan's duo into his trap.

He made a hand seal with one hand, then thrust it down downward, and the True Water Pouch in his other hand instantly began to bulge. A burst of black light erupted out of the opening of the pouch, and boundless heavy water came gushing out like a turbulent river through a broken dam, transforming into an inky-black heavy water wyrm that pounced directly toward the brocade-robed elderly man.

The heavy water wyrm was as heavy as a mountain, and the entire space beneath it began to tremble violently under its enormous weight.

At this moment, the elderly man resembled a crimson sun, and he was at a critical juncture in his Blood Incinerating Breath secret technique. If he were to be cut off here, then not only would all of his prior efforts go to waste, he would be severely injured by secret technique backlash.

He hurriedly summoned an antiquated dark azure suit of armor onto his body, and at the same time, he yelled to Fang Pan, "Help me, Brother Fang!"

Even before the cry for help, Fang Pan had already sprung into action, conjuring up a series of clones, one of which slashed its black saber viciously through the air.

Meanwhile, two other clones rose up into the air, leaving trails of afterimages in their wake as they sped directly toward Han Li.

Han Li completely ignored Fang Pan's attacks as he quickly made a hand seal, and the heavy water wyrm accelerated in its descent toward the brocade-robed elderly man at his behest.

In contrast with refining Heavy Water Veined Lightning, which required meticulous and precise control over heavy water, wielding such a massive volume of heavy water like this was more of a test of one's immortal spiritual power reserves and powers of concentration.

The heavy water wyrm came crashing down from above, and the first thing that it struck was Fang Pan's black saber, but it immediately swallowed up the saber with a dull thump.

In the next instant, the wyrm crashed directly into the crimson sun that was burning around the brocade-robed elderly man.

A thunderous boom rang out as the elderly man's body came plummeting directly downward as if a mountain had fallen onto his head, and all of the crimson light around him instantly disintegrated. The suit of armor that he had donned was releasing countless dark azure runes, all of which were hurtling up toward the heavy water wyrm.

A string of dull thumps rang out in rapid succession as the heavy water wyrm's body was completely scattered by the dark azure runes.

However, not only was Han Li not dismayed in the slightest to see this, a triumphant smile had appeared on his face. Lightning flashed around him as he just barely evaded the attacks from the oncoming Fang Pan clones, then rapidly shot back in retreat.

A hint of foreboding immediately welled up in Fang Pan's heart upon seeing this, and all three of his clones fled toward the outskirts of the blue space as quickly as they could.

Meanwhile, 20 or so fist-sized black balls had emerged without any warning from in the wake of the destruction of the heavy water wyrm's body. The balls were hovering in mid-air, not giving off any spiritual power fluctuations.

As for the vast expanse of heavy water that the wyrm had disintegrated into, it rose up toward Han Li in a black wave before vanishing into his body.

Right at this moment, the silver patterns on the black balls suddenly began to light up, and thin arcs of lightning appeared within them.

Chapter 170: Demise

The brocade-robed elderly man's heart jolted slightly at the sight of the flashing balls around him, and he was overcome by an intense sense of foreboding.

He hurriedly swept his sleeves through the air, releasing seven or eight protective treasures at once as he braced himself for what was to come.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, immediately followed by a string of thunderous explosions as the 20 or so balls of Heavy Water Veined Lightning exploded like fireworks one after another.

Arcs of silver lightning erupted violently in all directions, instantly encompassing the entire surrounding area within a radius of 10,000 feet.

The runes being released by the brocade-robed elderly man's suit of armor were instantly destroyed as soon as they appeared, and all of his other protective treasures were also swallowed up by an enormous black sun.

A burst of powerful shockwaves swept through the area in all directions, causing the surrounding space to fold in on itself in layers as a series of alarming black spatial rifts appeared.

The crimson sea down below was also severely ravaged, and the seawater began to boil, sending large plumes of red water vapor rising up into the air.

At the same time, a massive crater appeared on the surface of the sea as if the seawater had been forced down by some type of tremendous weight, and massive waves hundreds of feet tall rose up around the edge of the crater before collapsing toward its center. The blue space that encompassed this area of the sea was also unable to withstand the force of the explosions and was violently shattered.

The astounding commotion continued for several moments before gradually subsiding.

At this point, all that remained of the small island were several small rocky sections that were jutting out of the surface of the sea, while massive waves continued to surge through the area.

On one of the remaining small sections of the island laid the brocade-robed elderly man in a puddle of his own blood. His suit of armor had been completely destroyed, and there were many protective treasure fragments scattered around him, but he was still alive, albeit extremely severely injured.

All of a sudden, Han Li appeared around 10,000 feet away, and his gaze instantly locked onto the elderly man down below.

The elderly man also looked up at Han Li at the same time, and his eyes were filled with burning resentment.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as killing intent gleamed in his eyes, and he was just about to swoop down from above when several bursts of azure light suddenly appeared around him, and five identical Fang Pans emerged out of thin air in unison, all of which were slashing their sabers at him from different directions.

The five black saber projections fused as one, layering on top of one another in a dream-like fashion as they pierced directly toward Han Li's heart, and Han Li immediately sped up in his descent upon seeing this.

A loud thump rang out as the saber projection struck him on the back, instantly shattering his True Extreme Membrane and inflicting a bleeding gash that was deep enough to expose bone.

Han Li took advantage of the force of the impact to further accelerate in his descent toward the elderly man, and at the same time, he sent a small bead flying down at his target with a flick of his wrist.

At this point, all of the brocade-robed elderly man's protective treasures had already been destroyed, and he was carrying extremely severe injuries, rendering him unable to evade the oncoming attack.

A determined look immediately appeared on his face as he thrust a palm down onto the top of his own head, and a golden nascent soul shot out of in a flash of before attempting to flee.

However, before it was able to get away, the Heavy Water Lightning Bead that Han Li had purchased at the grand auction exploded without any warning.

A black sun the size of a mountain instantly appeared out of thin air, releasing hundreds of thick bolts of azure and purple lightning, as well as a burst of devastating law powers.

The bolts of azure and purple lightning resembled whips of the lightning god as they lashed out in all directions, destroying the brocade-robed elderly man's body and nascent soul in a flash.

However, right at this moment, a burst of azure light suddenly flew rapidly out of the elderly man's destroyed physical body. It was traveling so quickly that its speed rivaled instantaneous teleportation, and it flew straight into Han Li's body as he was frantically flying away from the explosion.

While Han Li was putting an end to the brocade-robed elderly man's life, Fang Pan had darted back in retreat, and a black chain had appeared in front of him, around which countless black runes were circulating incessantly.

Immediately thereafter, he shot forth through the air in direct pursuit of Han Li.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the mountainous black sun exploded into a vast expanse of black light that rapidly expanded in all directions.

Han Li and Fang Pan were able to just barely fly out of the black light's range, but they were still inevitably struck by the shockwaves resulting from the explosion, sending them flying away in a rather unsteady fashion.

Bright azure light appeared around Fang Pan as he darted through the air several times in succession, moving in a way that defied reason as he intermittently vanished before reappearing, reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye.

With a flick of his wrist, the black chain in his hand shot forth in a flash, hurtling directly toward Han Li's lower abdomen.

The oncoming chain was too close for Han Li to evade, and he immediately opened his mouth to release several balls of blood essence, which erupted into a large cloud of blood mist around him.

The black chain shot straight into the cloud of blood mist, but at virtually the exact same moment, a crimson figure flew out of the blood mist, and it had fled to hundreds of kilometers away in just a few flashes, then vanished altogether with one more flash.

The cloud of blood mist scattered quickly thereafter, and the chain was also nowhere to be seen.

……

Close to 100,000 kilometers away, a flash of silver lightning appeared in the sky above a dark blue sea, and Han Li stumbled out from within with his entire body covered in blood. He almost fell out of the sky before steadying himself, and his complexion had paled even further.

The Blood Shadow Movement Technique that he had just unleashed had worsened his condition even further, and his constant fleeing over the past nearly two months was taking a real toll on his body.

He took a deep breath to compose himself, and only after devouring an Origin Return Pill did a hint of color begin to return to his cheeks. He then closed his eyes and directed his spiritual sense into his own dantian, and sure enough, four extremely familiar black chains had appeared around his nascent soul.

However, he was quite relieved to see this.

Thankfully, he had managed to react just in the nick of time, so Fang Pan was unable to completely unleash the power of these troublesome chains. Otherwise, if he were to have his nascent soul sealed again, then he would've been as good as dead.

Even so, half of his immortal spiritual power had still been sealed away.

Immediately thereafter, his brows furrowed slightly as he noticed a glowing black mark hovering beneath his nascent soul, and it had been left behind by that streak of azure light that had shot out of the brocade-robed elderly man's body right before his demise.

This wasn't a restriction or anything of that nature. Instead, it was most likely some type of tracking mark.

Given sufficient time, he would be able to eradicate the mark, but Fang Pan clearly wasn't going to afford him that luxury.

What was rather peculiar was the aura emanating from the mark belonged to Fang Pan as opposed to the brocade-robed elderly man.

Right as Han Li was pondering this matter, he suddenly turned to take a glance in a certain direction as a peculiar look appeared on his face, and after a moment of contemplation, he began to fly deeper in that direction as a streak of azure light.

Around 15 minutes later, he drew to a halt above a certain section of the sea, and a rather perplexed look appeared on his face.

His spiritual sense told him that the surrounding sea in a radius of close to 100,000 kilometers was extraordinarily peaceful. There were many ordinary fish in the area, but barely any demon beasts.

With that in mind, he began to fly deeper into the area as a streak of azure light, and at the same time, he completely concealed his own aura, sinking toward the seabed like a rock.

As he did this, he released his enormous spiritual sense to envelop the mark in his body one layer after another in a bid to keep it as concealed and undetectable to the outside world as possible.

Not long after Han Li sank to the bottom of the sea, Fang Pan appeared above the surface of the sea amid a flash of azure light.

He closed his eyes to sense Han Li's location for a moment, then cast his gaze downward.

Even though the tracking mark he had left behind was being suppressed by something, he was still able to vaguely sense it.

A cold smile appeared on his face as he shot straight down toward the surface of the sea as a streak of azure light, then plunged into the water.

With his speed, he was able to reach the seabed in the blink of an eye.

It was completely dark and silent at the bottom of the sea, and he quickly scanned his gaze across his surroundings before focusing his attention on an unremarkable-looking giant rock several thousand feet away.

He then rushed toward the rock without any hesitation, unleashing a black saber projection that was several thousand feet in length, parting all of the seawater in its path as it surged along the seabed.

The saber projection struck the giant rock, but much to Fang Pan's surprise, the rock wasn't split apart.

All of a sudden, Han Li shot back from the other side of the rock as a streak of black light, and there was a barely detectable smile on his face.

A pair of clones appeared on either side of Fang Pan, and they slashed their black sabers through the water, sending a pair of saber projections hurtling toward Han Li from both the left and the right.

The two saber projections came together to form a black cross as they sped toward Han Li, stirring up all of the seawater in their wake.

Han Li seemed to have already been prepared for this, and he crossed his scaly arms in front of himself to form a barrier.

A loud clang rang out as he was sent flying back like a cannonball from the force of the impact, and right at this moment, a thunderous roar rang out from afar, causing the entire seabed to tremble and quake.

The seabed in the distance then exploded violently, sending countless rock fragments flying in all direction as a mountainous black shadow slowly emerged, giving off a terrifyingly powerful aura.

As it turned out, that seemingly unremarkable giant rock from before had actually been one of the fleshy bulbs on the mountainous creature's body.

Fang Pan was naturally quite alarmed by this unexpected turn of events, and he immediately paused in his pursuit of Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li gave Fang Pan a gloating grin, then vanished into a nearby trench on the seabed, completely vanishing out of sight. Even his aura had completely faded.

Fang Pan's heart immediately sank upon seeing this, and right as he was also about to conceal his own aura, a pair of giant green eyes suddenly opened up before him, and it was glowering at him with furious killing intent.

An unprecedented sense of fear immediately welled up in Fang Pan's heart.

At this point, he had already caught a clear glimpse of the black shadow's complete form, and it was a gargantuan purplish-black octopus that was over 10,000 feet in size. Its body was riddled with black bulbous growths that resembled giant rocks, and its massive, scaly tentacles were swinging through the water violently, churning up the entire sea.

A rift opened up beneath the pair of eyes, revealing a huge black hole, within which an array of sharp white teeth could just barely be made out, and it was clear that being devoured by this creature would be sure to spell one's demise.

This is a late-True Immortal Stage sea beast!

Chapter 171: Last Resort

All of a sudden, all of the giant octopus's tentacles closed in toward the center, and it's enormous body sped toward Fang Pan as a blurry black shadow, resembling a purplish-black mountain that was moving rapidly along the seabed in a bizarre sight to behold.

Even before it was fully upon Fang Pan, the surrounding seawater was churning violently in the face of the tremendous pressure that it was exerting. The resulting currents were so violent that Fang Pan was swaying unsteadily in the water, and he was sent flying back like a cannonball, only managing to steady himself after stumbling several times in succession.

Meanwhile, the giant octopus had already appeared no more than 1,000 feet away from him, and it swatted its eight tentacles viciously at Fang Pan, leaving a series of bright trails in the water amid a sound that resembled rumbling thunderclaps.

Fang Pan was quite alarmed, but he managed to maintain his composure as he instantly split up into five different clones amid a flash of azure light, and each of the clones fled in a different direction.

The giant octopus's tentacles faltered slightly upon seeing this, and it seemed to have been caught off guard by this maneuver from Fang Pan. However, in the next instant, its tentacles continued to come crashing down with devastating force, smashing several deep trenches into the seabed that were several thousand feet in length as countless rock fragments flew in all directions.

Taking advantage of this brief window of opportunity, the five clones conjured up by Fang Pan were just barely able to evade the flailing tentacles before rising up toward the surface of the sea like lightning.

The giant octopus let loose a furious roar, and green light flashed within its eyes as it opened its mouth to release five pillars of purplish-black lightning, each of which was as thick as a water tank.

The five pillars of lightning didn't appear to have been remarkable in any way, but they were far faster than normal lightning, and they caught up to the five Fang Pans in a flash before striking them with unerring accuracy.

Five resounding booms rang out as four of the Fang Pans were destroyed by the purplish-black lightning, with only the leftmost one managing to survive the attack, but even he was sent flyin forward by the force of the impact as he threw up a large mouthful of blood.

However, it seemed that he hadn't suffered any severe injuries, and he was able to steady himself after performing a somersault.

The material of the robe on his back had been torn apart by the lightning strike, revealing a suit of dark golden inner armor that was riddled with golden scales.

A deep mark had been blasted onto the suit of armor, and many of the scales on its surface had been broken. Its spiritual nature had also been severely damaged, but ultimately, it remained intact.

Meanwhile, Fang Pan continued to fly up toward the surface of the sea as a streak of azure light, traveling at an incredible speed.

The giant octopus let loose another thunderous roar of fury, and it extended its tentacles before withdrawing them forcefully, launching itself after the streak of azure light as a blurry black shadow.

Inside the sea, its speed was just about on par with Fang Pan's.

The two of them instantly vanished into the distance as the chase continued, and the turbulent seawater left in their wake slowly settled down again.

Only then did Han Li emerge from the trench on the seabed, and he took a glance at the direction that Fang Pan and the giant octopus had fled in with a hesitant look on his face.

However, he then quickly arrived at a decision and began flying in that direction as an azure shadow.

It appeared that his plan had been successful up to this point, but he wasn't confident that the sea beast would be powerful enough to hunt Fang Pan to his death, so he decided to follow them and finish the job himself if the octopus couldn't kill Fang Pan in his place.

Han Li's speed was far inferior to that of Fang Pan and the giant octopus, and at this point, the two of them had already traveled out of his spiritual sensory range, but the immortal spiritual power fluctuations left in their wake provided an extremely clear trail to follow.

He followed this trail for close to an hour, then suddenly drew to an abrupt halt.

The seawater several hundred kilometers up ahead was churning violently as if it had been brought to a boil, and there were countless vortexes raging in the area. Even from this far away, he could still feel tremendously powerful currents washing over him.

At the center of all the chaos was a giant ball of light that was several dozen kilometers in size with countless arcs of purple lightning and black mist surging around it.

The lightning and the mist intertwined to form a series of balls of purplish-black light before exploding violently, sending immense destructive energy erupting in all directions.

Even the seabed was constantly being torn apart, causing magma to flow out into the water.

This is a spirit domain... No, it's not quite the same. Instead, it seems to be some type of domain ability similar to a spirit domain.

A hint of lingering fear welled up in Han Li's heart as he sensed the terrifying spiritual pressure being released by the massive ball of light.

Even though the giant octopus that he had lured out possessed late-True Immortal Stage power, it seemed to be some type of primordial beast that hadn't yet attained higher intelligence. Otherwise, if it had unleashed this domain ability right away, then Han Li would've been swept up in it as well.

Han Li only entertained this thought for a moment before casting it aside, and a layer of blue light appeared in his eyes as he cast his gaze into the giant ball of light, within which he could just barely make out two figures, one far larger than the other, clashing over and over again.

The larger of the two figures was naturally the giant octopus. It had shrunk down from its original size to less than 200 feet tall, making it far more agile than before, while the other figure was none other than Fang Pan.

Fang Pan's speed seemed to have been severely limited within the ball of light, and he was at an absolute disadvantage, constantly being sent flying over and over again by the giant octopus's tentacles.

At this moment, he appeared to have been in an extremely sorry state. His face was pale, his hair was disheveled, and the azure light around his body had dimmed significantly.

However, there was a silver scroll hovering above his head, releasing countless silver runes that formed a silver light barrier around him. Under the protection of the light barrier, he was able to avoid significant injury despite being sent flying over and over again.

Once again, Fang Pan was sent flying by one of the flailing tentacles, and the silver light barrier was flashing erratically.

After such a long and drawn-out battle, the giant octopus was becoming impatient, and it was lashing out with its tentacles faster and faster. As a result, the frequency at which Fang Pan was being struck was significantly increased.

This was a dire situation. Given his current cultivation base, if he couldn't escape from this spirit-domain-like space, then he would be sure to meet his demise once the immortal treasure above his head was broken.

With that in mind, his resentment toward Han Li only grew more intense.

Right at this moment, the octopus's wildly flailing tentacles suddenly paused for a moment, and it abruptly opened its mouth to release a huge torrent of ink.

Fang Pan felt a foul stench surging toward him, and he was struck by a rush of dizziness.

He hurriedly drew upon his spiritual sense to rid himself of the sense of dizziness, and at the same time, the silver scroll above him began to radiate dazzling light.

Countless silver runes surged out of the scroll to form a round silver shield of light, which resembled a silver moon that protected him from above.

A burst of loud sizzling rang out as plumes of smoke rose up from the silver shield upon making contact with the black ink, and countless holes were instantly eroded into its surface.

The black ink flowed through the holes on the shield as it continued to rain down toward Fang Pan, who hurriedly switched to a different hand seal as he began to chant an incantation.

The silver scroll instantly erupted into flames, and balls of silver fire descended from it to ignite the silver light barrier around him.

From afar, it appeared as if Fang Pan's entire body had transformed into a massive silver fireball.

As soon as the black ink came into contact with the silver flames, the former instantly evaporated into plumes of black smoke.

However, before Fang Pan had a chance to catch his breath, the giant octopus suddenly extended its eight tentacles until they were ramrod straight and resembled eight staves, then swung them through the air to send countless staff projections sweeping toward Fang Pan from all directions.

A string of earth-shattering booms rang out, and the silver fireball began to tremble violently.

At the same time, the flames on the silver scroll above Fang Pan's head were quickly being snuffed out, and it clearly wasn't going to be able to last much longer.

"No! I refuse to die here!" Fang Pan roared, and a thought suddenly seemed to have occurred to him as he flipped a hand over to produce an azure pill.

The pill was only around the size of a thumbnail, but it was giving off extraordinary spiritual power fluctuations and was riddled with countless tiny azure runes, while an extremely life-like visage of a miniature azure wyrm had appeared above the pill.

This pill was called the Azure Wyrm Pill, and he had purchased it for an extremely steep price in preparation for his late-True Immortal Stage breakthrough. It wasn't a dao pill, but it wasn't any less valuable than the average first-tier dao pill.

He naturally wasn't going to attempt a breakthrough in this situation.

Instead, he wanted to take advantage of one of the pill's effects, which was its ability to stimulate the consumer's latent potential, allowing them to attain power far superior to their cultivation base for a short time. As a result, one would be able to experience what it was like to be at a higher cultivation base, thereby significantly increasing their chances of making a successful breakthrough.

In this desperate situation, Fang Pan had no choice but to take the pill.

His entire body instantly began to radiate incandescent azure light, and his waning aura was being rapidly elevated, quickly returning to its former peak before continuing to swell even further.

In this instant, it seemed that all of the latent potential in his body had been forced to the fore.

Violent immortal spiritual power fluctuations erupted out of his body, while the azure light was dancing over his skin like fire.

Furthermore, around 20 to 30 bright specks of azure light that were fluctuating in brightness had appeared all over his body, and they resembled a series of blinking eyes.

Immediately thereafter, another speck of azure light abruptly lit up on a certain part of his body.

In the next instant, all 24 specks of light brightened in unison as if they were resonating with one another, causing his aura to swell even further, to the point that it was beginning to reach the same level as that of the octopus monster.

Fang Pan bit down viciously onto the tip of his own tongue, then spat out a mouthful of blood essence, which fused into the silver scroll above his head.

The scroll was already on the verge of destruction, but with this injection of blood essence, the flames burning on its surface were suddenly revitalized, transforming into a fireball that was several dozen feet in size.

All the silver runes around Fang Pan also swept upward in a frenzy before fusing into the fireball as well.

Immediately thereafter, the silver fireball rose up toward the heavens, then exploded with a resounding boom.

Boundless silver light swept through the air in all directions alongside incredibly powerful shockwaves, keeping all of the staff projections formed by the giant octopus's tentacles at bay.

Fang Pan took advantage of this opportunity to dart through the air as a blurry azure shadow, and his black saber had already reappeared in his grasp.

In the blink of an eye, he arrived at the edge of the spirit-domain-like space, then conjured up seven identical clones, all of which lashed out viciously with the black sabers in their hands.

The seven black saber projections combined as one to form a massive saber projection that was close to 10,000 feet in length, and it struck the dark purple light barrier up ahead with devastating force.

The dark purple light barrier flashed erratically as a huge crack appeared on its surface, following which the entire light barrier exploded altogether.

Fang Pan immediately seized this opportunity, fleeing from the giant octopus as a streak of azure light.

All of this had taken place in the span of only one or two seconds, and by the time the giant octopus set off in pursuit, Fang Pan had already vanished into the distant sea.

Chapter 172: Put an End to Things

That's a pity.

Han Li turned to the direction that Fang Pan had fled in, but then quickly withdrew his gaze.

Fang Pan had already sustained severe injuries during that battle, so even if he remained intent on coming after Han Li, at the very least, he wasn't going to be able to do that anytime soon.

With that in mind, Han Li took one final glance at the furious octopus, then flew away into the distance along the seabed as a blurry shadow.

He traveled for tens of thousands of kilometers in one go, and only ensuring that the octopus hadn't detected him did he spring out of the sea before making a hand seal to conjure up a silver lightning array around himself.

A loud thunderclap rang out as he vanished on the spot, then reappeared in the next instant tens of thousands of kilometers away.

He then conjured up another lightning array without pause, teleporting him tens of thousands of kilometers in another direction.

He repeated this process quite a number of times before stopping on a small and deserted island.

There, he flipped a hand over to release a large pile of array treasures and other items before taking around half a day to set up a star array on a plot of empty island on the island, one that was identical to the star array that he had set up on Dark Veil Island.

He then also set up around a dozen protective arrays around the entire island to transform it into a fortress, one that even a late-True Immortal cultivator would be unable to break through in a short time.

Only after doing all of this did Han Li heave a faint sigh of relief before sitting down at the center of the star array on the island with his legs crossed.

Not long after that, layers of multi-colored light began to appear, enshrouding the entire island and presenting an extremely eye-catching sight.

Thankfully, this region of the sea was extremely desolate with not a single person around, so he didn't have to worry about catching the attention of anyone harboring sinister intentions.

Day quickly turned to night, and stars began to appear in the sky.

A vast expanse of dazzling starlight appeared on the island, and even the surrounding restrictions weren't able to completely conceal it.

Countless rays of starlight cascaded down from the heavens, forming seven scintillating pillars of starlight that crashed down from above.

A burst of dull rumbling rang out from the island, and it was audible even dozens of kilometers away.

Time slowly passed by, and over two months flew by in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, all of the light barriers encompassing the small island faded to reveal Han Li, who was holding a black chain around the same thickness as an infant's arm in his hand.

This time, his nascent soul hadn't been completely sealed, and with his prior experience, it hadn't taken him very long to remove the chains from around his nascent soul, but despite this, there was still a grim look on his face.

No matter what he tried, he was unable to completely remove that tracking mark in his body, and as time passed by, it was becoming more and more likely that Fang Pan would've recovered from his injuries to continue the hunt.

Furthermore, the fact that Fang Pan still hadn't shown up after all this time was evoking within Han Li a sense of unease.

He stood silently in mid-air with a contemplative look in his eyes, and moments later, he took a deep breath, seemingly having arrived at a decision.

He stowed away all of the array treasures on the island, then flew into the distance as a streak of azure light.

……

Over three more months passed by in the blink of an eye, and a roar of elation that pierced straight up into the heavens suddenly rang out from within a certain mountain range somewhere on the Primordial Wave Continent.

In the next instant, a burst of dazzling azure light appeared somewhere in the mountain range, only to vanish a moment later before reappearing in the sky.

Within the azure light was none other than Fang Pan, and he was chortling with glee.

"Even the heavens are on my side! Who could've imagined that the Azure Wyrm Pill would allow me to open up my 24th immortal accupoint?"

A burst of enormous spiritual pressure was emanating from his body as he spoke. At this point, he had already progressed to the late-True Immortal Stage, and it was as if he had been completely reborn anew.

He was glowing with joy as he sensed the changes in his own body, and only after a long while did his excitement subside, following which a cold smile appeared on his face.

"Run all you want, Han Li, but you're not getting away from me!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he shot forth as a streak of azure light, traveling eastward at a terrifying speed.

Meanwhile, Han Li was flying through the sky as a streak of azure light himself above a lush forest countless kilometers away.

All of a sudden, a dark look appeared on his face. Just now, the tracking mark that had sat dormant beneath his nascent soul for the past few months had suddenly stirred slightly.

"He's finally coming after me again... It's time to put an end to this..." Han Li murmured to himself, then accelerated even further as he sped through the air.

Even though he was flying at full speed, it still took only less than half a month before Fang Pan's familiar aura appeared on the edge of his spiritual sensory range, and the distance between the two of them was quickly being closed down.

No wonder he didn't appear for so long, he made a breakthrough! This is most certainly not good...

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as a grim look appeared on his face, but he didn't slow down in the slightest.

Before long, the two of them were only separated by a few thousand kilometers.

Only then did Han Li make a hand seal, and silver lightning erupted out of his body as he prepared to conjure up his lightning array.

Fang Pan's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this from afar, and countless azure runes surged out of his body.

Immediately thereafter, his speed was almost doubled, transforming into a blurry azure shadow as he let loose a draconic roar.

A burst of peculiar soundwaves spread rapidly through the air, causing the space to ripple as soundwaves instantly permeated throughout the entire surrounding area in a radius of several thousand kilometers.

Han Li was instantly struck by a rush of dizziness upon hearing this sound, and the formation of his silver lightning array was paused as a result.

Even though he was able to snap back to his senses an instant later, at this point, the azure shadow was now alarmingly close to him.

A bright saber projection swept through the air like lightning before striking the lightning array.

In the face of the saber projection, the arcs of silver lightning were as fragile as tofu, and the entire array was instantly destroyed.

Han Li immediately plummeted out of the sky upon seeing this to just barely evade the saber projection, and at the same time, he instantly adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form amid a flash of golden light.

He had only just completed his transformation when the azure shadow arrived directly before him, only to be greeted by a giant golden fist, which was carrying such tremendous power that even the nearby space was rippling violently.

However, Fang Pan was able to evade the golden fist projection with ease by sidestepping several dozen feet in an instant, and immediately thereafter, one Fang Pan turned into three.

One of the Fang Pan's lashed out with his saber to strike the giant ape's arm, and the blade of the saber was plunged into the golden ape's flesh, inflicting a huge wound that immediately began to bleed profusely.

In the past, the giant ape's defenses had been sufficient to ward off the saber, but this was no longer the case.

Meanwhile, the other two Fang Pans were pouncing at the giant ape like lightning while lashing out with their sabers at the giant ape's neck and chest.

The golden ape let loose a thunderous roar as its entire body swelled in dize, and countless rays of golden light surfaced over its fur.

Each ray of golden light was actually a strand of golden monkey fur, and they shot forth in all directions, screeching through the air while the space in their wake trembled violently.

The three Fang Pans' expressions changed slightly upon seeing this, and they shot back in retreat in unison while conjuring up azure light barriers around their own bodies.

The countless strands of golden fur struck the protective barriers, producing a sound much like that of rain pelting down on banana leaves.

The azure protective barriers flashed erratically, but remained intact. However, the three Fang Pans were still pushed back by quite a distance by the power imbued within the strands of golden fur.

The giant golden ape didn't unleash any further attacks, instantly transforming into a Lightning Bird instead.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as the Lightning Bird vanished from the spot amid a flash of silver lightning, only to reappear several thousand kilometers away.

"You're not getting away!" Fang Pan roared as his three clones instantly fused back into one, and he shot forth in pursuit as a blurry azure shadow.

However, the silver Lightning Bird wasn't making any effort to conserve its power of lightning as it unleashed its lightning movement technique over and over again, quickly opening up a distance of tens of thousands of kilometers between itself and Fang Pan.

Immediately thereafter, countless arcs of silver lightning erupted from the Lightning Bird's body to form a silver lightning array.

Meanwhile, Fang Pan was closing in at an incredible speed from the distant horizon.

A resounding thunderclap rang out, and the Lightning Bird vanished into thin air only an instant before Fang Pan arrived on the scene.

Fang Pan drew to a halt with a dark look in his eyes, but a cold smile then immediately appeared on his face.

Given how recklessly Han Li was using his power of lightning, he was going to exhaust this power very soon, and once that happened, his fate would be sealed.

With that in mind, Fang Pan continued in his pursuit of Han Li as a streak of azure light.

Three days later.

There was a dilapidated little brick temple situated in a lush forest on a mountain. The red paint on its outer walls had already completely peeled off, and they were hanging off the walls in flakes that were harder than the bark of old trees.

Out of the two wooden doors, one of them had already snapped off and was resting against the other relatively more intact door, leaving a gap that was around half a person wide.

Through the gap, it could be seen that the temple hadn't been visited for a very long time. Everything was covered in dust and cobwebs, and a thick layer of moss had grown over the bluestone floor as well.

An unrecognizable deity statue was situated inside the temple, but its head had fallen off and rolled to a corner of the temple.

Seated with a weary look on their face and their back resting against said head was none other than Han Li.

Right at this moment, he seemed to have detected something, and he immediately raised his head to look up at the sky through one of the holes in the dilapidated temple's roof, but he saw nothing but clearly blue skies.

He immediately flew out of the temple amid a flash of lightning, then fled toward the distance, followed by a streak of azure light several thousand kilometers away.

A high-speed chase ensued, and the two streaks of light passed over several dozen mountain ranges in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was rapidly burning through his immortal spiritual power reserves as he accelerated to as fast as he could go, but he was refraining from using his lightning movement technique, and as a result, the gap between himself and Fang Pan was constantly shrinking. Before long, they were separated by less than 1,000 kilometers.

Right at this moment, a mountain range in the shape of a semi-circle appeared up ahead, and Han Li immediately swooped down directly toward the snow-tipped summits of one of the mountains.

Not long after he landed on that mountain, plumes of dense white mist immediately began to rise up from the mountain summit, quickly enveloping the other mountains in the mountain range as well.

Chapter 173: Reality or Illusion

A burst of rippling silver light appeared within the mist, and a series of beautiful palaces and pavilions emerged, while gorgeous white jade arched bridges suddenly appeared to connect the mountains in the mountain range, giving the area the appearance of an immortal paradise.

As soon as this strange setting appeared, Fang Pan arrived on the scene before instantly drawing to a halt.

He looked down at the extremely life-like palaces and pavilions down below, and he harrumphed coldly, "Looks like you haven't just been sitting around, doing nothing for the past half a year. Let me see what other tricks you have up your sleeve!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swooped down toward the palaces, plunging headfirst into the mist before landing on the summit of one of the mountains.

He then closed his eyes, only to reopen them a moment later as a hint of bewilderment appeared on his face.

He discovered that he was suddenly unable to detect Han Li's exact location. Instead, he could only roughly sense that Han Li was somewhere nearby.

A cold look appeared on his face as his body began to blur, following which six identical clones flew out.

The seven Fang Pans then split up and shot forth in seven different directions as streaks of azure light.

The seven streaks of azure light traversed back and forth through the area, then returned to their original starting point not long thereafter, having failed to track down their target.

Right at this moment, one of the Fang Pans suddenly noticed something, and he immediately crouched down before laying a palm against the ground.

"This is... an array within an array!" he murmured to himself with tightly furrowed brows as he withdrew his palm before rising to his feet.

As soon as this realization was made, the seven Fang Pans immediately formed a circle with their backs facing one another.

All seven of them then lashed out with their black sabers in unison, sending seven massive saber projections sweeping through the air in all directions.

Gusts of fierce wind were swept up as the seven saber projections multiplied rapidly into countless saber projections, resembling a black lotus flower of saber projections as it rose up into the air while revolving incessantly.

The surrounding space trembled violently, and all of the illusory palaces and spires began to warp and twist in the face of the tremendous and peerlessly sharp power of the mass of saber projections.

Immediately thereafter, a dull thump rang out, and all of the illusory buildings gradually began to fade away, revealing the true state of the mountain.

As it turned out, the summit of the mountain had already been shaved off to produce a plateau, and the ground was laden with white jade stone slabs, upon which were engraved countless circles of strange rune. Engraved onto the ground at the center of these circles of runes was a strange-looking beast.

Around the beast were roughly a dozen white stone pillars, each of which was over 100 feet tall, and there were many crystals of different shapes and colors embedded onto the pillars, presenting a captivating sight to behold.

The seven Fang Pans reverted back to a single one, and a slightly dazed look appeared in his eyes at the sight of the scene that he had been greeted by. However, he then immediately turned around to spot the azure-robed Han Li standing several thousand feet away, holding a round array plate in one hand while rapidly casting incantation seals onto it with his other hand.

Han Li seemed to have detected Fang Pan's gaze, and he raised his head as a faint smile appeared on his face.

He was currently in the process of activating an array by the name of the Calabash Illusory Light Array, which was a high-grade illusory array that he had found through the Transient Guild several months ago, and it was a disposable array.

For this array, he had spent all of his top-grade spirit stones, the only two remaining Great Earth Fruits in his possession, and even a pair of spirit treasures of quite a high caliber from the storage bracelet given to him by Gan Jiuzhen.

It was said that the array was extremely powerful, and that anyone below the Golden Immortal Stage that fell into it would be unable to awaken on their own. Instead, they would only sink deeper and deeper into the array until they perished within it, and even their nascent soul wouldn't be able to escape.

However, the array also had some major drawbacks, the first of which was that it took an extremely long time to activate, which was why Han Li had set up a Nine Palaces Heavenly Array around it to stall for time.

The second drawback was that the one using the array had to use themselves as the array's core. As a result, they had to be subjected to the effects of the array as well, so the array posed just as much of a threat to its user as its target.

However, the one controlling the array naturally held many advantages over someone who was completely unprepared, and if they could awaken before their enemy, then they would be able to control the array to directly attack said enemy.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Fang Pan's heart at the sight of the faint smile that had appeared on Han Li's face, and he immediately launched himself at Han Li while thrusting his black saber directly toward Han Li's heart.

Meanwhile, sweat was beginning to bead up on Han Li's forehead, and he was finally able to cast the last incantation seal onto the array plate right before the tip of Fang Pan's saber could reach him.

All of a sudden, the surrounding stone pillars began to release bursts of bright light of different colors, and Fang Pan's vision was blurred by these bright lights.

Before he had a chance to react, he stumbled forward, feeling as if he had passed through an invisible barrier before arriving in a rather dimly lit hall.

He swept his gaze across the thick square pillars around him and the antiquated braziers hanging from the pillars, as well as the bright green flames burning within the braziers, and a sense of familiarity welled up in his heart.

The sound of metal chains clattering over one another suddenly rang out within the deathly silent hall, followed by a deep and extremely authoritative voice.

"How dare you swing your blade at me! Are you trying to kill your master?"

Fang Pan shuddered violently upon hearing this voice, and he reflexively lowered his blade in fear and submission.

He turned his gaze forward to discover an inky-black chair over 100 feet up ahead, upon which sat a middle-aged man. The man was wearing a pristine white cape, and he had purple and green zombie-like skin.

"Master," Fang Pan called out in a dazed voice, then immediately shook his head vigorously as a cold look appeared in his eyes.

"No, you're not my master! You're just an illusion conjured up by this array!" he roared as he raised his saber and pointed it directly at the zombie-like man again.

He then sprang forward through the air, leaving a trail of blurry afterimages in his wake.

In the blink of an eye, seven identical Fang Pans had appeared in the hall, and they were pouncing at the zombie-like man from all directions.

"How dare you!" the zombie-like man roared, and a devastating aura erupted out of his body.

He wasn't chanting any incantations or making any hand seals, but all of the black chains littered through the entire hall seemed to have suddenly sprung to life, surging through the air in all directions like a series of black waves.

Despite their incredible speed, all seven Fang Pan clones were struck by the chain without exception before falling onto the ground with blood gushing out of their mouths.

"I taught you everything you know, yet now, you're trying to turn on me?" the zombie-like man questioned as a derisive look appeared on his face.

Fang Pan was astonished by what he was seeing. The zombie-like man's aura, powers, disposition, and voice were all completely identical to those of his master.

Could it be that I fell into some type of special teleportation array as opposed to an illusory array?

For the first time, Fang Pan was beginning to doubt his own conviction.

Before Fang Pan had a chance to ponder the topic any further, the zombie-like man's voice rang out once again. "Come over here and accept your death! Or do you want me to catch you myself?"

A hesitant look appeared in Fang Pan's eyes...

Meanwhile, Han Li had fallen into the illusory array as well.

The wind was howling past his ears, and he found himself rapidly rising up into the heavens.

At this moment, there was a massive expressionless face high up in the sky, and it was gradually becoming more blurry and indistinct. A burst of dazzling purple light flashed behind it, following which a long white rift slowly opened up, from within which the sound of faint Sanskrit chanting could be heard.

This is the gate to the Immortal Realm! Am I transcending my ascension tribulation?

Never did Han Li think that the illusion that awaited him would be his ascension tribulation.

All of a sudden, a deafening thunderclap rang out from overhead, and a massive bolt of seven-colored lightning came crashing down from the giant face, which had almost completely faded at this point.

The bolt of lightning came crashing directly down toward Han Li, carrying with it a devastating aura of destruction.

Han Li reflexively swept a hand through the air, and a string of golden lightningfire instantly flew out of his palm toward the bolt of seven-colored lightning.

He looked down to find a dark green longsword in his hand, and the sword was very familiar to him.

It was none other than his Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword.

Han Li hesitated momentarily as he felt the tremendous pressure weighing down on him from above, then sped straight up into the heavens as a streak of azure light with the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword in his grasp.

A resounding boom erupted throughout the entire sky as a layer of resplendent light that obscured the entire sky flashed erratically before being destroyed amid a burst of violent law fluctuations.

Han Li was sent plummeting down from the heavens, and his entire body was in excruciating pain.

His body had been charred black and was riddled with bright red gashes, almost falling apart at the seams, while the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword in his hand had been completely destroyed.

At the same time, the giant face up above had become extremely clear again, and it remained expressionless as ever. It seemed to be looking down on all things with cold apathy before abruptly exploding.

Immediately thereafter, the gate leading to the Immortal Realm suddenly closed, while a massive spatial rift appeared beside it.

Through the rift, Han Li caught a glimpse of a vast expanse of absolute darkness that seemed to be capable of devouring all things.

The darkness didn't even harbor the slightest glimmer of light, yet it somehow struck him with a peculiar sense of allure, evoking within him an irrepressible urge to fly into it.

Chapter 174: Mastermind?

At this moment, Han Li's entire body was on the verge of falling apart, and he couldn't muster up even an ounce of energy or magic power.

He wanted to control his own body, but he discovered that he couldn't even lift a single finger, and he could only watch helplessly as he drifted toward the inky-black spatial rift.

This is an illusion, it's not real...

Han Li was telling himself this over and over again while doing everything in his power to snap out of the illusion.

Right at this moment, a disturbance suddenly appeared in the space in front of the massive rift in the sky, and ripples that were visible even to the naked eye swept through the air, immediately following which three faint black shadows flew out from within before drifting toward him.

They appeared to be moving quite slowly, but in reality, they were approaching Han Li at an incredible speed.

Even though Han Li was unable to move, he could see just fine, and as he examined the three approaching figures, he discovered that they were completely insubstantial and ethereal, resembling a trio of spiritual bodies. Only their heads seemed to hold any substance, and their faces were completely identical to his own.

Are these inner demons? No, they're Extrarealm Heavenly Devils!

In the next instant, one of the heavenly devils appeared directly in front of him, then crashed straight into him without any warning.

A dull thump rang out, and all of the gashes all over Han Li's entire body began to glow with bright crimson light. The gashes then began to expand, and before he knew it, he had already been torn into countless pieces like a piece of porcelain that had been dashed against the ground.

To his surprise, he discovered that even though his body had been destroyed, his soul had managed to emerge as a faint azure shadow, yet it was also completely unable to move.

The three heavenly devils immediately pounced from all directions like a pack of wolves that had been starving for days, opening their mouths up wide before sinking their fangs into his soul.

A faint tearing sound rang out as a large chunk of Han Li's soul was stripped off before being devoured, resulting in a burst of indescribable agony.

Throughout his cultivation journey, Han Li had never shied away from bodily refinement, so he had a far superior pain threshold to the average person, yet this pain went far beyond anything he had ever experienced.

There was no way to pinpoint exactly where the pain was coming from, all he could sense was that his own soul was being torn apart bit by bit, and his consciousness was also gradually fading.

He could see the three heavenly devils constantly tearing away at his body, and with each bite that they took, their bodies would become a little more substantial, while the greedy smiles on their faces became more pronounced.

Is this still an illusion?

Han Li was completely powerless to resist, and his resolve was beginning to sway.

Could it be that I never even successfully transcended my tribulation? Could it be that the Spirit Domain Realm, Liu Le'er, the Black Wind Sea, Gan Jiuzhen... All of those were just a dream conjured up by these Extrarealm Heavenly Devils? I was once the most powerful Grand Ascension cultivator in the entire Spirit Realm, but it seems I was ultimately unable to overcome these Extrarealm Heavenly Devils...

Han Li's consciousness was quickly fading, and his body had become so transparent that it was barely even visible anymore.

"Don't allow yourself to fall prey to the illusion, Fellow Daoist Han. Us Extrarealm Heavenly Devils are not like this."

All of a sudden, a cold voice rang out in the surrounding space, snapping Han Li back to his senses like a bucket of cold water to the head.

Han Li's vision had already begun to blur, but it quickly refocused again, and at the same time, a cold harrumph rang out within his consciousness. Immediately thereafter, he felt as if several sharp spikes were being driven into his head at once, sending a burst of excruciating pain tearing through his soul.

At the same time, the heavenly devils that were tearing away at his body screeched in anguish as they hurriedly flew back in retreat, then vanished into nothingness.

Han Li immediately snapped back to reality, returning to the shaved mountain summit with the array plate held in one of his hands.

Directly in front of him, Fang Pan was rooted to the spot, still locked in a forward-charging posture, and the tip of the saber in his hand was no more than a foot away from Han Li's glabella.

The surrounding stone pillars were flashing incessantly with disorienting light, but those lights no longer had any effect on Han Li.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang," Han Li said internally with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"This is indeed an extremely formidable array. Thankfully, Extrarealm Heavenly Devils like myself are extremely adept at conjuring up and seeing through illusions. Otherwise, things could've gone catastrophically wrong," Mo Guang sighed.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then pressed his palm down onto the array plate while chanting an incantation.

A burst of five-colored light flashed through the array, and Han Li's surroundings blurred momentarily, following which he found himself in a dimly lit hall.

He could see Fang Pan kneeling on the ground with a horrified look on his face, kowtowing over and over again as he repeatedly implored, "Please spare me, Master..."

It seemed that he was completely oblivious to Han Li's presence.

There was a zombie-like middle-aged man with chains draped all over his body, and he was sitting on a large black chair in front of Fang Pan.

"Why have you used the Origin Separation Law Chains without my permission?" the zombie-like man interrogated.

Fang Pan shuddered violently upon hearing this, and he hurriedly replied, "I had no choice, Master! I ran into an extremely formidable foe, and at the time, I was with two other fellow daoists, but one of them was killed, while the other remaining fellow daoist and I were both severely injured. If I hadn't used those chains, there was no way I would've been able to kill that man."

Han Li was rather intrigued by what he was hearing, and he took a deep breath, then slowly made his way over to the zombie-like man before turning around and taking a seat on the large black chair.

His body gradually overlapped with that of the zombie-like man before the two completely fused as one, and Han Li did his best to imitate the zombie-like man's disposition as he asked, "Oh? Who exactly is this man, and why did you have to fight him?"

"His name is Han Li, and he's an immortal who ascended from a lower realm. He has a type of special crystal that contains the power of time laws, and that's why the three of us went after him," Fang Pan hurriedly explained.

With that, Han Li finally figured out why he had been in conflict with Fang Pan in the first place.

"Is that right? Do you know how he was able to obtain these crystals?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid I do not. At the time, I wasn't able to capture him, so I couldn't search his soul," Fang Pan replied.

"Are you telling the truth?" Han Li asked in a cold voice as he raised an eyebrow.

"I am, I swear! I would never dare to lie to you, Master! My other companion and I were both handed down severe punishments for failing to complete this mission," Fang Pan replied in a trembling voice.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, and he asked, "Who handed down your punishment? Are you telling me someone instructed the three of you to go after this Han Li?"

"Please forgive me, Master, but the one you ask of is someone of an extremely lofty status, so I cannot reveal their identity to you..."

Before Fang Pan had a chance to finish, he was struck by a heavy blow to the chest, sending him flying back through the air before crashing into one of the stone pillars in the hall with a dull thump.

The zombie-like man swept a sleeve through the air, and a black chain instantly shot forth like a spirit snake before plunging straight through Fang Pan's chest, sending blood splattering in all directions.

Fang Pan's face was deathly pale, and he was half-knelt on the ground as he violently threw up a mouthful of blood.

"Please spare me, Master..." he implored, but he still didn't dare to reveal that person's name.

"Even now, you're still choosing to withhold information from me! It looks like you're intent on testing my patience. I have no need for a disobedient disciple," the zombie-like man said in a cold voice, and a chorus of metallic rattling rang out across the entire hall.

Countless black chains drifted up into the air, and Fang Pan could feel mountainous pressure surging toward him from all directions, striking him with a crushing sense of asphyxiation.

"Please spare me, Master! I'll tell you everything!" he hurriedly yelled.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air upon hearing this, and all of the chains in the hall settled down again.

He then cast a cold gaze toward Fang Pan, silently waiting for him to continue.

"The name of the person who ordered us to go after Han Li is..."

Right as he was about to reveal the name, his face suddenly became twisted with pain , and he threw his hands onto his head as he howled in agony.

A peculiar spiritual aura that clearly didn't belong to Fang Pan began to emanate from his head, causing the surrounding illusion to ripple and warp, looking as if it could fall apart at any moment.

Han Li's heart immediately sank upon seeing this, and he instantly rushed forward to escape from the illusion.

In the real world, Fang Pan was still locked in the same posture as before, but his eyelids were rapidly fluttering, and it was clear that he was about to regain consciousness soon.

Han Li immediately made a decision, stepping forward to force Fang Pan's mouth open before summoning his final remaining Heavy Water Lightning Bead and tossing it inside.

He then turned and flew away into the distance as quickly as he could.

At this point, Fang Pan finally awakened from the illusion, but it was already too late.

As soon as his eyes sprang open, a bolt of purple and azure lightning blasted its way out of his mouth, following which an earth-shattering explosion rang out.

A massive black sun appeared out of thin air, and heaven and earth trembled and quaked violently.

Hovering at an altitude in excess of 100,000 feet, Han Li was watching the widespread destruction taking place below with a grim expression.

Even though he had finally managed to kill Fang Pan, he knew that this wasn't the end of his troubles.

Judging from what Fang Pan had revealed, it was clear that there had been someone instructing Fang Pan and the brocade-robed elderly man to come after him.

Furthermore, that person had left a mark on Fang Pan's soul, and it was that very same mark that had almost helped Fang Pan awaken from the illusion. Han Li didn't know whether that person would be able to detect that Fang Pan had met his demise, so he would have to be even more cautious from this point onward.

Once the shockwaves down below had subsided, Han Li flew down from his vantage point up above.

At this point, the array on the mountain had already been completely destroyed, as was the case with Fang Pan's physical body, and not even the slightest hint of his aura could be detected.

Han Li found Fang Pan's storage bracelet amid some rubble, then discovered that black saber under a giant rock, and after collecting those two things, he flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light.

Chapter 175: Seafaring Lightning Boat

Only after flying for tens of thousand of kilometers did Han Li heave a long sigh of relief.

Judging from the information that he had received from Fang Pan, he clearly still wasn't safe yet, but at the very least, the most immediate threat had been eliminated.

He released his spiritual sense to briefly inspect his surroundings, then flew toward a certain direction.

A short while later, he arrived in front of a large city.

He had changed his own appearance once again, transforming into a young scholar who appeared to be in his thirties. At the same time, he had concealed his own cultivation base entirely, and he was casually fanning himself with a peach wood paper fan as he made his way into the city as part of the crowd.

This city was called Moonview City, and it already belonged to the eastern region of the Primordial Wave Continent.

While fleeing from Fang Pan, he had been traveling eastward the majority of the time, so his eastbound journey actually hadn't been delayed by much at all.

In contrast with a rural city like Seaside City, Mooview City was no less prosperous than Black Wind City, but of course, it was far smaller than the latter.

Another difference between this city and Seaside was that the vast majority of the people here were mortals, while cultivators were far less common. Among the small proportion of cultivators, most of them were at or below the Core Formation Stage, and even Nascent Soul cultivators were quite rare.

Furthermore, all of these cultivators had concealed their auras so that they resembled mortals in the crowd.

Along this journey, Han Li had passed through quite a few cities of different sizes, but aside from Seaside City, the vast majority of those cities belonged to the nations of the mortal world.

Furthermore, it was an unspoken rule in these cities that cultivators had to conceal their auras and refrain from using their flight abilities, all to maintain the order of the mortal world.

The ones establishing these rules were naturally the immortal forces behind the authorities.

Of course, in some of the larger cities, there were some marketplaces that were set up exclusively for cultivators.

As the largest city in a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers, such marketplaces naturally existed in Moonview City as well.

These marketplaces were situated in the southeastern part of the city, and the concealment restrictions set up there were essentially non-existent to Han Li. He was able to directly enter the area, then made his way along a main street that was lined with shops to a tall pagoda constructed from giant white stone blocks.

The pagoda was several hundred feet tall, presenting a grand and majestic sight to behold, and it was giving off a bright white radiance under the light of the sun.

This was where the teleportation arrays of Moonview City were situated.

There was also a shimmering golden palace near the white pagoda, and that was the city's Immortal Outlet.

Han Li made his way directly into the pagoda, and the first thing that he saw on the first floor were five teleportation arrays, each of which was separated by no more than 1,000 feet from the other. The arrays were arranged around the hall in a circulation formation, and there was a golden-robed cultivator stationed beside each array.

The golden dragons embroidered onto their robes were a clear indication that all of them served the Immortal Palace.

Furthermore, there were also several cultivators standing beside each teleportation array, seemingly waiting for something.

Han Li only took a brief glance at his surroundings before making his way directly toward the teleportation array at the center of the hall.

Before Han Li had a chance to say anything, the golden-robed cultivator beside the array smiled as he said, "Please go and purchase a teleportation talisman from over there. Once we have enough people, the teleportation will commence."

Han Li turned to the direction that the golden-robed cultivator was pointing in to discover a long stone table, behind which sat a golden-robed elderly man, and there were several people lined up in front of the table.

The person at the very front of the line just so happened to be in the process of accepting a golden badge in exchange for a small pouch of spirit stones.

Han Li paused for a moment upon seeing this, then immediately turned and left the teleportation hall.

He made his way into a secluded little alley nearby, and by the time he re-emerged, he had already transformed into a middle-aged man with a yellow complexion. Upon his emergence, he strode into the Immortal Outlet before arriving in the room where immortal tokens were arranged.

"Tell me your name and place of origin," a bald elderly man instructed.

"My name is Li Yufei, and I'm from the Precious Jade Mountain Range," Han Li replied in a calm manner.

He had previously set off from Seaside City under the identity of Liu Shi, and there was a chance that someone could track him from Seaside City to Moonview City if he were to use the same identity again. Hence, it was best to switch to a different identity as a safety precaution.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li returned to the white pagoda, and it didn't take long before it was his turn to purchase a teleportation talisman.

The golden-robed elderly man took a glance at Han Li's new immortal token, then asked, "Where do you want to go?"

"Red Lake City," Han Li replied.

……

Thunderclap City was situated on the easternmost coastline of the Primordial Wave Continent, and going any further eastward of the city would take one into the vastly renowned Thunderstorm Sea.

This was a massive city, and due to its location, it was a natural gathering place for all high-grade cultivators who wanted to cross the Thunderstorm Sea to reach other continents.

Given its geographic advantage, it naturally stood to reason that Thunderclap City was an extremely prosperous place. It wasn't the most prosperous city on the entire Primordial Wave Continent, but it could definitely rank in the top five.

Due to its close proximity to the Thunderstorm Sea, the sky above the city was perpetually concealed behind a thick blanket of dark clouds, and occasional flashes of lightning could be seen within the clouds, followed by rumbling thunderclaps.

There was a massive tree planted every few kilometers in the city, and each tree was over 10,000 feet tall. These trees were all of a dark purple color, and their trunks and leaves were all riddled with lightning-shaped patterns.

All of these giant trees had extremely lush canopies that resembled massive purple umbrellas, and together, they were able to encompass the entire sky above the city.

These trees were called Urgent Lightning Trees, and they possessed the ability to absorb and store the power of lightning while being impervious to lightning strikes.

Fearsome thunderstorms took place all year round on the Thunderstorm Sea, and Thunderclap City was often affected due to its close proximity to the sea. If it weren't for the presence of these Urgent Lightning Trees, Thunderclap City would've most likely already been destroyed long ago.

Furthermore, these trees were also able to convert the power of lightning stored within them into light, and as a result, the city was constantly brightly lit regardless of whether it was daytime or nighttime.

At the center of the city was a giant purple pagoda, and around a dozen teleportation arrays were flashing incessantly on the pagoda's first floor as groups of people were teleported away from the city or arriving from other cities.

This first floor was extremely massive, with an area of several thousand feet, but even so, it was still quite crowded.

Right at this moment, around a dozen figures appeared on one of the teleportation arrays amid a flash of light, and one of them was none other than the yellow-skinned middle-aged man that Han Li had disguised himself as.

He followed the crowd out of the teleportation hall, and he couldn't help but heave a sigh of relief as he took in the wide street ahead of him.

After several months of traveling, he had finally gotten to the coastline, and once he crossed the Thunderstorm Sea, he would be able to reach the Ancient Cloud Continent, home of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Even with the canopies of the Urgent Lightning Trees up above, rumbling thunderclaps could still be occasionally heard.

However, most of the people on the streets displayed any reaction to this, and it was clear that they were already accustomed to this. Only those who were only visiting the city for the first time were still feeling disturbed by the frequent thunderclaps.

Han Li naturally wasn't going to be affected by these thunderclaps, but he didn't take a few extra glances at the collective canopies of the massive Urgent Lightning Trees up above.

Right at this moment, a youthful voice rang out beside him.

"I'm assuming this is your first time here in Thunderclap City. Is that correct, Senior?"

Han Li turned to discover an honest-looking young man not far away from him, extending a salute with a cupped fist.

Han Li didn't say anything, and the young man continued, "My name is Gu Sanming. This is quite a big city with many complex streets, so it can be rather inconvenient to get things done. If you want to buy something or find someplace, I can be of help to you, Senior."

"So you're a guide? I suppose it can't hurt to have one. Tell me this: what is the safest way to cross the Thunderstorm Sea?" Han Li asked.

The young man faltered slightly upon hearing this, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he asked, "Is there something wrong?"

Due to the fact that Han Li had concealed his aura, Gu Sanming was rather taken aback that someone of Han Li's cultivation base would be seeking to cross the Thunderstorm Sea. However, it then quickly occurred to him that Han Li was most likely concealing his cultivation base, and he hurriedly replied, "Not at all. If you want to cross the sea, then you've come to the right person, Senior.

“My cultivation base may be nothing remarkable, but I worked at the Black Feather Trading House a few years ago, and the Black Feather Trading House's Seafaring Lightning Boats are the safest mode of transformation to cross the Thunderstorm Sea. If I recall correctly, a Seafaring Lightning Boat is set to depart in less than three months from now, and there should still be some spots available."

"What is this Seafaring Lightning Boat?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Ah, please forgive me for not offering an explanation. This is your first time here in Thunderclap City, so there must be many things you're still unfamiliar with," the young man hurriedly said in an apologetic manner.

"It's fine. Seeing as you're so familiar with this matter, why don't you tell me about these Seafaring Lightning Boats? Give me as detailed a description as you can, and if your information is useful, I'll be sure to reward you," Han Li said.

On the way here, he had conducted some research into ways to cross the Thunderstorm Sea, and he had heard about how incredible these Seafaring Lightning Boats were. Now that he had arrived in Thunderclap City, this was the perfect chance to enquire more about this subject.

The Thunderstorm Sea was renowned for how perilous it was, so he naturally had to find the safest way to cross it.

"A Seafaring Lightning Boat is a type of special flying boat crafted specifically for the purpose of crossing the Thunderstorm Sea. Fearsome lightning storms that are comparable in destructive power to heavenly lightning tribulations frequently take place in the Thunderstorm Sea, and a normal flying boat would quickly be torn apart in such storms.

“However, Seafaring Lightning Boats are constructed from extremely lightning-resistant materials, and a layer of Urgent Lightning Tree membrane is applied to the outside. This is a special membrane made from the sap of the Urgent Lightning Tree, and even the most ferocious of thunderstorms won't be able to harm it in the slightest. Hence, Seafaring Lightning Boat can cross the Thunderstorm Sea with a very high degree of safety..."

"I see. How many spirit stones are required for a spot on one of these boats?" Han Li asked.

A slightly hesitant look appeared on the young man's face, and he was carefully gauging Han Li's reaction as he replied, "Given that they're the safest mode of transportation across the Thunderstorm Sea, the required fare is naturally quite steep, costing 500 top-grade spirit stones per person."

"I want to take a look at the boat," Han Li said in an expressionless manner.

The young man's heart began to pound in his chest upon hearing this, and he hurriedly replied, "Please come with me, Senior."

Even though he couldn't discern much from Han Li's reaction, if Han Li were to claim a spot on the boat, then he would receive a handsome reward from the trading house for the role that he played in guiding Han Li.

Chapter 176: Thunderstorm

Two months later.

In a pitch-black region of the Thunderstorm Sea, the seawater here was of a light purple color, and it stretched as far as the eyes could see.

Even without any wind, massive waves were still sweeping over the surface of the sea. At the moment, the wind was quite fierce, and that was only aiding in the formation of the waves.

The dark clouds in the sky were thick and dense and situated at an extremely low altitude, only six hundred to seven hundred feet above the surface of the sea.

It seemed that some of the taller waves surging over the sea were almost able to reach the clouds up above.

Thick bolts of lightning were occasionally flashing through the dark clouds, illuminating the sea down below amid rumbling thunderclaps, presenting a doomsday-like scene.

Right at this moment, yet another bolt of lightning pierced through the surface of the sea.

A massive shadow appeared beneath the dark clouds in the distance, and it was a giant boat that was hurtling rapidly through the air. The boat was several thousand feet long and over 100 feet tall.

It appeared to have been constructed from some type of wooden material, but this material somehow gave off a metallic appearance, and it was clearly extremely resolute and durable.

The surface of the boat was riddled with runes that were glowing with purple light, and it was also entirely covered in a thin translucent membrane.

Even though the giant purple boat was flying at as low an altitude as possible, it was still inevitably struck by some of the lightning that was crashing down from above.

However, despite how fearsome the bolts of lightning appeared, as soon as they struck that thin membrane on the giant boat, they were immediately repelled, leaving the boat completely unharmed.

The boat was divided up into a series of independent rooms, and each room had a window that allowed those staying inside to see what was outside.

Inside one of the rooms on the boat was a slightly chubby young man with a fair complexion, and he was looking out through the window at the giant bolts of lightning that were tearing through the heavens as he mused, "I'd always heard that the Thunderstorm Sea was an incredible place, and it's certainly living up to its reputation."

Behind him was a yellow-skinned middle-aged man who was seated with his legs crossed, and he was also looking out the window as he nodded in agreement. "Indeed, this is an extremely rare and spectacular sight to behold."

The yellow-skinned man was none other than Han Li, and the fair-skinned young man said in an excited manner, "I came from a mountainous region with a very dry climate, and we often go years without seeing any rain, so this is definitely a refreshing contrast."

Han Li merely smiled in response and remained silent.

The chubby young man's name was Sun Ke, and he was a Spatial Tempering cultivator. According to him, he was the young master of quite an affluent clan on the Primordial Wave Continent, and the two had met over a month ago.

At the time, Han Li had been staying in a secluded inn in Thunderclap City, waiting for the Seafaring Lightning Boat to set sail. However, on the night before the boat was scheduled to depart, Sun Ke was targeted in an assassination attempt while staying in the same inn.

Han Li didn't want to get involved in this matter, but the assassin was an overconfident Body Integration cultivator who planned to kill everyone in the entire inn in order to cover his tracks.

Unfortunately for him, he was slain by Han Li with ease.

Sun Ke was extremely grateful to Han Li for saving his life, and the two of them met once again the very next day on the port where the lightning boat was docked. Sun Ke was traveling to the Ancient Cloud Continent as well, and the two of them quickly became close acquaintances.

According to the Sun Ke, his assassin was an elder from his clan, and he had originally been instructed by the clan leader to protect him on his trip. However, he was bribed by Sun Ke's half-brother to have Sun Ke killed instead.

Thankfully, Sun Ke was able to discover his ploy in time, and he had several bodyguards who had been willing to sacrifice themselves in order to buy him time to escape. Only then was he able to flee all the way to Thunderclap City.

On the way here, he learned that some massive changes had taken place within his clan, and it was no longer a place that he could return to.

Hence, in order to completely distance himself from this mess, he decided to leave the Primordial Wave Continent altogether.

During their conversations, Han Li discovered that Sun Ke was a very knowledgeable person, and one of his hobbies was to learn about all types of general trivia and obscure historical events. Hence, he was quite happy to interact with and speak to Sun Ke as well.

After all, following his return to the Immortal Realm, he had spent a long time in the Black Wind Sea, which was quite an isolated place, so his knowledge of the rest of the immortal region was rather lacking.

Sun Ke was a wealth of knowledge, both important and trivial, and he really liked to impart his knowledge on others, but back in his clan, no one liked to hear him talk about these things. In contrast, Han Li was actively seeking out his knowledge and listening to everything that he said with keen attention, and that filled him with a sense of immense satisfaction. In addition to that, Han Li had saved his life, so over time, he naturally became very fond of Han Li.

"I've heard that the deeper one ventures into the Thunderstorm Sea, the more fearsome the lightning becomes. It hasn't been very long since we set off, yet the lightning outside is already this fearsome. Once we reach the deepest parts of the Thunderstorm Sea, the lightning there is said to be 10 times more powerful. Will this Seafaring Lightning Boat be able to handle that?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Rest assured, Brother Li. This Seafaring Lightning Boat is crafted from the wood of a 100,000-year-old Urgent Lightning Tree, and this type of wood is extremely lightning-resistant. On top of that, according to my observation, the sap used for the lightning membrane on the surface of the boat came from an Urgent Lightning Tree that was at least 200,000 years old, so there won't be any issues," Sun Ke declared in a confident manner.

"I didn't think that you would be so familiar with the construction of this Seafaring Lightning Boat," Han Li praised.

"You're far too kind, Brother Li. The Black Feather Trading House actually shares some very close ties with my clan. I wonder when I'll be able to return there," Sun Ke sighed as a slightly dejected look appeared on his face.

Han Li remained silent as he rose to his feet, then cast his gaze out the window.

Even through the restrictions on the boat, he could still sense the incredibly formidable lightning aura outside, and it was resonating slightly with his Lightning Bird bloodline.

This was a perilous place, but it was definitely also a fantastic location for those using lightning-attribute cultivation arts.

However, the lightning in the Thunderstorm Sea wasn't the only dangerous thing about it.

Ever since the boat entered the Thunderstorm Sea, Han Li had detected that the spatial pressure in the area had begun to increase sharply.

The Immortal Realm had an abundance of the world's origin qi, and the spatial pressure here was also immense, thereby severely limiting his speed of movement and the effective range of his spiritual sense.

To his surprise, the spatial pressure in the Thunderstorm Sea was several times more severe than in other places, and he couldn't help but wonder why this was the case.

"Brother Sun, I'm sure you can feel the spatial pressure here as well. Why is there such tremendous spatial pressure in this area?" he asked.

"I've tried to find an answer to that question myself in the past, but I'm afraid I wasn't able to find anything concrete. Some people say that this is the result of a battle between a pair of Dao Ancestors that took place here long ago, while others speculate that there's an enormous lightning beast concealed within the Thunderstorm Sea, but both of these are just unsubstantiated rumors," Sun Ke replied as he scratched his head in a slightly embarrassed manner.

"It's rare to see something that even you don't know the answer to," Han Li chuckled.

Initially, the scenery outside was extremely stunning to behold, but over time, it eventually grew stale, and Sun Ke quickly lost interest in the spectacle as he bade farewell to Han Li and returned to his own room.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to set up a restriction in the room, then summoned his Twin Starshift Plate before casting several incantation seals onto it, and the array plate immediately began to glow brightly.

A long while later, the light radiating from the array plate faded, and Han Li was left to look at the ball of egg-sized heavy water hovering above the palm of his hand with a wry smile on his face.

At this point in his journey, the Twin Starshift Plate's transmission ability had taken another severe hit, and even after such a long time, it was only able to transmit a tiny amount of heavy water to him.

He shook his head as he stowed the array plate and the ball of heavy water away, then flipped a hand over to produce a series of thick books that he began poring over.

The Thunderstorm Sea was extremely vast, and it would take at least two to three years to get to the other side.

Time flew by quickly, and over half a year passed by in the blink of an eye.

The lightning in the clouds was becoming more and more concentrated, indicating that the Seafaring Lightning Boat was gradually reaching the deepest parts of the Thunderstorm Sea.

Han Li was standing in front of his window, looking at the dark clouds outside. Thick bolts of lightning were regularly flashing through the clouds one after another, almost perpetually illuminating the sea with their radiance.

Most of the lightning was only raging in the clouds, and only a small proportion of them would actually come crashing down.

Due to how massive the boat was, it was regularly struck by lightning.

In this area, the bolts of lightning were far thicker and more powerful than before. Each time the boat was struck by a bolt of lightning, it would tremble while the lightning membrane on its surface rippled, but there was no sign of any damage being caused.

Han Li was staring at the lightning flashing outside through his window with deep focus and concentration in his eyes.

The lightning here appeared to be completely chaotic and haphazard, but it harbored some profound laws of nature, and watching the permutations in the lightning aided him in improving his mastery of lightning.

Right at this moment, the dark clouds up above suddenly began to churn like the surface of the sea down below, and the lightning in the clouds also began to surge violently, as if there were some gigantic objects crashing against one another inside.

Han Li was quite intrigued to see this, but he had already witnessed similar scenes many times on this journey, so he wasn't too surprised.

The Seafaring Lightning Boat began to glow with bright purple light as it immediately changed directions and fled into the distance.

The boat was extremely fast, but not as fast as the changes taking place in the clouds, and a massive vortex took shape in the blink of an eye.

All of the nearby lightning around the vortex was drawn toward it, converging into a dense clump of lightning that was so bright and concentrated that it forced any onlookers to avert their eyes.

A burst of terrifying rumbling rang out, and the boat accelerated to its top speed, attempting to fly out of the area encompassed under the vortex as quickly as possible.

In the next instant, the center of the massive vortex abruptly lit up, and countless thick bolts of lightning came crashing down onto the sea, encompassing an area with a radius of several thousand kilometers.

Each bolt of lightning resembled a massive tree, forming an enormous forest of lightning, causing the sea down below to churn and boil incessantly.

Thankfully, at this point, the Seafaring Lightning Boat had already just barely flown out of the area encompassed under the vortex, so it managed to avoid the forest of lightning.

Han Li's eyes were flashing with amazement as he watched the unfolding spectacle.

This was a renowned thunderstorm that the Thunderstorm Sea received its name from, and there were many types of thunderstorms, with this type of vortex thunderstorm being one of the more common types.

Chapter 177: Deep Sea Giant Clam

Aside from this lightning vortex, Han Li had also witnessed even more terrifying types of thunderstorms, such as the mist tide thunderstorm and the tornado thunderstorm.

However, just as Sun Ke said, the Seafaring Lightning Boat was extremely resolute, and it was able to weather the storms just fine.

The boat continued onward, covering a distance of several hundred kilometers in just a few seconds to leave the vortex in the clouds behind.

After releasing that forest of lightning, the vortex began to slowly vanish, starting from its outermost parts, and soon, all that remained was a black hole in the middle, and that was quickly about to disappear as well.

Han Li was just about to withdraw his gaze when he spotted a blurry shadow in the black hole out of his peripheral vision.

However, it was too far away, and there were still some remnants of lightning lingering in the air as visual disruption, so he wasn't able to see the shadow clearly.

Out of curiosity, he released his spiritual sense toward the black hole.

At this point, they were already deep in the Thunderstorm Sea, so the spatial pressure permeating throughout the area was extremely potent. As a result, even his spiritual sense was only able to extend to several hundred kilometers away at most, only just barely reaching the black hole.

All of a sudden, Han Li's expression changed drastically, and he almost jumped up in alarm.

Through his spiritual sense, he had detected that the shadow within the black hole was a gargantuan eye.

The eye was several thousand feet in size and orange in color. Inside the eye's giant pupil was a long and thin vertical vein that was flashing with a cold light.

This was already as far Han Li's spiritual sense could go, so he was unable to glean the full appearance of the owner of the eye.

However, judging from the size of the orange eye alone, it had to have been far more massive than any living being that Han Li had ever seen before.

Right at this moment, the orange eye seemed to have detected Han Li's spiritual sense, and it turned slightly to "look" in Han Li's direction.

A sense of foreboding immediately welled up in Han Li's heart, and he hurriedly tried to withdraw his spiritual sense, but it was already too late.

A terrifying aura swept toward him from afar, slamming into his soul like a heavy blow from a hammer.

He immediately threw up a large mouthful of blood, and his face turned deathly pale.

His soul began to tremble violently like a candle flame flickering in a gust of fierce wind, looking as if it could be snuffed out at any moment.

He hurriedly activated his Spirit Refinement Technique, and his spiritual sense transformed into countless translucent threads that enveloped his soul to stabilize it.

The translucent threads intertwined with one another to form a series of translucent chains that wrapped around his soul layer upon layer, and thankfully, that was enough to hold it together.

He opened his eyes before quickly devouring a few pills, then flipped a hand over to produce a small jade vial that was half-filled with a type of light purple liquid, which was giving off a peculiar aroma.

Han Li immediately tipped his head back and drank a large mouthful of the fluid.

This was a type of soul-nurturing spirit liquid that he had made from some Soulbirth Flower fluid left behind from his Earthly Deity Avatar refinement, and it was very effective for treating spiritual damage.

Thanks to the combination of the pills and the spirit liquid, his complexion was beginning to improve, and he took a deep breath before taking another glance outside.

The Seafaring Lightning Boat was traveling extremely quickly, and at this point, it had already completely departed from that area of the sea. The black hole in the clouds had also disappeared, having been concealed by other clouds.

However, Han Li didn't dare to let his guard down, and with a sweep of his sleeve, he released several hundred bursts of light in rapid succession, setting up one restriction after another throughout his room.

All of a sudden, a long black saber appeared in his hand amid a flash of light, and it was none other than the weapon that he had acquired from Fang Pan.

Through his examination, he had already verified that this saber was an Acquired Immortal Treasure of a decent caliber. It contained a type of extremely destructive law powers, and that was why it was able to slice through the defenses of Han Li's Giant Mountain Ape transformation.

However, up to this point, he hadn't been able to determine exactly which type of law powers it contained.

At the same time, several spirit treasures had also been summoned, circling around him in a wary fashion.

The Seafaring Lightning Boat continued onward, and soon, close to an hour had passed by without any further mishap.

Only at this point was Han Li finally convinced that the crisis had been averted, and he stowed the black saber and the spirit treasures away, but the surrounding restrictions remained.

He then sat down with his legs crossed, then closed his eyes as a layer of azure light appeared over his body.

Several days later, the azure light faded, and Han Li slowly exhaled as he reopened his eyes.

His complexion was already looking far better, and the spiritual damage that he had sustained was also close to halfway healed.

What on earth was that thing?

There was still a hint of lingering fear in Han Li's heart as he thought back to that giant eye.

Even though the contact had only been extremely brief, he was still able to clearly sense the insurmountable gap between himself and the owner of the giant eye. He felt like an ant staring into the eye of a giant, and just that single glance had almost been enough to destroy his soul.

He had heard from Sun Ke that that there were some extremely powerful lightning beasts that had the innate ability to control lightning residing in the Thunderstorm Sea, but according to Sun Ke, even the most formidable of those lightning beasts were only comparable in power to True Immortal cultivators, which was most definitely not the case of the owner of that giant eye.

With that in mind, he suddenly recalled something else that he had heard from Sun Ke, which was that it was speculated that the reason why there was such immense spiritual pressure in the Thunderstorm Sea was because there was a gargantuan beast residing deep within it.

Could it be that this rumor was true, and that the gargantuan beast in question was the owner of the eye?

Han Li only entertained this train of thought for a moment before shaking his head.

There was no point in considering such matters, and all he could do now was pray that he didn't encounter anything else that formidable.

Close to half a year later.

Inside a spacious room that was several hundred feet in size on the top floor of the Seafaring Lightning Boat, there were some tables and chairs, with each table separated by some elegant screens or bonsai trees.

It appeared that this was a restaurant, and the windows around the room were quite large, granting the patrons of the restaurant an exceptional view of the Thunderstorm Sea outside.

The journey to cross the entire Thunderstorm Sea was one that took several years, and it was quite boring to constantly stay in one's room all the time, so there were some amenities like restaurants and teahouses on the boat.

At this point, everyone on the boat had already become accustomed to the sights and scenes of the Thunderstorm Sea, and people had gradually begun visiting the restaurant as a form of relaxation.

At one of the tables sat Sun Ke and Han Li across from one another.

Sun Ke wore a bright smile as he filled his and Han Li's cups with the contents of an intricate dark red flagon in his hand.

"This is the renowned Red Crane Wine from my hometown, Brother Li. It's flavor is quite exquisite," Sun Ke said with a smile.

Han Li offered no response as he picked up the cup before taking a small sip.

Sun Ke was quite an avid drinker, and his storage treasures were filled with all types of delectable wines, but drinking alone was rather depressing, so he would often ask Han Li to drink with him.

After having some drinks, Sun Ke would often begin telling Han Li about some of the interesting stories pertaining to the Immortal Realm that he had seen from the books that he had read in the past, so Han Li was quite happy to drink with Sun Ke.

This Red Crane Wine was sweet and gentle, producing a slight heat in one's dantian following consumption. Han Li could tell that it would be quite beneficial to the cultivation of low and mid-grade cultivators, but its effects on him were quite minimal.

He held his cup as he cast his gaze outside.

Through the window, he could clearly see that the dark clouds had become even denser than before, and just the mere sight of the thick bolts of lightning tearing through the sky struck the beholder with a primordial fear.

The boat had already reached the very center of the Thunderstorm Sea, and the restrictions around the boat had been activated to their maximal capacity, while its speed had also decreased significantly.

"What a stunning place this is. It's a pity that I'm too weak to venture outside. Otherwise, I would be sure to explore this Thunderstorm Sea to my heart's content. According to writings left behind by some immortals, the Thunderstorm Sea is home to countless rare and precious lightning-attribute materials that are impossible to find anywhere else, and there are even supposed to be treasures that contain the power of lightning laws here," Sun Ke sighed as he also cast his gaze out the window.

"Risk and reward have always come hand in hand. The more perilous a place is, the greater the rewards that can often be reaped there," Han Li said.

"Indeed, Brother Li," Sun Ke chuckled as he filled Han Li's cup again.

Right at this moment, the dark clouds outside began to churn once again, and this time, the affected area was extremely massive. All of the lightning clouds stretching as far as the eyes could see were surging violently, as if the sky were about to collapse.

"Looks like another thunderstorm is coming," Sun Ke said with a hint of apprehension on his face.

Han Li rose to his feet and began making his way toward the entrance of the restaurant.

The restaurant was situated on the top floor of the Seafaring Lightning Boat, so whenever a thunderstorm took place, it would be struck by violent tremors, and that was why everyone had to vacate the restaurant during thunderstorms.

Countless bolts of lightning were flashing through the air like giant serpents, and every single one of them was several thousand feet in length.

Each bolt of lightning that struck the water down below would instantly cause the surface of the sea to explode.

"It's a wandering serpent thunderstorm!"

Everyone in the restaurant quickly departed to seek refuge in the lower levels of the boat.

The wandering serpent thunderstorm was the most formidable of all types of thunderstorms. In order to weather the storm, the Seafaring Lightning Boat had completely stopped in its tracks, darting from left to right as quickly as it could to avoid being struck by the enormous bolts of lightning.

"Well, this is rather depressing. I'm going back to my room for now, Brother Li," Sun Ke said with a slightly dejected expression, then made his way back to his room.

Han Li was watching the unfolding thunderstorm through the window beside him, and he was just about to retire to his room as well when he suddenly spotted something that caught his attention.

The surface of the sea roughly 200 to 300 kilometers away from the boat had suddenly begun to churn, and a giant vortex had appeared.

A round blue object that was several thousand feet in size emerged from within the vortex, revealing itself to be an enormous clam. The clam's blue shell was riddled with countless lightning-shaped patterns, and it was giving off an immense True Immortal Stage aura.

The giant clam shell slowly opened up, and two purple feelers that resembled elephant tusks emerged from within, while plumes of purple mist were billowing out of the holes at the center of the feelers' tips.

All of a sudden, a ball of purple light that was around the size of a human head shot out of the clam shell.

It was an object with thick arcs of purple lightning revolving around it, and the purple lightning was so bright that it was impossible to see what was inside, but it appeared to have been a ball of some sort.

As soon as this object appeared, all of the surrounding lightning immediately began to churn violently before converging toward the ball and surging into it.

After absorbing those bolts of lightning, the lightning radiating from the purple ball had become even brighter.

A string of strange sounds rang out from within the giant clam shell, and it seemed that the clam was roaring with excitement.

Han Li was rather intrigued by the sight of that purple ball.

His spiritual sense was only just barely able to reach the clam, but he could still clearly sense that the purple ball was giving off extremely potent law power fluctuations.

He didn't know if the ball was the clam's pearl, but it was definitely imbued with tremendous lightning law powers.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he quickly returned to his room, then released a series of array flags with a sweep of his sleeve to set up several restrictions.

After that, he flew out of his room as an invisible shadow.

Even though there were some restrictions around the boat, they naturally didn't affect him, and as soon as he left the boat, he immediately flipped a hand over to produce his High Zenith Invisibility Talisman, allowing him to bypass the restrictions with ease before flying toward the giant clam.

Chapter 178: Taking the Clam's Pearl

The violent thunderstorm showed no signs of abating anytime soon.

At the center of the vortex, the shell of the giant clam opened up slightly, releasing arcs of lightning to envelop the purple bead. The arcs of lighting intertwined to form a giant mouth of lightning that was greedily devouring the boundless power of lightning in the surrounding area.

It was clear that this formidable storm was providing the clam with the ideal cultivation conditions.

Right at this moment, a strange cry rang out from the distance.

It was an extremely loud cry that was audible even through the relentless chorus of booming thunderclaps.

The shell of the giant clam suddenly stirred slightly, and a speck of green light appeared within the darkness inside the shell. That seemed to have been the eye of the clam, and it had turned to the direction that the sound had come from.

Far away on the horizon, a black shadow had emerged and was rapidly approaching, appearing on the scene in the blink of an eye.

It was an enormous purple whale the size of an island, and its two massive eyes were gleaming with greed and yearning as it stared intently at the purple bead above the clam.

Furthermore, a tremendous aura that exceeded even the giant clam's was emanating from its body.

However, the clam didn't immediately withdraw its bead. Instead, its shell opened up even further, and two thick bolts of purple lightning erupted out from within, hurtling toward the whale like a pair of lightning dragons.

The space in the wake of the bolts of purple lightning shuddered violently as a charred smell wafted through the air, as if the very space itself had been scorched by the purple lightning.

A solemn look appeared in the giant whale's eyes at the sight of the oncoming bolts of lightning, and it opened its cavernous mouth to reveal a mouthful of massive white fangs before biting viciously down onto the purple lightning.

A layer of black electricity surfaced over its teeth as it brought its jaws shut in a forceful motion, biting the two bolts of lightning into halves.

A resounding thunderclap rang out, and the two bolts of purple lightning were quickly dispelled.

A black hole then appeared on the whale's back, and black light flashed within the hole, following which an inky-black bolt of lightning shot out from within, transforming into a black lightning wyrm that was several thousand feet in length in the blink of an eye. The lightning wyrm sprang through the air in a menacing fashion, reaching the giant clam in the blink of an eye.

The clam let loose a low roar as the purple ball above its head stopped devouring the lightning in the surrounding area, then appeared in front of it in a flash to clash against the oncoming black lightning wyrm.

An earth-shattering thunderclap rang out as the black lightning wyrm exploded into balls of lightning of different sizes, which instantly encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of close to 10 kilometers, swallowing up the giant clam in the process.

Bolts of dazzling black lightning flashed through the air as thunderclaps and explosions rang out in unison to produce an astounding commotion.

Right at this moment, the countless arcs of black lightning in the air suddenly converged toward a single spot, then vanished in the blink of an eye as if they had been devoured by something.

As a result, the giant clam was revealed once again, and it was completely unharmed.

At this moment, the purple ball in front of it was flashing with black lightning, and it was clear that it had just devoured the black lightning unleashed by the whale.

The massive whale let loose a roar of fury upon seeing this, and it whipped its giant tail forcefully through the air as arcs of black lightning surfaced over its entire body, following which it threw itself at the clam like a gargantuan cannon ball.

The clam wasn't backing down in the slightest, and arcs of purple lightning emerged over its shell as it threw itself at the whale as well.

A ferocious battle ensued between the two enormous creatures, further contributing to the commotion caused by the wandering serpent thunderstorm.

In the heat of battle, neither of the two beasts had noticed that there was a blurry humanoid figure standing less than 10 kilometers away from them. It was none other than Han Li, who had completely concealed his own aura.

Thanks to the effects of his High Zenith Invisibility Talisman, even if someone were standing right beside him, they wouldn't be able to detect his presence unless their spiritual sense was far superior to his.

At this moment, he was watching the fierce battle taking place before him with an unblinking gaze.

He could clearly sense the astonishing law fluctuations emanating from the purple ball, and there was a hint of yearning in his eyes.

If he weren't mistaken, the ball contained the power of lightning laws. He had previously seen some precious materials that contained law powers, but regardless of whether it was the eye of the Primordial Fei Beast, the Great Earth Fruits, or the Sea Condensing Crystal, none of them contained anywhere near the volume of law powers as what was in this ball.

The giant clam had most likely already spent countless millennia nurturing the ball.

Han Li took a deep breath to suppress his excitement, then continued to slowly close in on the pair of giant beasts while still in his invisible form.

He could sense that the clam and the whale were at the early-True Immortal Stage and the mid-True Immortal Stage, respectively. Of course, this was only relative to human cultivation standards. Given the exceptional immortal aptitude of these immortal spirit beasts, they often possessed far more immortal spiritual power than human cultivators of the same level, and that allowed them to hold their own against cultivators of a superior cultivation base.

Han Li didn't fear the prospect of facing them in battle, but he would rather avoid having to face them if possible.

Hence, at the moment, he was pondering how he could secure the purple ball before fleeing the scene without being forced into a confrontation.

Han Li continued to slowly approach the pair of giant creatures, and before long, he was no more than four kilometers away. However, he failed to notice the extremely faint purple mist permeating through the area around the giant clam, and he inadvertently came into contact with it.

As soon as this happened, the giant clam immediately swung around, and the speck of green light within its shell seemed to have suddenly turned to Han Li.

In the next instant, its shell opened up wide, and a thick bolt of purple lightning came crashing toward Han Li at an incredible speed.

Looks like my cover's been blown!

A cold look appeared on his face as arcs of silver lightning surfaced over his body, and he transformed into a bolt of silver lightning to evade the attack. He then appeared right in between the pair of giant beasts in the blink of an eye before grabbing onto the purple ball.

However, to his surprise, the ball was extraordinarily heavy despite the fact that it was only the size of a human head, and it refused to budge, even in the face of his enormous strength.

Both the clam and the whale flew into a thunderous rage upon seeing this, and they immediately joined forces to turn on Han Li.

Two bolts of purple lightning and one bolt of black lightning were sent hurtling toward Han Li in unison.

On top of that, a flurry of purple lightning began to spiral around the purple ball, striking Han Li's palm like a series of purple lightning blades.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly, but he displayed no intention of taking evasive measures.

He let loose a low roar as bright golden light appeared over his entire body, and he instantly took on his Giant Mountain Ape form. At the same time, countless golden scales appeared over his body and the palm of his hand.

The purple and black lightning struck the golden ape in unison, causing it to stumble in an unsteady manner.

The scales on the parts of its body that had been struck by the lightning had been broken to reveal the charred skin and flesh underneath, but the wounds weren't very deep.

Meanwhile, the purple blades of lightning around the purple ball had also sliced through the scales on the palm of his hand, causing him to bleed profusely.

The giant ape paid no heed to these injuries as it made a forceful grabbing motion to lock the purple ball firmly in its grasp, following which it shot back in retreat as quickly as it could.

At the same time, dazzling golden light erupted out of the palm of its hand to envelop the purple ball, attempting to forcibly sever its connection with the giant clam.

The purple ball began to struggle violently while flashing with purple lightning, illuminating the giant ape's hand into a semi-transparent purple color as it attempted to break free.

The giant clam roared with fury as it sprang out of the vortex on the surface of the sea, pouncing toward the golden ape like a living mountain.

After launching itself up into the air, its shell sprang open, and dazzling purple lightning appeared on its surface as countless bolts of lightning came crashing down from the dark clouds up above before converging onto its shell.

A burst of light surged over the shell, and all of the purple electricity transformed into a layer of dark purple light that struck the beholder with a sense of foreboding.

The clam shell then moved once again, and two crescent-shaped streaks of purple light were sent flying through the air, hurtling rapidly toward the golden ape while leaving ripples that were visible even to the naked eye in the space in its wake.

The lightning whale also pounced at the giant ape with a furious roar, and countless arcs of black lightning had already gathered together in its cavernous mouth.

Immediately thereafter, around a dozen massive balls of black lightning shot out of its mouth, hurtling rapidly toward the golden ape as well.

The giant ape's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this. It was already retreating at an incredible speed, but the attacks from the pair of lightning beasts were even faster, catching up to the giant ape in the blink of an eye.

However, the golden ape remained calm and collected as dazzling golden light erupted from its body, and several massive projections, including that of the Golden Dragon, the Five-colored Phoenix, the Lightning Bird, and the Azure Luan Bird had appeared behind it before instantly fusing into its body.

Immediately thereafter, the giant ape's body swelled drastically in size as it transformed into a devilish deity that was over 10,000 feet tall in the blink of an eye. Countless purplish-golden scales had appeared over its body, and it was giving off an almighty aura of destruction.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of its body, causing all of the oncoming purple lightning and balls of black lightning to stop cold in their tracks.

At the same time, bright purplish-golden light glowed from the hand of the devilish deity that was holding the purple ball, and a dull cracking sound rang out as the lightning around the purple ball was forcibly crushed, severing the connection between the ball and the giant clam.

The clam shuddered as a look of vicious resentment appeared in its eyes, and it let loose an enraged roar as around a dozen bolts of purple lightning were sent hurtling toward the devilish deity at once.

The devilish deity flipped a hand over to stow the purple ball away, and at the same time, the black saber that he had acquired from Fang Pan appeared in his hand.

A layer of dazzling black light appeared over the surface of the black saber, and all of the world's origin qi in the nearby space shuddered before beginning to surge into the saber, forming a massive vortex of energy.

The black saber immediately swelled drastically in size, transforming into a giant black blade that was over 1,000 feet in length.

Countless black runes appeared all over the surface of the saber, and rings of black light proliferated through the air in all directions, carrying powerful law fluctuations that caused the surrounding space to tremble and shudder.

A hint of surprise appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

The black saber had been quite formidable in Fang Pan's hands, but it definitely hadn't been this fearsome. Could it be that his Holy Nirvana Physique had better synergy with the power of laws contained in the black saber?

This thought only appeared in Han Li's mind for a moment before he refocused on the battle at hand, and the muscles on his arm bulged as he slashed the saber viciously through the air.

A resounding boom rang out as the black runes surged violently, and a crescent-shaped black saber projection that was several thousand feet in length was unleashed, clashing against the oncoming purple lightning and balls of black lightning.

The black saber projection was able to destroy the oncoming attacks with ease, and its power wasn't diminished in the slightest as it continued to sweep toward the pair of massive lightning beasts.

A tremendous burst of law powers came crashing down upon the two lightning beasts, and the space around them had abruptly turned as hard as a block of metal.

The pair of massive beasts immediately stopped cold in their tracks, seemingly quite wary of the oncoming attack.

The giant clam hurriedly closed its shell, and purple lightning flashed all around it, forming a massive ball of purple lightning that served as a protective barrier.

Meanwhile, the lightning whale let loose a thunderous roar as it released a millstone-sized black ball out of its mouth, and the ball was giving off an enormous aura with arcs of black lightning flashing around it.

As soon as the black ball emerged, it rapidly swelled to the size of a small mountain to shield the lightning whale behind it.

Chapter 179: Arriving on a New Continent

The crescent-shaped saber projection crashed into the bodies of the two lightning beasts, and a scintillating black sun instantly appeared out of thin air to envelop both creatures.

In the next instant, the black sun exploded violently amid an earth-shattering boom, causing the nearby space to twist and warp.

Rings of black shockwaves swept through the air in all directions, destroying everything in their path.

Only after a long while did these black shockwaves subside to reveal the giant clam and the lightning whale.

At this point, all of the purple lightning around the giant clam had already vanished, and a series of cracks had appeared on its shell, out of which blue blood was seeping out incessantly.

The lightning whale was in an even more sorry state. The black ball in front of it had reverted back to its original size, and its surface was riddled with cracks.

Furthermore, there were several huge wounds on the lightning whale's body that extended all the way from its head to its tail. The wounds weren't very deep, but the sea around it had still been stained red by its blood.

As for Han Li, he was already nowhere to be seen.

The giant clam's shell opened up slightly, revealing its glowing green eye, which was flashing erratically in alarm and fear.

Even though it had lost the prized object that it had been nurturing for countless millennia, it had managed to survive the attack, and it could always create another pearl given more time.

On the other side, the lightning whale opened its mouth to swallow the black ball, and its eyes were also filled with alarm and unease.

At the same time, the wandering serpent thunderstorm was slowly subsiding.

The pair of giant beasts exchanged a glance with one another, and they naturally had no intention of continuing their battle as they slowly descended into the depths and went their separate ways.

Meanwhile, the Seafaring Lightning Boat was already several thousand kilometers away, and Han Li abruptly reappeared in his room in a flash.

Only after setting up several more restrictions in his room did he sit down with his legs crossed. He then flipped a hand over to summon the black saber, and there was a hint of elation in his eyes.

During that battle, he had finally developed an understanding of the black saber's power. Even though its destructive power couldn't compare with that of the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword, he finally had a strong immortal treasure in his possession.

However, the saber still didn't truly feel like an extension of his body yet, and he would have to refine it for some time to achieve perfect synergy with the weapon.

With that in mind, he opened his mouth to release a ball of azure flames to envelop the saber, then devoured it into his belly.

After that, he flipped his hand over once again to produce the head-sized purple ball.

The ball wasn't perfectly spherical in shape. Instead, it was an ovular object that was as translucent as jade and dark purple in color.

At this moment, there wasn't even a single arc of lightning on its surface. Instead, it was giving off a purple glow, while faint law fluctuations were emanating from within.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he inspected the object. He had thought that this would be the giant clam's demon core, but upon closer inspection, he discovered that this didn't seem to have been the case.

It was said that demon beasts that reached the True Immortal Stage no longer had demon cores. Instead, they would manifest nascent souls, just like human cultivators.

Once they mastered the power of laws, they would mostly deposit those law powers in a certain part of their body. For example, the Primordial Fei Beast that Han Li had slain had deposited its power of time laws in its single eye.

However, there were also some True Immortal Stage demon beasts that focused the essence in their bodies around the power of laws that they had mastered to form a demon root.

Unlike demon cores, demon roots weren't vital to the survival of True Immortal Stage demon beasts. Instead, they were more like naturally occurring treasures, and every single one of them was extremely precious.

Han Li shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then cupped the ball in both hands and slowly injected his immortal spiritual power into it.

As a result, the purple light glowing from the ball brightened a little, but no further change was observed.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and after a moment of contemplation, he released some arcs of silver lightning into the purple ball.

The purple ball immediately began to glow brightly, and arcs of purple lightning that were as thick as a grown man's arm emerged over its surface amid a string of dull thunderclaps.

Arcs of purple lightning that were as thin as strands of spider silk had also appeared within the ball, and upon closer inspection, one would discover that they were formed by countless lightning runes, which were constantly changing forms while giving off formidable lightning law power fluctuations.

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he began scrutinizing the lightning runes within the purple ball intently, trying to glean the secrets of lightning laws through his observation.

Close to a year passed by in the blink of an eye.

At this moment, the purple ball was hovering in mid-air as it slowly revolved on the spot with arcs of purple lightning flashing all around it.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed beneath the purple ball, and he was observing all of the changes taking place in the ball through the use of his spiritual sense.

A long while later, he opened his eyes, then heaved a resigned sigh as he swept a sleeve through the air.

The purple lightning flashing over the surface of the ball instantly faded, following which it fell into his hand.

Even after observing the purple ball for close to a year, he was no closer at all to mastering the laws of lightning.

"Looks like I was too naïve," he murmured to himself with a wry smile.

The powers of laws were extremely profound, and no small degree of fortune was required to master such powers. Even though he had obtained a ball that contained the power of lightning laws, that was certainly no guarantee that he would definitely be able to master the laws of lightning.

Even though he was already prepared for such an outcome, he still couldn't help but feel a little disappointed.

Having said that, this hadn't been a completely fruitless endeavor.

Following this near-year-long stint of observation, he had developed a more thorough understanding of the power of lightning, and his proficiency in the control of lightning had also improved in subtle ways.

Han Li set the purple ball down beside him, then drew a ball of heavy water out of his True Water Pouch.

After that, he pointed a finger at the purple ball, and arcs of purple lightning emerged, fusing with the ball of heavy water at his behest.

As soon as the two made contact with one another, they immediately began to reject each other fiercely.

Han Li remained calm and collected upon seeing this, making a rapid series of hand seals to release a string of incantation seals that enveloped the purple lightning and heavy water from all directions, forcing the two to slowly combine and integrate with one another.

Three days later, Han Li was holding a fist-sized ball in his hand with some purple lightning patterns on its surface.

This was another ball of Heavy Water Veined Lightning, except this time, he had used the purple lightning from the purple ball.

Even though he hadn't tested it out, he could tell that it was definitely more formidable than the Heavy Water Veined Lightning he had refined using the power of the Lightning Bird.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to stow the ball of lightning away, following which he took a glance out the window.

After such a long journey, the Seafaring Lightning Boat had already left the central region of the Thunderstorm Sea, and the lightning flashing through the dark clouds in the sky had clearly become more sparse.

At this point, over half of the journey had already passed by, and he would be arriving on the Ancient Cloud Continent in just two or three more years.

This was a very encouraging thought for Han Li, and he drew another ball of heavy heavy water out of his True Water Pouch.

He had to make some extensive preparations prior to reaching the Ancient Cloud Continent.

……

Three years later.

There was a snow-covered cliff that was over 100,000 feet tall and shaped like an eagle's beak.

Atop the cliff stood a grand and imposing pass that was over 1,000 feet tall and constructed from some type of dark red stone material, and there was a golden plaque that carried the name "Eagle Beak Pass" hanging above the pass.

Beneath the cliff was a sea of white clouds that extended for tens of thousands of kilometers, with mountain summits poking through the clouds at intervals of several dozen kilometers. Those mountain summits resembled islands on a vast sea, and they appeared to have been quite tiny and insignificant, but in reality, all of them belonged to majestic mountains that were hundreds of thousands of feet tall.

These mountains belonged to the vastly renowned Crane Call Mountain Range of the Ancient Cloud Continent, and even though this was only a remote branch of the mountain range, it was still an exceptional visual spectacle.

It was very early in the morning, and the sun was only just beginning to rise, basking the entire sea of clouds in a warm, golden glow.

The clouds surged and churned in the face of the cold mountain wind, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

All of a sudden, what sounded like a string of cow moos rang out. The sound was very low and deep, but was also extremely penetrative and rang out across the entire sky.

At the same time, a gigantic creature was breaking through the vast expanse of golden clouds as it slowly flew toward the Eagle Beak Pass.

The creature was several thousand feet in size, and it resembled a dark green turtle. Its four massive flippers resembled a set of oars that were slowly moving through the clouds, propelling the enormous creature forward.

A three-story louchuan-like structure that exhibited exceptional craftsmanship had been constructed on the shell of the giant turtle, and it was complete with engraved golden and jade pillars, presenting a lavish sight to behold.

At this moment, there were several hundred people standing on the deck of the louchuan, most of whom were appreciating the scenery around them with relaxed and carefree expressions.

At the very front of the louchuan, situated closest to the turtle's head, was an azure-robed man with a medium build. He was holding onto the thick and sturdy dark wood railing in front of him as he cast his gaze toward the Eagle Beak Pass in the distance.

The man was none other than Han Li, who had traveled here from the Primordial Wave Continent.

After arriving at the Seafaring Lightning Boat, he had parted ways with Sun Ke, and the giant turtle that he was riding at this moment was a beast by the name of the Cloudfaring Turtle.

Despite their enormous size, these creatures had a very gentle and mild personality that made them easy to tame. At the same time, they had an enormous load capacity and were able to travel through the sky at extremely high altitudes, so they were often kept by large trading houses to serve as a mode of long-distance transportation.

Not all of the cities on the Ancient Cloud Continent had teleportation arrays, and having only just arrived on this new continent, Han Li was still yet to find his footing, so he decided to pay the fare to take the Cloudfaring Turtle. Along the way, he would be able to familiarize himself with the Ancient Cloud Continent.

The giant turtle let loose another long call as the edge of its shell made contact with the port of the Eagle Beak Pass, resulting in some slight tremors that quickly subsided.

Ushered by the manager of the Cloudfaring Turtle, all of the passengers began to make their way down a wooden ladder constructed along the slope of the turtle's shell to step onto the tall cliff.

Han Li followed the stream of disembarking passengers onto the cliff, and he couldn't help but look up at the imposing pass before him.

According to his map, he had officially reached the central region of the Ancient Cloud Continent.

Chapter 180: Detection

There were over 200 people who had disembarked here with Han Li, and the majority of them were humans, while the rest were beings from other races, and there were several mortals among those humans.

In reality, these people weren't actually just ordinary mortals. Instead, they focused solely on refinement of the physical body, much like the body refinement cultivators of the Spirit Realm.

Everyone made their way down the mountain path, and upon entering through the gate of the pass, they arrived in a spacious hall.

The hall was virtually completely empty with the exception of a sandalwood table that was around three feet in length situated in one corner of the hall. On the table sat an incense burner, out of which incense smoke was billowing out incessantly.

Through the thin veil of smoke, Han Li could see a purple-robed elderly man with white hair and a white beard sitting on a taishi chair behind the table. The elderly man's eyes were closed, and his head was bobbing back and forth slightly, making it impossible to tell whether he was meditating or taking a nap.

His aura indicated that he was a Grand Ascension cultivator, and right as Han Li was about to avert his gaze from the elderly man, the latter suddenly opened his eyes before fixing his gaze on Han Li.

At the same time, an elderly voice suddenly rang out in Han Li's heart.

"I won't ask why you've intentionally suppressed your cultivation base from the True Immortal Stage to the Body Integration Stage, but now that you've entered the territory of our Blaze Dragon Dao, you must follow the rules of our sect."

"Please enlighten me," Han Li replied through voice transmission.

He wasn't bothered by the slightly threatening tone of the elderly man's voice. The only thing that was rather perplexing to him was how the man had been able to glean his true cultivation base despite the fact that he was only a Grand Ascension cultivator.

"Rest assured, Senior, our Blaze Dragon Dao most definitely has the good grace to tolerate outsiders. However, as a True Immortal, you must remember at all times that you are not allowed to meddle in the affairs of the mortal world, and you certainly can't disrupt the order of the mortal world and kill mortals for no good reason," the purple-robed elderly man elaborated.

"Thank you for informing me of this. Those rules sound very reasonable," Han Li replied.

Seeing as Han Li was willing to comply, the tone of the purple-robed elderly man's voice instantly became more polite as he said, "In that case, I wish you a smooth and fruitful journey, Senior."

Han Li gave the elderly man a slight nod, then turned to follow everyone to the gate on the other side of the hall.

Outside the gate was a huge white plaza, where there were many beast-drawn carriages, some of which could gallop through the mountains, while others could soar through the heavens, and they were mostly catering toward the mortal body refinement cultivators.

On the mountains further away were layers of white forest that resembled jade belts, reflecting the light of the sun.

As soon as he arrived on the Ancient Cloud Continent, Han Li clearly noticed that the temperature here was far lower than anywhere else on the Primordial Wave Continent, and the climate was also more humid.

He paused momentarily to collect his bearings, then flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

Inside the jade slip was the tracking map that he had exchanged for from the Transient Guild, and even though only a portion of the landscape had appeared on the map, it was far more detailed than when he checked it back in the Black Wind Sea.

There was also another clear point of difference compared with before, which was that an extremely eye-catching red line had appeared on the map. The starting point of the red line was the Eagle Beak Pass, and it stretched all the way to a place by the name of White Kite City in the northeast.

According to the map, White Kite City was situated in the Hundred Blessings Nation, which was quite far away from the Eagle Beak Pass.

As a safety precaution, he was planning to travel at a speed appropriate for a Body Integration cultivator, so the journey was going to take him around half a month.

In contrast with the Primordial Wave Continent, the Ancient Cloud Continent had a far greater abundance of world's origin qi and spirit veins. Hence, there were also far more immortal sects here than on the Primordial Wave Continent, thereby naturally making it a more dangerous place as well.

After taking a moment to ascertain the right direction, Han Li stowed the jade slip away, then flew up into the sky as a streak of azure light.

Seven or eight days passed by in a flash, yet as Han Li was passing over a snow-covered forest, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he drew to an abrupt halt.

Just now, he had detected the auras of Daoist Xie and his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

However, it was clear that both of them were still extremely far away, and he wouldn't have been able to notice them at all had it not been for his tremendous spiritual sense.

After a brief hesitation, he quickly inspected his surroundings, then flew directly down toward a snow-covered valley.

After descending into the valley, Han Li began to skip rapidly along the ground like an agile gazelle, ultimately coming to a halt on a very flat and level rock deep in the valley.

With a casual sweep of his sleeve, all of the snow that had accumulated on the rock was cleared, and he sat down with his legs crossed, then closed his eyes and began making a series of hand seals while chanting an incantation.

His consciousness began to churn as a subtle spiritual connection began to travel through the air like a winding thread, searching for Daoist Xie and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords based on the faint connection that he had detected earlier.

However, right as the spiritual connection was gradually beginning to become clearer, the spiritual thread that was wandering through the air was suddenly cut off. Even the original connection that he had felt had faded, as if someone had cut him off.

His brows furrowed slightly as he switched to a different hand seal and fully activated his spiritual sense, trying to recapture that connection, but moments later, he reopened his eyes with a resigned expression, then sighed to himself, "Looks like it won't be so easy to recover what I've lost."

Han Li was feeling a little disappointed in the wake of all of this, and he sat in silence in the peaceful valley for a while to collect his thoughts, then continued on his journey to Whit Kite City.

Three days later.

A streak of azure light descended out of the sky outside a white city that was situated at an intersection point between a pair of rivers.

The streak of azure light then faded to reveal a tall and imposing man with a prominent forehead and a thick beard. The man's appearance was quite rugged, presenting a bit of a mismatch with his bright and piercing eyes.

The man was none other than Han Li in disguise.

Prior to entering the city, he used his mask from the Transient Guild to adopt yet another disguise, and this time, he concealed his own aura completely, posing as a mortal as he made his way into the city.

There was no snowfall near White Kite City, but it was still quite cold. There weren't many people passing through the city gates, and most of them were wearing thick cotton-padded clothes.

There was a group of cultivators situated on either side of the city gates, but most of them were only at the Foundation Establishment Stage, and they were there more so to maintain order than to examine the people entering the city.

Initially, Han Li felt this to be rather strange, but he quickly came to realize that White Kite City was only a small rural city in the Hundred Blessings Nation, and the vast majority of its residents were mortals, thereby explaining the rather lax security measures.

After entering the city, Han Li checked the map in the jade slip once again, and this time, the annotations had become even more detailed, pointing him toward a restaurant in the eastern part of the city.

Han Li made his way through the city streets in accordance with the path stipulated on the map, and he spotted the restaurant that he was looking for in a rather understated alley.

As soon as he arrived at the entrance of the restaurant, he was immediately greeted by the strong odor of fermented spirits. Perhaps it was because the memory was from too long ago, but the smell was different from what he recalled it to be like.

Back when he was a child, whenever Uncle Zhang came to visit, he would always bring some home-brewed wine to share with Han Li's father over their crude meal.

At the time, Han Li had been quite young, so he had never drunk the wine, but he recalled finding its aroma very sharp on the nose.

Han Li was momentarily dazed as these distant memories flooded into his mind, but he then shook his head in a self-deprecating manner before making his way into the restaurant.

According to the habits of the mortal world, it was already past lunchtime but not yet time for dinner. In addition to that, the alley was quite secluded, and as a result, most of the tables and chairs in the restaurant were empty, with the only exceptions being one table that was occupied by two men who were having some wine with some salted peanuts.

As soon as Han Li entered the restaurant, a waiter with a hand towel draped over his shoulder immediately approached him with a warm smile.

However, before the waiter had a chance to say anything, someone grabbed onto his shoulder and tugged him aside.

A portly middle-aged man then stepped around the waiter with a smile as he said, "This is an acquaintance of mine, so I'll attend to him in person."

As the portly manager led Han Li up to the second floor, the waiter scratched his head as he murmured to himself, "An acquaintance? How come I don't recall ever seeing him before?"

However, he didn't ponder the matter any further as he stretched lazily, then sat down onto a chair, slacking off on the job.

Han Li followed the portly manager up the creaky wooden staircase to the second floor, where he was then led into a booth at the end of the corridor.

Upon entering the booth, the portly manager stepped aside to allow Han Li to enter the room as well, following which he closed the door.

After that, he swept a hand through the air, and a layer of faint light appeared over the walls of the room, producing a soundproof barrier.

"Please take a seat, Fellow Daoist."

The portly manager made an inviting hand gesture as he spoke, and the smile on his face gradually faded.

Han Li sat down and swept his gaze around the room to find that the surrounding concealment array wasn't of a particularly high standard. If a cultivator of his caliber wanted to see what was happening in the room, then he would be able to do so from kilometers away.

However, the restaurant was quite secluded in location, and that allowed it to avoid unwanted attention and prying eyes.

The portly manager sat down across from Han Li, then asked, "I'm assuming you have the token, right, Fellow Daoist? Would you be able to bring it out to show me?"

Han Li wasted no time as he flipped a hand over to produce the jade slip that contained the missions debriefing and the tracking map, then slid it across the table toward the portly manager.

The latter picked up the jade slip before inspecting its contents for a moment with his eyes closed, then nodded as he said, "This is the right token. Looks like you are indeed a fellow daoist of the Transient Guild."

Chapter 181: Heavenly Devil Possession

"Now that you've verified the authenticity of my token, I believe it's time that you told me exactly what needs to be done for this mission," Han Li said in a direct and straightforward manner.

"Before that, there's one more thing that I must examine before I decide whether I'm going to entrust this mission to you," the portly manager said.

"What is it?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I need to examine your cultivation base to see if you truly possess the ability to complete the mission," the portly manager said.

Han Li didn't suppress his aura any longer upon hearing this, releasing his early-True Immortal Stage aura in a completely unconcealed form.

Even though he had only released a hint of his aura, the portly manager still swayed unsteadily as an unnatural flush appeared on his face, and he appeared to have been struggling to breathe.

Han Li hurriedly withdrew his aura upon seeing this, and a hint of befuddlement flashed through his eyes.

The portly manager's appearance was clearly also a disguise manifested by a mask from the Transient Guild, and it had concealed his aura as well, so even with Han Li's immense spiritual sense, he was unable to glean the man's cultivation base.

He had only released a tiny hint of his aura, so he was rather taken aback by the strong reaction displayed by the portly manager.

The portly manager's complexion was still a little pale, but some color had returned to his cheeks after a few deep breaths, and he asked, "If I'm not mistaken, you're an early-True Immortal cultivator, right, Fellow Daoist?"

Han Li merely nodded in response.

A hint of disappointment flashed through the portly manager's face as he sighed, "In that case, I advise you not to take on this mission."

"Why is that?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression. "The mission description stated that any True Immortal cultivator could take on the mission, "

"To tell you the truth, the mission that I released will require you to kill someone. According to my knowledge, that person is also at the True Immortal Stage, but he possesses certain powers that make him far more formidable than other cultivators of the same caliber. I'm concerned that you'll be no match for him and end up losing your life here," the portly manager explained with a shake of his head.

"If it's another early-True Immortal cultivator, then I'm fairly confident that I can take him on. Even if I can't defeat him, I'll definitely be able to at least ensure that I'll survive the encounter, so rest assured and give me the mission debriefing, Fellow Daoist. I've already made up my mind, and I'm not going to back down," Han Li insisted with a smile

The portly manager could see that Han Li was quite determined, so he could only comply with Han Li's request.

"Alright. The person that I want to kill is a man by the name of Bai Songshi, and he currently serves as the imperial preceptor of the Hundred Blessings Nation. If you can kill him, then you'll receive the promised reward."

Han Li was rather taken aback by this request, and he asked, "You want me to kill the imperial preceptor of a mortal nation? Aren't cultivators prohibited from meddlings in the affairs of the mortal world while in the territory of the Blaze Dragon Dao? Also, if that man really is a True Immortal cultivator, then how did he end up becoming the imperial preceptor of a mortal nation?"

Instead of answering Han Li's question, the portly manager raised one of his own. "I'm assuming you're not from our Ancient Cloud Continent, right, Fellow Daoist?"

"That's right," Han Li admitted in a forthright manner.

"That explains it. The thing is that there are trillions of mortals on the Ancient Cloud Continent, and as a result, there are millions of mortal nations. Some nations like the Hundred Blessings Nation appear to be run by the mortal imperial family on the surface, but in reality, they're being presided over by one or two cultivating clans in the shadows. They are the ones pulling the strings behind the scenes," the portly manager explained.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he asked, "So what you're saying is that the clan that Bai Songshi belongs to is the actual ruler of the Hundred Blessings Nation?"

"That's right. These cultivating clans are supported by some powerful cultivating sects as well, but due to certain unspoken rules, unless a nation is facing complete annihilation, these cultivating clans generally won't interfere with the nation's affairs. Hence, the mortals residing in those nations don't feel the influence of these cultivating clans at all," the portly manager explained.

"In that case, if I kill Bai Songshi, won't I be making an enemy out of his clan and the cultivating sects that support his clan? In fact, wouldn't that make me a target of the Blaze Dragon Dao as well?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"You can rest assured on that front, Fellow Daoist. The man that I'm asking you to kill is not the true Bai Songshi," the portly manager replied with a wave of his hand.

Han Li was becoming more befuddled by the second, and he was just about to ask what all of this meant when the portly manager continued, "The one that I want you to kill is actually an Extrarealm Heavenly Devil. While transcending his ascension tribulation, the true Bai Songshi was possessed by that heavenly devil.

“In order to avoid attracting attention to itself, the heavenly devil has been suppressing its cultivation base to the Grand Ascension Stage this entire time, even though it's actual cultivation base is at the early-True Immortal Stage..."

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he interjected, "That makes sense, but I have one question: if a heavenly devil really did possess Bai Songshi's body, they would've been sure to act in a secretive manner to avoid attention, so how do you know so much about all of this?"

A hesitant look appeared on the portly manager's face, and it seemed that he was unsure of how to respond.

"What you've just described to me is truly rather bewildering. If you're unable or unwilling to explain the situation to me in further detail, then I'm afraid I can't believe you," Han Li said.

The portly manager lowered his head and fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

Han Li also fell silent and waited patiently for a response.

After a long silence, the portly manager slowly raised his head, and there was a determined look in his eyes, indicating that he had just arrived at an important decision.

He raised his hands and placed them on his cheeks, then made a gentle lifting motion, and an azure rabbit mask that was riddled with spirit patterns was removed amid a flash of rippling azure light.

As soon as the mask was removed, azure light surged over the portly manager's entire body, and he began to rapidly shrink, while his waist was also quickly compressing.

It didn't take long for the portly manager to completely disappear, replaced by a young woman who appeared to have been around 17 to 18 years of age.

The woman had a pair of almond eyes and thin lips, coupled with a pair of fine eyebrows and a delicate nose. There was still some baby fat lingering on her cheeks, and she was wearing a tight-fitting pink lotus flower dress, giving her a gorgeous and refreshing appearance.

However, there was a slight wrinkle between her brows, striking the beholder with a hint of sympathy.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he finally understood why the woman had displayed such a strong reaction to the release of his aura from earlier.

As it turned out, she was only a Deity Transformation cultivator, and upon detecting this, Han Li couldn't help but wonder how someone of such a lowly cultivation base had managed to join the Transient Guild.

However, after some closer inspection, he noticed that there seemed to be something out of the ordinary about the woman, but he couldn't pinpoint exactly what was different about her.

"I'm sure you're aware that members of the Transient Guild are prohibited from enquiring about the true identities of other members, so the fact that I'm revealing my true appearance to you should be a sufficient show of my sincerity, right, Fellow Daoist?" the young woman asked, and her voice was very pleasant on the ears.

Despite the fact that she was facing a True Immortal whose cultivation base far exceeded hers, she remained quite calm and collected.

Han Li remained unmoved by this gesture, and he said, "Please answer my question from earlier."

The young woman took a deep breath, then said, "To tell you the truth, my name is Bai Suyuan, and I am the granddaughter of Bai Songshi. At the time..."

Thanks to her description of the events that unfolded at the time, Han Li was able to get a rough grasp on the timeline.

As it turned out, Bai Suyuna's parents had unfortunately passed away during an outing when she was still at a very young age. Due to her cleverness and her exceptional cultivation aptitude, Bai Songshi was very fond of Bai Suyuan and always kept her by his side, constantly showering her with doting affection.

During Bai Songshi's ascension tribulation, he was possessed by an Extrarealm Heavenly Devil, but no one was able to tell. She was the first one to have noticed, but no one in her clan believed her when she told them, not even her own grandfather.

In the beginning, the heavenly devil was quite restrained and didn't step out of line. However, once it had completely integrated itself with Bai Songshi's memories, it gradually began to control the entire Bai Clan, then set his sights on the Hundred Blessings Nation's imperial court, aiming to seize more power with his status as imperial preceptor.

After that, strange happenings began to occur frequently in the Hundred Blessings Nation, with entire cities or towns of people disappearing overnight. As the cultivating power presiding over the Hundred Blessings Nation, the Bai Clan had naturally sent people to investigate these strange occurrences, but all to no avail.

"Eventually, the heavenly devil's behavior became more and more brazen, and some of the members of my clan finally caught on to the fact that something was wrong, so they began to investigate the matter, but they were all taken out by the heavenly devil before they could uncover the truth.

“My cultivation aptitude caught the heavenly devil's eye, and it wanted to develop me into a cultivation cauldron, so it had me imprisoned in a restricted area in our clan, and my grandfather was killed by the heavenly devil while rescuing me."

Bai Suyuan's voice trailed off here, and a hint of pain and grief flashed through her eyes.

"My condolences, Fellow Daoist Bai," Han Li consoled.

Bai Suyuan was silent for a moment longer, then continued, "After my grandfather rescued me, he entrusted me with this mask and the token of our ancestor, both of which had been passed down for generations in our clan.

“He told me to take this token to the Blaze Dragon Dao and cultivate there until I attained the power to avenge our clan, but I'm only at the Deity Transformation Stage, who knows how long it'll take before I can contend against that heavenly devil?"

"So that's why you released this mission in the Transient Guild to find someone to help you kill him?" Han Li asked.

Han Li could understand why Bai Suyuan was so disheartened. For a Deity Transformation cultivator, even the Spatial Tempering Stage would've seemed impossibly far away, let alone the True Immortal Stage. Having progressed arduously through the ranks himself, Han Li knew just how difficult and perilous this process could be.

At this point, Bai Suyuan had already regained her composure, and she replied, "That's right. I discovered the existence of the Transient Guild by chance through this mask, and I decided to release this mission.

“The heavenly devil has been constantly searching for me ever since I escaped, and it was only thanks to this mask that I've been able to avoid capture all this time. If I don't find someone to kill that heavenly devil, then I'm afraid I won't be able to get away from it for much longer."

Chapter 182: Heavenly Worship

"I see. Your explanation makes sense, but why is it that you were able to join the Transient Guild with your cultivation base. Also, you mentioned that this mask and the token were passed down for generations in your clan, is that right?"

"This mask originally belonged to an ancestor of our Bai Clan, the same one who once served as an inner sect elder of the Blaze Dragon Dao. He was also the reason why our Bai Clan was able to become the immortal clan controlling the Hundred Blessings Nation from the shadows. As for the token, that belonged to him as well," Bai Suyuan explained.

"In that case, why didn't you go to the Blaze Dragon Dao to search for that ancestor of yours and get him to help you slay the heavenly devil?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"According to my grandfather, that ancestor of ours suddenly disappeared without a trace several thousand years ago. Several Body Integration Stage elders of our clan had been sent out to search for him, but all of them disappeared as well.

“As a result, our Bai Clan gradually fell into decline, and it was exactly because of this that my great-grandfather prematurely attempted a breakthrough to the True Immortal Stage, ultimately resulting in him being possessed by that heavenly devil," Bai Suyuan sighed.

Han Li contemplated Bai Suyuan's story for a moment, then said, "There's nothing that can back up your claims at the moment. I have to see Bai Songshi for myself to verify whether he's actually been possessed by a heavenly devil before I decide if I want to carry out the mission."

At the moment, he still didn't completely trust Bai Suyuan.

In his eyes, the fact that a late-Deity Transformation cultivator like her was able to escape from a True Immortal for all these years was a clear indication that there was more to her than met the eye, so he was naturally slightly wary of her.

Bai Suyuan hesitated momentarily, then said, "I suppose that's reasonable. The Hundred Blessings Nation's decennial heavenly worship ceremony is being held early next month. The emperor and all of his officials will be in attendance, and they'll be traveling collectively to the Grand Loft Mountain for the ceremony.

“Bai Songshi will naturally be among them as well, and that would be the best opportunity to strike as the Grand Loft Mountain is far away from all mortal cities."

Han Li nodded in response, expressing his silent approval of this plan.

Bai Suyuan's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and she said, "By the way, I still don't know your name, Fellow Daoist."

"My name is Li Feiyu."

……

The Grand Loft Mountain Range situated in the eastern region of the Hundred Blessings Nation had always been renowned for its beauty and majesty, and the Grand Loft Mountain in the mountain range was the tallest mountain in the entire nation. It had always been known as the Eastern Divine Mountain, and it held an extremely lofty position in the hearts of all of the nation's citizens. It was said that a True Immortal had once ascended from that very mountain.

The scholars and poets of the Hundred Blessings Nation had also always taken pride in scaling the Grand Loft Mountain and dedicating poems and odes to the majestic mountain. Even to this day, the mountain was still riddled with poems that had been engraved onto the rock faces, attracting many tourists every year to see those poems for themselves.

However, starting from a month ago, the entirety of the Grand Loft Mountain had been surrounded by large numbers of armored soldiers, completely sealing it off to everyone, regardless of whether they were common folk or nobility.

No one in the Hundred Blessings Nation had any complaints about this as they knew that the heavenly worship ceremony was about to commence.

Even though the mountain had been sealed off, countless people had gathered at the foot of the mountain from the nearby counties in the days leading up to the ceremony.

On the day of the official ceremony, even before first light had arrived, the official road leading up to the Grand Loft Mountain was already lined with people wanting to witness the emperor in person.

As soon as the designated hour arrived, the carriages of the emperor and the officials made their way out of the imperial palace, traveling toward the Grand Loft Mountain while escorted by the imperial guard.

On the summit of the Grand Loft Mountain was a large round altar, atop which stood a table and an incense burner. There was a damask red carpet draped over the ground, while many officials in ceremonial robes were gathered around the altars, waiting with their hands clasped in front of them and reverent looks on their faces.

Among them was an ordinary-looking middle-aged official whose eyes were constantly darting around, inspecting his surroundings.

This person was none other than Han Li, who had managed to sneak into the ranks of the officials, while Bai Suyuan had concealed herself outside of the altar.

After some observation, Han Li discovered that aside from the dozen or so Nascent Soul and Foundation Establishment cultivators among the patrolling soldiers present on the mountain summit, the high official of the Ministry of Rites standing beside him was also a Deity Transformation cultivator.

Han Li knew that these people had most likely been planted into the imperial court by the Bai Clan in secret.

After waiting for a few hours, the emperor's carriage finally arrived on the summit of the Grand Loft Mountain, followed by a procession of other carriages.

The emperor appeared to have only been around 20 years of age, and he was helped down from his carriage by a eunuch. However, instead of immediately making his way to the altar, he stopped beside his carriage, seemingly waiting for something.

Moments later, the carriages behind him also arrived on the mountain summit one after another, and the door of the carriage immediately following the emperor's swung open.

There was a white-haired elderly man in a purple robe inside, and he reached out a hand before making his way out of the carriage in a shaky manner, assisted by a couple of servants.

The man had an extremely geriatric appearance. He had a pair of murky eyes, and his face was riddled with wrinkles. There were several stray strands of white hair drifting in front of his forehead, and his body was severely hunched over. It seemed that even a slightly strong breeze would be able to knock him down.

A faint smile appeared on the emperor's face as he slowly made his way to the elderly man's side, then accompanied him toward the altar, followed quickly by all of the other officials.

Standing among the crowd, a hint of barely detectable blue light flashed through Han Li's eyes as his gaze swept over the elderly man, and just that single glance alone was enough for him to tell him that this man was the imperial preceptor, Bai Songshi.

Bai Songshi was putting on the façade of a frail old man, and he had done a very good job of concealing his own aura, but he was naturally unable to fool Han Li's spiritual sense, and on the surface, he didn't indeed appear to have been a Grand Ascension cultivator.

Aside from the fact that he was intentionally suppressing his own aura and cultivation base, Han Li didn't find anything else worthy of note about him.

The emperor and Bai Songshi slowly made their way up the staircase toward the altar, while the other officials stopped at the foot of the altar.

While passing by Han Li and the other officials, Bai Songshi's footsteps faltered ever so slightly, and he took what appeared to have been a casual glance in a certain direction outside of the altar out of the corner of his eye. A faint gleam flashed through his murky eyes, but it was gone in an instant, and he continued to make his way toward the center of the altar as if nothing had happened.

The ceremony commenced under the watchful eye of a high-ranking official from the Ministry of Rites, while Han Li was silently contemplating how to proceed.

Right at this moment, Bai Suyuan's voice suddenly rang out in his mind, and she was sounding a little frantic. "Fellow Daoist Li, why have you still not done anything? I'm sure that heavenly devil has already discovered me at this point. Have you been fooled by that heavenly devil's façade?"

Han Li lowered his head to look down at his own shadow, then asked internally, "Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, can you take a look at that man for me?"

A brief moment later, Mo Guang's voice rang out in his mind. "He's done a fair good job of disguising himself, but as far as I can tell, he is indeed an Extrarealm Heavenly Devil."

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

At this point, the emperor had already offered up his three customary sticks of incense to the altar and had returned to the side of his carriage.

Meanwhile, as the head of all of the imperial court's officials, Bai Songshi had been tasked with reciting the heavenly worship oration on the emperor's behalf. His voice was hoarse and strained, and he really did sound like an old man who was struggling just to speak.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly strode forward and emerged from the crowd.

The officials of the Ministry of Rites around him were stunned by this insolent gesture, and they hurriedly called out to stop him, but before they could do anything, he had already vanished on the spot.

In the next instant, he appeared at the center of the altar, and with a sweep of his sleeve, a gust of fierce azure wind was released, sweeping up all of the officials, including the emperor, before carrying them down to the foot of the mountain.

The cultivators concealed among the mortals were trying to break out of the gust of azure wind with all their might, but they were completely powerless to do so and could only look on helplessly as they were carried down the mountain.

Bai Songshi ceased his chanting as he turned to face Han Li. "So you're the one that the girl has sought out to kill me?"

At the same time, his murky eyes instantly became incredibly clear, and his hunched back had also become ramrod straight. He smoothed down the strands of stray hair in front of his forehead, and all of his geriatric frailty had vanished in an instant, replaced by a powerful and domineering aura.

Han Li offered no response as a cold smile appeared on his face, and he launched himself forward as he threw a punch directly at Bai Songshi's head.

Bai Songshi's eyelids twitched slightly as he detected the immense aura that had erupted out of Han Li's body, and he immediately shot back several hundred feet in retreat.

As a result, Han Li's fist missed its target and struck the altar instead.

A resounding boom rang out as the entire altar was destroyed, reduced to a pile of rubble and dust.

Around a dozen streaks of light appeared around Han Li one after another, each of which contained a cultivator who was glowering at Han Li with furious expressions.

An azure-robed elderly man stabbed a finger in Han Li's direction as he yelled, "How dare you attack our patriarch, you insolent cur!"

After that initial punch, Han Li didn't unleash any further attacks. Instead, he merely observed Bai Songshi from afar while ignoring everyone around him.

The cultivators that had surrounded him were all from the Bai Clan, and even the most powerful one among them was only at the late-Deity Transformation Stage, so he naturally wasn't going to target them.

Right at this moment, a slender figure shot forth from afar before descending onto the destroyed altar, revealing herself to be none other than Bai Suyuan.

"Stop! This is Senior Li, a cultivator that I implored to come and eradicate this heavenly devil. Don't be fooled by that devilish creature!" Bai Suyuan yelled in a frantic voice.

The azure-robed elderly man erupted into a fit of fury as he rushed directly toward Bai Suyuan. "Silence, you foul wench! Not only have you killed your grandfather, you're now slandering the head of our clan! You are the only devilish creature here!"

Han Li could see what was happening out of the corner of his eye, but he paid that no heed as he made his way toward Bai Songshi.

Chapter 183: Slaying the Devil

A cold look appeared in Bai Songshi's eyes at the sight of the approaching Han Li, and he swept his sleeves through the air to release a pair of giant fiery wheels that were enveloped in five-colored light and burning with five-colored spirit flames.

This was a pair of spirit treasures of quite a high caliber, but Han Li remained completely unfazed as he chuckled coldly, "Even now, you're still unwilling to reveal your true form?"

Bai Songshi offered no reply as he swept his sleeves toward Han Li while chanting an incantation.

The sound of howling wind rang out as the pair of five-colored fiery wheels rapidly expanded, swelling to several hundred feet in size in the blink of an eye before hurtling directly toward Han Li.

A burst of wince-inducing screeching rang out as a pair of extremely deep trenches were dug into the surface of the mountain summit by the pair of fiery wheels. Five-colored flames were burning within both of the trenches, melting straight through the solid rock.

The surrounding cultivators of the Bai Clan knew that they were far too weak to participate in the battle between Han Li and Bai Songshi, so all of them turned to attack Bai Suyuan at the azure-robed elderly man's behest.

Bai Suyuan clearly had no intentions of fighting fire with fire, and she summoned two or three protective treasures at once, conjuring up a large fiery cloud around her to ward off the attacks from the surrounding Bai Clan cultivators.

Even though she was significantly younger than all of the Bai Clan cultivators around her, she possessed outstanding cultivation aptitude, and her late-Deity Transformation Stage cultivation base meant that she was able to hold her own just fine despite being severely outnumbered.

Han Li displayed no intention of taking evasive measures from the pair of oncoming fiery wheels. Instead, he took a step forward, and golden scales surfaced over both of his arms as he reached forward with both hands at once.

A pair of massive golden hands appeared out of thin air, then reached straight into the five-colored flames before grabbing tightly onto the wheels within.

The fiery wheels were instantly stopped cold in their tracks as if they had crashed into an insurmountable barrier.

Bai Songshi's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he began to chant a loud incantation while making a rapid series of hand seals.

The flames around the fiery wheel instantly began to burn with even greater ferocity, while the wheels themselves began to revolve at a higher speed, sending the flames around it shooting through the air in all directions.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he felt the increased power output from the pair of fiery wheels, and he let loose a thunderous roar, then abruptly threw both of his hands up into the air.

Both of the giant fiery wheels were involuntarily hurled up into the sky, and in the next instant, Han Li sprang forward, arriving in front of Bai Songshi in a flash.

A string of cracks and pops rang out from one of his arms, which also expanded drastically in size as he launched a fist directly at Bai Songshi's head.

However, Bai Songshi was already prepared for such an attack, and he thrust both of his hands forward to release a round shield with the head of a beast engraved onto its surface.

A resounding thump rang out as Han Li's fist made contact with the shield, and the latter instantly caved in significantly, while Bai Songshi was sent flying back by the tremendous force behind Han Li's punch.

Before he had a chance to steady himself, Han Li appeared in front of him once again before throwing another devastating punch.

Bai Songshi had no choice but to raise the already severely damaged shield once again to defend himself, and a resounding boom rang out as the shield exploded into the pieces in the face of Han Li's attack.

Even after plowing through the shield, Han Li's fist still carried tremendous momentum as it continued to hurtle through the air before striking Bai Songshi square on the chest.

A dull thump rang out, and even though the sound wasn't very loud, it sent tremors running through the entire mountain summit.

Bai Songshi's chest was instantly caved in by the blow, but he suddenly raised his head to the heavens before opening his mouth to release a burst of dense, black devilish qi, which rose up into the sky like a plume of black smoke.

The plume of devilish qi quickly filled the entire sky above the Grand Loft Mountain, and in the blink of an eye, the entire surrounding area in a radius of several hundred kilometers had been plunged into a pitch-black night.

"What the hell..."

"Everyone, stop!"

"Suyuan, could it be that you were telling the truth this entire time?"

All of the Bai Clan cultivators who were attacking Bai Suyuan immediately stopped what they were doing as they looked up into the sky with incredulous expressions. No longer supported by the heavenly devil, Bai Songshi's lifeless body was falling out of the air.

Bai Suyuan also looked up into the sky as the fiery cloud around her faded, and a hint of fierce resentment had surfaced in her eyes.

"If you don't want to die, then take those mortals at the foot of the mountain and leave this place right now," Han Li instructed in a cold voice.

Everyone immediately snapped back to their senses upon hearing this, and they hurriedly picked up Bai Songshi's remains before flying down the mountain.

The azure-robed elderly man turned to Bai Suyuan with a complex expression, and after some hesitation, he said, "I'm sorry for doubting you, Suyuan. Come with us, it's not safe here."

Bai Suyuan didn't even spare a glance at the elderly man as she spat through gritted teeth, "No, I have to see that heavenly devil die with my own eyes."

The azure-robed elderly man opened his mouth to say something, but ultimately only heaved a resigned sigh before flying down the mountain.

At this point, the devilish cloud in the sky had already become extremely dense, and it had manifested itself into a giant human face.

"I'm going to tear off your skin and grind your bones to dust for forcing me to abandon my human body!"

A cold voice rang out from the heavens, and as soon as the voice trailed off, the human face in the sky immediately opened its mouth to release a vast expanse of devilish flames that swept toward Han Li in a frenzy.

At this point, Han Li had already summoned the black saber that he had taken from Fang Pan, and with a flick of his wrist, he unleashed a massive saber projection that was over 100 feet wide, sending it sweeping toward the oncoming sea of devilish flames.

The sea of black flames was instantly parted by the formidable saber projection, creating a path straight down the middle that was 1,000 feet wide.

Han Li flew directly through that opening as he slashed his saber incessantly through the air, conjuring up a vast expanse of black saber projections that hurtled toward the massive face up above.

In the face of the saber projections, the enormous devilish cloud up above was sliced into pieces while churning incessantly.

The giant face in the sky continued to blast devilish flames at Han Li, but the flames were easily kept at bay by Han Li's saber projections.

Right at this moment, the devilish cloud suddenly began to shrink, contracting from several hundred kilometers in size to only dozens of kilometers, forming a massive devilish face with a pair of black horns on its head.

The devilish face opened its mouth, and an enormous black vortex appeared within, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force that sucked Han Li into the vortex in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, the devilish face closed its mouth to swallow up Han Li.

Bai Suyuan's heart sank slightly upon seeing this, and she flipped a hand over to produce a golden ball, which she concealed up her sleeve.

The golden ball was riddled with runes, and there were arcs of golden lightning flashing over its surface. It was a ball of Divine Devilbane Lightning, which was unmatched in its effectiveness against Extrarealm Heavenly Devils.

A long while later, the devilish face remained completely unchanged, and a hint of resolve appeared in Bai Suyuan's eyes as she prepared to fly up herself and attack the heavenly devil in one final act of defiance.

Right at this moment, flashes of silver light suddenly appeared from the corners of the devilish face's lips, and immediately thereafter, a resounding thunderclap rang out as the giant devilish face exploded amid an eruption of silver lightning.

A Lightning Bird with silver lightning all over its body then flew out into the open before reverting back to Han Li's human form.

After the devilish face exploded, the scattered devilish cloud converged once again to form an inky-black elderly man that sped directly toward Bai Suyuan.

The elderly man was identical to Bai Songshi in appearance, except its entire body was pitch-black in color.

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he slashed his black saber downward, and a black saber projection flashed through the air at an incredible speed, striking the inky-black elderly man and slicing its body in half right before it could reach Bai Suyuan.

A thunderous crack rang out as the black saber projection continued onward even after passing through the inky-black elderly man's body, slicing straight into the Grand Loft Mountain itself.

A burst of violent tremors rang through the entire mountain, and countless rocks were sent clattering down the mountain while flocks of birds flew away in alarm and panic.

Only after a long while did the tremors subside, and after the dust settled, Bai Suyuan was astonished to discover that an enormous rift had appeared before her.

The entire Grand Loft Mountain had been sliced in half.

Unbeknownst to Han Li, this casual slash of his would go on to erase the name of the Grand Loft Mountain from the map of the Hundred Blessings Nation. From that day onward, the Grand Loft Mountain became known as the Mountain of Halves, and this new name was accompanied by a legend detailing the exploits of a devil-slaying immortal.

Of course, none of that was of any concern to Han Li.

The heavenly devil's body had also been sliced into two, with each half situated on one side of the rift.

Han Li descended out of the sky and arrived beside the inky-black elderly man with a cold look in his eyes. He raised a hand and was just about to deal the killing blow when a voice suddenly rang his mind.

"Hold on a second, Fellow Daoist Han."

A pitiful look appeared in the inky-black elderly man's eyes as he implored, "Please don't kill me, Fellow Daoist. I'm willing to sign a heavenly devil contract with you and pledge my eternal servitude to you."

Han Li offered no response to this, but a peculiar look had appeared on his face.

Bai Suyuan was terrified that Han Li would accept this offer, and she hurriedly approached him to dissuade him from giving in to temptation.

Right at this moment, Han Li's shadow abruptly elongated, and an inky-black figure emerged from within. It was none other than Mo Guang, and he was the one that had called out to Han Li just now, urging him not to deal the killing blow right away.

Chapter 184: A Request

As soon as Mo Guang appeared, he looked down at the inky-black elderly man on the ground as he scoffed in an emotionless voice, "How insolent of you to think that low-tier trash like yourself is worthy of signing a heavenly devil contract with him!"

The inky-black elderly was terrified at the sight of Mo Guang, and black light flashed over its body as it attempted to flee by disintegrating into a cloud of devilish qi.

However, Mo Guang wasn't going to allow such a thing to happen, and he instantly extended a hand forward. Black light flashed from his palm, forming a large black net that descended onto the elderly man, enveloping the cloud of devilish qi that the man had transformed into before rapidly contracting.

"No!"

An anguished howl rang out from within the cloud of devilish qi, and it twisted and warped momentarily before reforming into the elderly man's body within the net.

Immediately thereafter, Mo Guang chanted an incantation in an unfamiliar language, and black light flashed within his eyes, following which he opened his mouth before inhaling sharply, and the elderly man reverted back into a cloud of devilish qi that flowed into Mo Guang's mouth along with the black net.

The other half of the heavenly devil's body on the other side of the rift wasn't spared, either, and it was also devoured by Mo Guang as a stream of mist, following which the storage bracelet that it was carrying clattered down onto the ground.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already collected the pair of fiery wheel spirit treasures before returning to his original spot.

Mo Guang's body blurred momentarily before he re-entered Han Li's shadow, and at the same time, his voice rang out within Han Li's mind.

"Please examine the contents of that man's storage treasure for me, Fellow Daoist Han. As a heavenly devil, I'm sure he must have a good collection of Devilish Deed Stones. If I can get my hands on those stones, I'll be able to recover a bit more."

After devouring the other heavenly devil, Mo Guang's voice had become slightly more expressive and wasn't as stiff and wooden as it had been previously.

Han Li swept a sleeve toward the ground upon hearing this, and the black storage bracelet rose up into the air.

Right at this moment, a white shadow flashed past, and the black bracelet abruptly vanished from the spot.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

The white shadow drew to a halt not far away, revealing itself to be Bai Suyuan, and she was clutching the black bracelet tightly in both hands.

"Thank you for slaying that devil for me, Senior Li, but this bracelet belongs to our Bai Clan. As a lofty immortal, surely nothing in the possession of our Bai Clan would be of sufficient value to catch your eye," Bai Suyuan said.

Her expression had eased significantly in the wake of the heavenly devil's death, and she was clearly extremely relieved. Furthermore, she wasn't displaying any fear at the sight of Mo Guang.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then said, "Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Bai. I have no intention of taking anything that rightfully belongs to your Bai Clan. However, that Extrarealm Heavenly Devil most likely had some Devilish Deed Stones in his collection, and those stones are very important to me.

“Please check if there are any such stones present in the storage bracelet, and if there are, I'm willing to purchase them from you with spirit stones."

Bai Suyuan nodded in response as a smile appeared on her face, then directed her spiritual sense into the black bracelet.

Moments later, she flipped a hand over to produce a black stone that had wisps of black mist drifting around it and was giving off a peculiar aura.

"Is this what you're looking for?"

Han Li consulted Mo Guang through their spiritual connection, and after verifying that this was indeed a Devilish Deed Stone, he replied, "That's right. How many of these stones are in there? I'll take them all."

"Hold on, I'll count them now... There are 20 of these stones in the bracelet," Bai Suyuan replied.

"I can offer you 20 top-grade spirit stones for these Devilish Deed Stones. What do you think?" Han Li asked as he flipped a hand over to produce 20 top-grade spirit stones.

To his surprise, Bai Suyuan immediately shook her head and turned down his offer.

"Is the price too low for your liking?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Bai Suyuan shook her head once again as she replied, "That's not the case. I know that there's no way that a True Immortal like yourself would stoop to trying to swindle someone like me. In our Hundred Blessings Nation, a top-grade spirit stones is worth at least 100 high-grade spirit stones, and even back when our Bai Clan was in its heyday, I only received an allowance of no more than three high-grade spirit stones per year, and that was only because I was held in high regard by our patriarch."

"Then what would you like in exchange for those Devilish Deed Stones?" Han Li asked as he stowed his spirit stones away.

"I want you to fulfill a request of mine," Bai Suyuan replied with a mischievous smile.

"A request?" Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, and he felt as if he were getting to know Bai Suyuan for the first time all over again.

Following the heavenly devil's demise, it was as if she had become a completely different person, as if her quirky and mischievous nature, which had previously been repressed by her stress and desire for vengeance, was only just returning to the fore.

"That's right. As for exactly what the request is, I haven't decided on it yet, but rest assured, my request definitely won't be a dangerous one to fulfill, or beyond the scope of your abilities. I'll only be a small request," Bai Suyuan said with a serious expression.

Han Li contemplated the situation momentarily, then nodded in agreement. "Alright, but I'll only give you three days to think of your request. If you take any longer than that, then the deal's off."

"It's a promise!" Bai Suyuan smiled as she tossed a small pouch at Han Li.

"I've already completed the mission that you requested for me, so I believe it's time you gave me the promised reward," Han Li said as he stowed the pouch away.

"Given what's just happened here, other people are most likely going to arrive on the scene to investigate soon, so let's leave this place first. Rest assured, Senior, if I don't give you your reward for completing the mission, even if you don't come after me, the Transient Guild wouldn't spare me," Bai Suyuan said.

Immediately thereafter, she turned and flew away into the distance as a streak of white light without waiting for a response from Han Li.

Han Li also rose up into the air and followed along behind her.

A short while later, the two of them descended onto a lush mountain several thousand kilometers away from the Grand Loft Mountain.

The environment on the mountain was quite peaceful, and there was also a quaint river at the foot of the mountain, presenting a captivating sight to behold.

On the mountain was a grave, complete with an old tombstone with some text engraved upon it. The text had already become quite indistinct from age and natural wear, but the initial Bai character could still be made out.

Bai Suyuan descended onto the ground in front of the grave, and a film of tears appeared in her eyes at the sight of the tombstone as she sank to her knees.

"That devilish creature is finally dead, Grandpa. Your soul can rest now..." Bai Suyuan sobbed as her thin and delicate shoulders trembled.

Han Li waited patiently as Bai Suyuan paid her respects at her grandfather's grave, turning to look away from the grave in order to give her some privacy.

Bai Suyuan's sobs continued to ring out from behind him, and only after a long while did they gradually subside.

"I'm sorry you had to see that, Senior Li. I was momentarily overcome with emotions," Bai Suyuan said as she slowly made her way toward Han Li.

"There's nothing to apologize for, Fellow Daoist Bai, you were only displaying normal human emotions. Having said that, as those who remain in the world of the living, we have to remain strong, so don't dwell too much on your grief," Han Li consoled.

The rims of Bai Suyuan's eyes were still a little red, and there were still some tear streaks on her cheeks. Both her expression and her aura indicated that her emotions were completely genuine.

Having seen so much throughout his life, Han Li wasn't moved by her emotional display, but he didn't have a heart of stone, either, so he naturally offered her some words of consolation.

"Thank you, Senior Li," Bai Suyuan sighed as she flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized azure badge. On one side of the badge was inscribed the characters for "Blaze Dragon", while the visage of a strange dragon with a pair of wings on its back and a single horn on its head was engraved on the other side.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly as his gaze fell upon the badge.

"This is a Blaze Dragon Token. Seeing as you're not from the Ancient Cloud Continent, you may not be aware of how rigorous the standards are for someone wishing to join the Blaze Dragon Dao. For a start, they must possess exceptional aptitude and have a pure and untarnished background.

“However, this token can allow one to directly enter the Blaze Dragon Dao's inner sect regardless of their aptitude. The ancestor of our Bai Clan was only awarded with this token after making a significant contribution to the Blaze Dragon Dao," Bai Suyuan said as she gently stroked the badge with her fingers.

"I see. This is indeed quite a precious token then," Han Li replied with a nod.

"After my grandfather passed away, I originally planned to join the Blaze Dragon Dao using this token, but I couldn't bear the thought of allowing that heavenly devil to remain at large for the foreseeable future, and that's why I used the token to release this mission instead," Bai Suyuan sighed as she offered the badge to Han Li.

A hint of sympathy flashed through Han Li's eyes, but he still accepted the badge from her.

All of a sudden, Bai Suyuan raised her head as she asked, "Your promise to fulfill a request of mine still counts, right?"

"Have you thought of what you'd like to request from me?" Han Li asked.

"I don't have very strong emotional ties with the rest of the members of the Bai Clan. In fact, most of them hold negative views of me for what happened in the past, so I can't stay here any longer. Even though I no longer have a Blaze Dragon Token, I still want to go to the Blaze Dragon Dao and try my luck.

“Who knows? Maybe I'll be fortunate enough to be accepted. Seeing as you accepted this mission for this Blaze Dragon Token, I presume you must intend to join the Blaze Dragon Dao as well. Hence, I would like you to take me there," Bai Suyuan said.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, clearly not anticipating such a request.

The Ancient Cloud Continent was extremely vast, and there was still a very long way to go before one could reach the Bell Toll Mountain Range where the Blaze Dragon Dao was situated. The journey wouldn't be as perilous as that of crossing the Primordial Wave Continent, but it still definitely wasn't going to be smooth sailing.

Given her Deity Transformation Stage cultivation base, attempting the journey on her own would've been extremely risky, and even the slightest mishap along the way could result in her demise.

Despite her frail appearance, Bai Suyuan was quite a crafty girl, and Han Li had no good reason to turn down her request.

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li said, "If you've made up your mind, then I could certainly bring you with me. However, once we reach the Blaze Dragon Dao, your request will be fulfilled, so don't expect anything more out of me."

"Really? Thank you so much! I'm already extremely grateful that you're willing to take me there, I wouldn't dare to trouble you for anything else, Senior Li!" Bai Suyuan said as an exuberant smile appeared on her face.

Han Li wasted no time with words upon hearing this, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a white jade boat shaped like a flying bird before drifting onto it.

This was a top-grade spirit treasure that he had found in Fang Pan's storage treasure, and it was only a sliver away from becoming an immortal treasure.

Bai Suyuan hurriedly flew onto the boat as well before taking a seat. Her smile then faded as she put on a serious expression and vowed, "I'll be sure to remember everything you've done for me, Senior Li."

Han Li offered no response as he released an incantation seal, and the jade boat immediately began to glow with bright white radiance before shooting rapidly away into the distance.

Chapter 185: Arriving at the Blaze Dragon Dao

The Bell Toll Mountain Range was situated atop a massive system of spirit veins, so the world's origin qi in the area was extremely abundant. Hence, even though the climate here was quite cold, the mountain range was still rife with lush greenery, and countless spirit beasts and spirit herbs could be found in the region.

The mountain range was so vast that it stretched across virtually half of the entire Ancient Cloud Continent, and all of the mountains within it were extremely tall and steep, extending straight up into the heavens. Furthermore, the mountains were enshrouded within a type of azure mist all year round, giving them a sense of enigma and mystique.

A strange loud noise would periodically ring out across the entire mountain range during all times of the year, and the sound was very similar to the toll of a bell, thereby giving the mountain range its name.

Apparently, these sounds came from the tectonic plate activity taking place in the earth beneath the mountain range.

The Bell Toll Mountain Range was quite a renowned place in its own right, but it was overshadowed by the Blaze Dragon Dao, which was vastly renowned across the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

The Blaze Dragon Dao was one of the oldest sects in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and its founder was a man with the title of Daoist Master Blaze Dragon.

Ever since its founding, the Blaze Dragon Dao had always been the number one sect on the Ancient Cloud Continent, and at this point, its forces had branched out across the entire continent. The sect was home to countless prodigious disciples, and even in the context of the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, it ranked among a small handful of the very top sects.

Around the central region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range stood a massive mountain near the edge of the mountain range.

The mountain extended all the way up into the clouds, and a vast white jade plaza had been constructed halfway up the mountain. A series of tall buildings were situated on the plaza, and they were also primarily white in color, giving off a bright glow that allowed them to be clearly seen even from hundreds of kilometers away.

This was one of the external mountains of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and it was generally used to accommodate visitors.

Due to the resounding reputation of the Blaze Dragon Dao, it received an enormous number of visitors, so there were several dozen such accommodation sites littered throughout the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

At this moment, there were several Blaze Dragon Dao disciples chatting with one another while standing in the welcome pavilion on the plaza.

These disciples were all at around the Deity Transformation Stage, and each of them had the visage of a dragon with a pair of wings and a single horn on its head embroidered onto their sleeve.

"How many batches of visitors have we had over the past few days?" a tall and thin young man asked with a smile.

"It's already been 25 batches. What can I say? Our Blaze Dragon Dao has such a resounding reputation that people flock here from all over the continent," a slightly portly man replied with a proud grin on his face.

"Welcoming these guests is such a boring job. I just want my shift to be over as soon as possible," a gorgeous purple-haired young woman complained with a disgruntled expression.

"I understand your frustration, Junior Martial Sister Yin. You've already reached the pinnacle of the Deity Transformation Stage, so you'll be attempting a breakthrough to the Spatial Tempering Stage soon. This is indeed a rather unsuitable time for you to be serving guest welcoming duties. How are your preparations for the breakthrough coming along?" the thin young man asked.

"I've already made some preparations, but I'd say I only have a roughly 30% chance of success," the purple-haired young woman replied with furrowed brows.

"Don't be disheartened, Junior Disciple Sister. Welcoming guests isn't necessarily always a waste of time. If you encounter a generous senior and ensure that they receive a satisfactory welcome, perhaps they'll be willing to gift you some spirit stones. In particular, someone as beautiful as yourself stands a much better chance of receiving such a reward than men like us," the portly man said with a smile.

The purple-haired young woman's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this. "Is that so?"

Right at this moment, a speck of white light appeared on the distant horizon, and it was rapidly approaching the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

As the speck of white light drew closer to the mountain range, it was revealed to be a white jade boat.

A middle-aged man with a yellow complexion was standing on the boat, accompanied by a gorgeous young woman in a long white dress.

These two were none other than Han Li and Bai Suyuan, and they had finally arrived here after traveling for several years.

"So this is the Bell Toll Mountain Range... the world's origin qi here is extremely abundant," Han Li remarked with an approving nod.

A hint of longing had also surfaced in Bai Suyuan's eyes, and she was looking quite excited, but she then immediately took a deep breath to recover her composure.

Instead of descending onto the mountain range right away, a contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face.

Even though Bai Suyuan had told him that the Blaze Dragon Token would be sufficient for him to join the Blaze Dragon Dao, he still had to think about how to make the best use of the token.

Ideally, he would have someone in the Blaze Dragon Dao submit a recommendation for him.

Han Li knew nothing about the Blaze Dragon Dao, but this wasn't a very difficult task to accomplish. All that he required was some time for planning.

An intelligent gleam flashed through Bai Suyuan's eyes as she said, "Senior Li, if you're considering how to acquaint yourself with someone in the Blaze Dragon Dao, then I believe I can lend you a hand."

"What do you propose?" Han Li asked as he turned to Bai Suyuan.

He wasn't all that surprised that she had managed to guess his intentions.

During the past few years traveling together, he had come to know Bai Suyuan quite well. Her cultivation base wasn't worthy of note, but she was extremely intelligent and observant, often able to glean his thoughts and intentions from very limited tidbits of information.

As a result, he barely said a word to her throughout the final two to three years of their journey.

"It just so happens that the ancestor of our Bai Clan had a good friend by the name of Qi Liang in the Blaze Dragon Dao. He's an inner sect elder, and our ancestor once said that if anyone in our clan wishes to join the Blaze Dragon Dao in the future, then we can seek out Qi Liang to look out for us.

“It's been several thousand years since our ancestor disappeared, so I'm not sure if he would still be willing to help us, but we should at least be able to request an audience with him," Bai Suyuan explained.

"In that case, I'll have to trouble you, Fellow Daoist Bai," Han Li replied with a nod.

"It's no trouble at all, Senior Li. You looked after me throughout our entire journey to the Blaze Dragon Dao, this is the least that I can do for you. However..." Bai Suyuan's voice trailed off here as a hesitant look appeared on her face.

"What is it?" Han Li asked.

"Forgive me for prying into your personal matters, but I'm assuming that your current appearance isn't your true appearance, right, Senior Li?" Bai Suyuan asked in a hesitant voice.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he asked, "What do you mean by that, Fellow Daoist Bai?"

"Over the past few years, I've developed somewhat of an understanding of your personality. You're extremely cautious when it comes to everything else, but you've made no effort at all to hide your appearance, and that tells me that this most likely isn't your true appearance at all. On top of that, as a member of the Transient Guild, I'm aware that these masks can provide extremely effective disguises," Bai Suyuan explained with a faint smile.

"As expected, these little tricks of mine aren't enough to fool you. Your intelligence is truly unmatched, Fellow Daoist Bai," Han Li praised with a smile of his own.

"You're far too kind, Senior Li. If it isn't for the fact that I've been by your side for so long, I wouldn't have been able to make this educated guess. If you want to join the Blaze Dragon Dao, then you'll have to do away with your disguise.

“The masks of the Transient Guild can fool the vast majority of cultivators, but it's said that here are 13 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and the first dao lord is said to have already reached the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage and is on the very cusp of the High Zenith Stage.

“I doubt the disguises conjured up by the masks of the Transient Guild will be able to fool them, and if you're exposed, not only will you be barred from joining the sect, there's a chance that you'll even be regarded as a spy from an enemy sect," Bai Suyuan said with a serious expression.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then nodded in response as he made a hand seal, reverting back to his original appearance amid a faint flash of light.

Bai Suyuan's gaze lingered momentarily on Han Li's completely unremarkable appearance, following which she pursed her lips slightly as she withdrew her gaze.

The white jade boat continued to fly onward at Han Li's behest, quickly reaching the mountain up ahead before descending onto the plaza.

After Bai Suyuan had gotten down from the boat, Han Li stowed it away, and the two of them were standing side by side on the plaza.

The disciples responsible for welcoming guests had already spotted them from afar, and they approached Han Li's duo as one of them said, "Welcome to the Blaze Dragon Dao. May I ask what business you have here?"

The disciples were immediately able to tell that Han Li possessed a cultivation base far superior to theirs, but even so, all of them wore relaxed smiles and didn't appear to have been feeling intimidated or inferior in the slightest.

"We've come here with the intention of paying Elder Qi Liang a visit. Is he in the sect right now?" Han Li asked as he revealed a hint of his True Immortal Stage aura, and the Blaze Dragon Dao cultivators before him shuddered collectively in the face of his aura, but thankfully, the aura was only revealed for an instant before it was withdrawn again.

"Please inform Elder Qi of our arrival." Han Li flicked a finger through the air as he spoke, releasing several precious Deity Transformation Stage pills.

These pills had all been obtained from the storage treasures of cultivators that he had slain in the past, and they were useless to him, so he was naturally happy to present them as gifts to these Blaze Dragon Dao cultivators.

The group of cultivators before him swept their spiritual sense over the pills, and they weren't able to maintain their composure any longer as ecstatic looks appeared on their faces.

These worthless pills to Han Li were nothing short of priceless treasures to these disciples.

Even a pill suitable for consumption for Nascent Soul cultivators could be sold on the market in exchange for spirit stones sufficient to cover their cultivation needs for a long time, let alone these pills that were fit for consumption for Deity Transformation cultivators.

Among the disciples, the thin young man was more restrained, and he cupped his fist in a respectful salute as he said, "You're far too kind, Senior. Elder Qi Liang serves in the Heavenly Star Palace, so he's always present in the sect. May I ask your name, Senior? And also, do you have any tokens that we can pass onto Elder Qi?"

"I am Li Feiyu, and this is Bai Suyuan. In terms of tokens..." Han Li turned to Bai Suyuan as he spoke.

"Please pass this onto Elder Qi and he'll know who we are." Bai Suyuan pulled out a red penannular jade pendant and offered it to the thin young man as she spoke.

"I see. I'll inform Elder Qi of your arrival right away, Senior Li. However, I must make it clear ahead of time that I can't guarantee whether Elder Qi will agree to see you or not," the thin young man said as he accepted the jade pendant.

"Of course," Han Li replied with a nod.

Thus, the thin young man took his leave before quickly making his way toward a certain palace in the sect.

"Senior Li, Fellow Daoist Bai, please come and take a rest in the side hall," the slightly portly man said in a respectful voice, then led Han Li and Bai Suyuan to a pavilion constructed halfway up the mountain.

The pavilion was situated in a bamboo forest, and the light of the sun was filtering through the gaps among the bamboo leaves, casting some beautiful shadows onto the building. The interior of the pavilion was cool and tidy, and all of the furnishings inside had clearly been chosen with care, presenting a pleasant sight to behold.

"Please wait here for a moment. Elder Qi is an inner sect elder, so it may take some time to reach him," the portly man said with a hint of apology on his face, then offered up two cups of spirit tea.

Han Li nodded in response and left the spirit tea on the table beside him, while Bai Suyuan began to sip on her tea, savoring it with keen interest.

The portly man remained in the hall alongside Han Li and Bai Suyuan, and before long, close to half a day had passed by.

Despite the long wait, Han Li remained patient, taking the time to ponder the situation that he was in.

While traveling to the Blaze Dragon Dao, he had been periodically detecting for the presence of Daoist Xie and his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

To his elation, the closer he drew to the Bell Toll Mountain Range, the clearer he was able to sense those lost treasures, indicating to him that they were most likely situated in the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

If he wanted to recover them, then he would have to join the Blaze Dragon Dao first.

Chapter 186: Plan

Han Li's primary objective for coming to the Blaze Dragon Dao was to recover his lost treasures, and he also wanted to read the sect's scriptures pertaining to the laws of time to see if he could learn anything from them.

Even though he was able to manifest crystals that also contained the power of time laws using his Heaven Controlling Vial, the crystals served no other purpose than to speed up his Earthly Deity Avatar's derivation of heavy water, and he was unable to glean anything from them.

As one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time were extremely profound, and given his aptitude, it was downright delusional to think that he could master the laws of time unless he had some immense luck on his side.

In contrast, these sects had already studied the laws of time for millions, even tens of millions of years, and there was no lack of prodigiously talented individuals to come out of these sects during this time, so they would've surely developed some valuable insights.

Of course, if it proved impossible for him to access the scriptures that he desired, then he wouldn't force the issue. Time was of the essence for him, and he couldn't afford to waste it. Given how vast the Northern Glacial Immortal Region was, he would always be able to find something else.

This was his initial thought process, but during the journey to Bell Toll Mountain Range, he had learned some things about the Blaze Dragon Dao from Bai Suyuan that had convinced him to change his mind.

The Blaze Dragon Dao had a long history and a vast foundation, home to countless high-grade immortal scriptures of all descriptions. Most importantly, it harbored no aversion to outsiders.

It was very difficult for itinerant cultivators like Han Li to join the Blaze Dragon Dao, but if he could successfully join the sect, then he would be granted a high degree of freedom and autonomy, and that was a very tempting prospect to him.

Some time had already passed since his return to the Immortal Realm, and aside from the initial few years that he had spent in the Black Wind Sea, he had been traveling the rest of the time, so he hadn't been able to take any time to cultivate.

The Black Wind Sea was a relatively safe place, but it was extremely short on resources, with not even a single high-grade immortal scripture to be found.

There were all types of cultivation resources available in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and his freedom wasn't going to be overly restricted here, so this was the ideal place for him to stay for the time being.

Thanks to his powers as a Profound Immortal and certain cultivation arts that he mastered in lower realms, such as his Provenance True Devil Arts, he had been able to deal with some early and mid-True Immortal Stage itinerant cultivators just fine.

However, contending against True Immortals who had attained the power of laws was still quite a struggle for him. After all, he couldn't expect to get lucky every single time as he had against Fang Pan.

As their name suggested, True Immortals were immortal, but they weren't indestructible, and they could perish all the same, just not by natural causes.

Hence, he required more power if he wanted to stake a foothold for himself in the Immortal Realm. The problem was that he didn't even have a suitable immortal cultivation art, so he was still stuck at the early-True Immortal Stage.

Right as these thoughts were running through Han Li's mind, the sound of footsteps rang out from outside, and he immediately opened his eyes to find the same thin young man from before accompanying a middle-aged man who appeared to have been in his forties into the room.

The man wore a long white robe, and there was an authoritative look on his square face. His features were quite unremarkable, but there was a sharp and piercing gleam in his eyes. What was particularly noteworthy about him was his vast aura, which indicated that he was also a True Immortal cultivator.

Han Li rose to his feet, and Bai Suyuan hurriedly got up from her chair as well.

The square-faced man was holding Bai Suyuan's penannular jade pendant, and he took a glance at the two people in the room, resting his gaze on Han Li for a moment as he declared, "I am Qi Liang. May I ask how you've managed to come across this token of Elder Bai Fengyi's?"

"Bai Fengyi is the patriarch of my clan, Senior Qi. My name is Bai Suyuan, and I am a descendant of Patriarch Bai," Bai Suyuan explained as she extended a curtsey toward Qi Liang.

"I see, then who is this Fellow Daoist Li?" Qi Liang asked as he turned his gaze to Han Li.

"I am just an itinerant cultivator who accompanied Fellow Daoist Bai to the Blaze Dragon Dao. It's an honor to make your acquaintance, Fellow Daoist Qi," Han Li said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"The honor is all mine, Fellow Daoist Li. Please take a seat," Qi Liang said as he returned Han Li's salute.

The thin young man brought the three of them fresh cups of spirit tea, then extended a respectful bow before departing from the room.

"Where is Brother Bai right now, Suyuan? Is he well? If I recall correctly, it's already been several thousand years since he left the sect, and there's been no news of him at all since then," Qi Liang said.

"Unfortunately, we haven't heard any news from our patriarch, either, ever since his departure several thousand years ago, so I have no idea where he is or what condition he's currently in," Bai Suyuan replied as a dejected look appeared on his face.

Qi Liang seemed to have been rather taken aback to hear this. "You're saying Brother Bai never returned to his clan?"

Bai Suyuan could tell that Qi Liang seemed to know something that she didn't, and she hurriedly asked, "Senior Qi, do you know exactly for what purpose our patriarch last left the sect?"

"If I recall correctly, Brother Bai left the sect to carry out some type of mission. There's no need to be overly concerned, Suyuan. Brother Bai's Origin Soul Lamp in our sect has remained lit this entire time, so perhaps he's simply been delayed by some matters. For the likes of Brother Bai and myself, several thousand years is not a very long time. Perhaps he'll be back soon," Qi Liang consoled.

Bai Suyuan was ecstatic to hear this, and an excited look appeared in her eyes. "Is that true? That's great!"

Meanwhile, Han Li sat off to the side in silence, taking no part in the conversation.

"Suyuan, may I ask why you've come to the Blaze Dragon Dao with Fellow Daoist Li?" Qi Liang asked as he took a glance at Han Li's duo.

Bai Suyuan and Han Li exchanged a glance, and Han Li made a slight gesture, indicating for her to speak first.

"I've held a great deal of admiration toward the Blaze Dragon Dao ever since I was a child, and I've come here on this occasion with the hope of being able to join the sect. I know that we're currently not in the sect's disciple intake window, so I wanted to trouble you to submit a recommendation for me. I've prepared these gifts as a gesture of my sincerity, please accept them, Senior Qi."

Bai Suyuan rose to her feet and extended a deep curtsey as she spoke, then pulled out a storage treasure that she was just about set down onto the table next to Qi Liang.

A displeased look appeared on Qi Liang's face as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of invisible force that lifted Bai Suyuan's body into an upright posture again. "Brother Bai and I are extremely close friends, how could I possibly accept a gift from you over such a minor matter? Put that away at once!"

Bai Suyuan didn't insist on making Qi Liang accept her gifts, and she stowed the storage treasure away discreetly as she said, "In that case, I'll be counting on you, Senior Qi."

"I can submit a recommendation for you, but the prerequisites for disciple recruitment in the Blaze Dragon Dao are very rigorous. If your aptitude is found lacking, then I'm afraid there's nothing I can do," Qi Liang said.

"Of course. If my aptitude is lacking, then that means I was simply not meant to go further on the path of cultivation, and I certainly wouldn't dare to blame you for anything, Senior Qi," Bai Suyuan immediately replied.

Qi Liang nodded in response, then took a glance at Han Li, and even though he didn't say anything, it was clear that he wanted to know Han Li's purpose for visiting the Blaze Dragon Dao as well.

"My objective for visiting the Blaze Dragon Dao is the same as Fellow Daoist Bai's. I would also like to join the Blaze Dragon Dao, and I was wondering if you could submit a recommendation for me as well. Regardless of the outcome, I'll be sure to compensate you for your efforts," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Qi Liang's brows furrowed ever so slightly upon hearing this.

Even though he had told Bai Suyuan that he couldn't guarantee her entry into the Blaze Dragon Dao, he had briefly examined her spiritual roots just now, so he knew that given her aptitude, there should've been no problems for her to join the sect.

However, Han Li was a True Immortal cultivator, and if he were to join the Blaze Dragon Dao, then it definitely wouldn't be as a disciple.

The Blaze Dragon Dao's requirements for recruiting foreign True Immortal cultivators had always been far more rigorous than that of recruiting disciples, so a thorough examination had to be made into Han Li's identity, background, cultivation base, and aptitude.

If Han Li were found to be lacking in any of those areas, then Qi Liang would be punished by the sect for submitting a recommendation for him without performing due diligence.

Han Li could see that Qi Liang had some qualms about accepting his request, so he flipped a hand over to produce the Blaze Dragon Token as he said, "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Qi. I may be an itinerant cultivator, but I haven't committed any heinous crimes in the past, and I have this token with me. All I need is for you to submit a small recommendation for me."

"That's a Blaze Dragon Token!" Qi Liang exclaimed as he rose to his feet, then turned to Bai Suyuan with a surprised expression.

"That's right, that is the very same Blaze Dragon Token that previously belonged to our patriarch. Recently, our Bai Clan encountered an extremely severe crisis, and it was only thanks to Senior Li that we were able to avert the crisis, so I gave him the Blaze Dragon Token as thanks for saving our clan," Bai Suyuan explained.

"I see. If Fellow Daoist Li has indeed saved the entire Bai Clan, then he's certainly deserving of the Blaze Dragon Token. Please come with me," Qi Liang replied with a nod as he turned to depart from the pavilion.

Han Li and Bai Suyuan followed him to a nearby azure hall, hanging above the entrance of which was a plaque that read "Teleportation Pavilion".

"Our Blaze Dragon Dao is so massive that it can be very inconvenient to get to certain places by flight. Hence, these teleportation pavilions have been set up in all of the important places in the sect," Qi Liang explained.

"As expected of the number one sect on the Ancient Cloud Continent," Han Li praised in a heartfelt manner.

Upon stepping into the pavilion, Han Li discovered that the interior space wasn't very large, and there was only a single small teleportation array at the center of the room, surrounded by an array of stone pillars.

Aside from that, there was also a middle-aged man who was roughly at the Deity Transformation Stage standing beside the array, and he hurriedly extended a respectful bow at the sight of Qi Liang.

"Send us to the Ostentatious Palace," Qi Liang instructed after all three of them had made their way into the teleportation array.

"Yes!" the middle-aged man hurriedly replied with a nod, then chanted an incantation before releasing a burst of white light out of the palm of his hand.

As the teleportation array began to operate, a vast expanse of dazzling white light rose up to swallow up Han Li's trio.

Their surroundings blurred for a moment, and in the next instant, they appeared in another spacious azure hall.

His expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was feeling quite stunned.

Having already taken teleportation arrays on many occasions after arriving in the Immortal Realm, he was able to roughly estimate the distance of teleportation according to the time taken, and he had determined that if he were to fly over the same distance that they had just teleported, then it would've taken him roughly a month.

For the first time, he was given a rough indication of just how massive the Blaze Dragon Dao was.

"What an enormous place this is..." Han Li murmured to himself.

Chapter 187: Mediocre Aptitude

Moments later, Han Li's trio emerged from the teleportation pavilion.

This teleportation hall was situated on an extremely tall mountain summit, and there was a massive pavilion nearby as well, but this one was several times the size of the guest welcoming plaza.

The entire plaza was paved with white jade, which was giving off a bright white sheen, as well as traces of white mist.

Walking upon the plaza, one could see all the nearby mountains beneath their feet, striking one with the feeling that they were overlords presiding over everything.

There was a massive place hovering in mid-air above the plaza, and it was half-concealed within the clouds, giving it the appearance of a celestial city.

Above the entrance of the palace was a golden plaque, upon which was inscribed the words "Ostentatious Palace" in flowing golden characters.

"The Ostentatious Palace is where our sect examines the spiritual roots and aptitude of those wishing to join the sect. It's overseen by a deputy dao lord, so take care in how you act and speak once we're inside," Qi Liang cautioned.

Han Li gave a slight nod upon hearing this.

According to his knowledge, the Blaze Dragon Dao was different from normal sects in that it had no sect master. Instead, the sect was overseen by the 13 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords on a rotating roster.

Beneath the 13 dao lords were the 36 deputy dao lords, all of whom were said to have been at the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage.

Furthermore, these deputy dao lords weren't just ordinary True Immortals. Instead, all of them had mastered the power of laws, so they were far more powerful than the average itinerant immortal of the same cultivation base.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Qi," Han Li replied, and Bai Suyuan also responded in kind.

As they were speaking, the three of them had already descended onto the ground in front of the floating palace.

The gates of the palace up ahead were tightly shut, and a pair of young disciples were standing on either side of the gates.

The two young disciples hurriedly extended respectful bows toward Qi Liang, who asked them, "Is Deputy Dao Lord Xiong inside?"

"He is, but he's currently cultivating in seclusion at the moment, and he forbade us from interrupting him," one of the young disciples replied with a slightly awkward expression.

Qi Liang's brows furrowed lightly upon hearing this. "Did he tell you when he was going to conclude his seclusion?"

"No," the disciple replied.

Qi Liang pondered the situation in silence for a moment, then said, "Please inform him of our arrival, and tell him that I've come to him with an important matter."

Reluctant looks appeared on the faces of the two disciples, but after exchanging a glance, one of them pulled out a white badge before communicating something into it.

A full 15 minutes passed by before a brief flash of white light appeared on the badge.

"Deputy Dao Lord Xiong has invited you to go in," the disciple informed in a relieved voice, then cast an incantation seal, and the gates of the palace slowly swung open.

"Let's go."

Qi Liang led the way into the palace, and its interior was very spacious, with an area of several thousand feet.

There were dozens of azure stone pillars standing around the palace, every single one of which had a beastly statue coiled around it, including ones that depicted creatures like the Divine Dragon, the Azure Phoenix, the White Tiger, and the Qilin.

The mouths of these beasts were all aimed at a dark azure stone platform that resembled an altar, which stood at the center of the hall.

It was a circular platform that was over 100 feet in size, with countless extremely complex runes inscribed upon it, as well as diagrams formed by countless specks of light, giving the entire platform an extremely profound appearance.

At the very rear of the hall was a tall white platform, atop which sat a short and stubby middle-aged man who appeared to have been around 40 years of age. There was a thin mustache above his upper lip, and instead of the usual white robes worn by Blaze Dragon Dao disciples, he was dressed in a lavish golden robe with a golden hat on his head, giving him the appearance of a wealthy merchant of the mortal world.

The man wore a rather disgruntled expression, seemingly displeased by the fact that his cultivation had been disrupted.

"Greetings, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong," Qi Liang greeted as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Han Li took a glance at the man on the platform, and his pupils immediately contracted slightly.

The man was very unassuming in both appearance and stature, but he was giving off an incredibly powerful aura that far exceeded the auras of Fang Pan and that octopus sea beast.

Han Li couldn't help but be impressed by the man's immense aura, and he and Bai Suyuan both followed Qi Liang's example, each extending a salute toward the deputy dao lord.

Deputy Dao Lord Xiong didn't even spare a glance at Han Li and Bai Suyuan as he asked, "What is this important matter that you speak of, Elder Qi? Could you not have waited for me to conclude my seclusion before requesting an audience."

"My apologies for disrupting your cultivation, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong. This here is Fellow Daoist Li, and he's carrying a Blaze Dragon Token with the intention of joining our sect, so I had no choice but to come to you," Qi Liang explained with an apologetic expression.

Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "I see. Show me your Blaze Dragon Token."

Han Li had already summoned the token into his grasp, and Deputy Dao Lord Xiong made a beckoning motion to draw the token to himself.

"This is indeed an authentic Blaze Dragon Token," Deputy Dao Lord Xiong concluded after a brief examination, and only then did he turn his gaze toward Han Li.

At the same time, a faint gleam flashed through his eyes, as if he were trying to see straight through Han Li.

Under Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's sharp and intrusive gaze, Han LI felt as if there were blades raking over his entire body, resulting in a slightly painful sensation.

His brows furrowed ever so slightly, but he didn't say anything.

Deputy Dao Lord Xiong then withdrew his gaze as he cast an incantation seal and instructed, "Step on the Immortal Revolution Platform to have your aptitude examined."

All of the dozens of stone pillars in the hall shuddered slightly in unison before releasing dazzling azure light, and it was as if all of the spirit beasts engraved onto the pillars had sprung to life.

Bursts of azure light erupted out of the mouths of the spirit beasts engraved on the statues before vanishing into the round stone platform at the center of the hall.

All of the runes on the stone platform began to radiate dazzling light, forming a semi-transparent ball of light, upon which countless specks of what appeared to be starlight were flashing incessantly.

"Please go ahead, Fellow Daoist Li," Qi Liang said as he turned to Han Li.

Han Li nodded in response, then made his way onto the stone platform, and a huge burst of heat instantly rose up from the platform before surging into his body.

Countless specks of light of different colors instantly appeared within the ball of light, then began to rapidly revolve around Han Li in an extremely chaotic fashion.

Wherever that burst of heat flowed to in his body, Han Li felt as if everything within that part of his body was revealed for all to see, and that was a slightly disconcerting sensation.

All of a sudden, the burst of heat flowed into his brain and surged into his consciousness.

Han Li was greatly alarmed by this, and he immediately compressed the majority of his enormous spiritual sense into a point, leaving only around a tenth to a fifth of his spiritual sense exposed.

The surge of heat flowed through his brain for a moment before quickly moving onto other parts of his body, and it didn't take long before it left his body altogether, then flowed back into the stone platform.

The spherical light barrier on the stone platform faded, but those countless runes continued to linger in the air, then converged to form a blurry humanoid figure that was giving off lights of different colors, including azure, black, crimson, and purple. However, these lights weren't very bright, and they appeared to be extremely chaotic.

Qi Liang's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the indistinct humanoid figure.

A cold sneer appeared on Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's face, and he made no effort to hide his derision as he declared, "Your aptitude is downright mediocre. The cultivation arts that you've dabbled in are a chaotic mess, but your energy and blood essence are both quite abundant. It seems that you've managed to absorb some demonic bloodlines, but those are in a state of complete disarray as well.

“On top of that, you haven't managed to open up even a single immortal acupoint. It's a miracle that you were even able to reach the early-True Immortal Stage at all."

Qi Liang seemed to have been rather surprised by this assessment, and he turned to Han Li with a surprised expression, as did Bai Suyuan.

As for Han Li himself, he wasn't disappointed at all after hearing this verdict, and he gave Deputy Dao Lord Xiong a slight nod, then made his way down from the stone platform, following which the platform quickly reverted back to its original state.

Deputy Dao Lord Xiong was just about to depart when Qi Liang suddenly said, "Please wait a moment, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong. This is Bai Suyuan, and she's a descendant of Elder Bai Fengyi. She has also come here to join our sect, so please examine her aptitude as well."

Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's patience was clearly running thin, and his expression only eased slightly upon hearing mention of Bai Fengyi.

"Alright, but make it quick!" He took a glance at Bai Suyuan, then cast another incantation seal.

Once again, the stone pillars in the hall began to radiate dazzling azure light, and the massive ball of light reappeared around the stone platform.

Bai Suyuan took a deep breath before stepping onto the platform, and countless runes emerged within the ball of light.

However, in contrast with the runes that had appeared for Han Li, all of the runes on this occasion were silver in color and had a glittering and translucent quality to them.

The entire hall began to rumble violently, and all of the spirit beast statues engraved onto the stone pillars let loose ferocious roars, while powerful energy fluctuated surged throughout the hall.

"What's going on?"

Both Qi Liang and Han Li were quite startled by this turn of events, and they turned their attention toward Bai Suyuan in unison.

Meanwhile, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong had abruptly risen to his feet, and an excited look had appeared in his eyes.

The ball of light on the stone platform quickly faded, while the countless silver runes converged in one place to form a silver humanoid figure.

The figure was of an extremely bright silver color, resembling a bright moon hanging in the night sky.

The most eye-catching thing about it was that there were seven bright specks of light shining on its chest.

Deputy Dao Lord Xiong rushed onto the stone platform in a flash as he declared with an excited expression, "She possesses the legendary Moonlight Immortal Physique and had seven immortal acupoints opened from birth!"

A thought then occurred to him, and he immediately released an incantation seal, upon which all of the light on the stone platform faded alongside the silver humanoid figure, and Bai Suyuan was revealed again.

All of a sudden, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's attitude had become extremely amicable and benevolent, and he said in a warm voice, "Your name is Bai Suyuan, right? As expected of a descendant of Elder Bai Fengyi's, your aptitude is truly exceptional."

"That's correct. Bai Suyuan pays her respects to Deputy Dao Lord Xiong."

Bai Suyuan had been enveloped by a burst of enormous power that had cut off her senses just now, so she had no idea what had just happened, but she could tell from Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's reaction that she seemed to have displayed some remarkable aptitude.

"I can tell that you're still quite young. How many years have you been cultivating for?" Deputy Dao Lord Xiong asked.

"I began cultivating at three years of age, and I've been cultivating for over 50 years up to this point," Bai Suyuan replied.

Both Han Li and Qi Liang were quite taken aback to hear this, but Deputy Dao Lord Xiong merely nodded in response, seemingly not surprised by this answer at all.

Indeed, with her Moonlight Immortal Physique and seven innately awakened immortal acupoints, it wasn't all that remarkable for her to have reached the late-Deity Transformation Stage in less than 60 years of cultivation.

As long as she had access to the right cultivation arts and resources, he was confident that he could elevate her all the way to the True Immortal Stage within 1,000 years.

Given her exceptional aptitude, it was even possible that she could reach the Golden Immortal Stage in the future.

Chapter 188: Disciple to a Golden Immortal

"Bai Suyuan, given your outstanding aptitude, you won't have to start off as an outer sect disciple like all other new disciples. Let me ask you this: are you willing to accept me as your master and become a direct disciple of mine?" Deputy Dao Lord Xiong asked in a gentle voice?

Bai Suyuan's mouth gaped open in shock, and she was completely rooted to the spot.

Right at this moment, a hazy voice suddenly rang out before spreading through the hall like waves of gentle, rippling water. "Xiong Shan, you're cultivating the laws of metal, while this child possesses the Moonlight Immortal Physique, so you're not suitable to serve as her mentor. Hand her over to me instead."

As soon as Han Li heard this voice, he felt as if had fallen into a boundless sea of flowers. His mouth and nose were completely filled with a floral aroma that intoxicated the mind.

However, he was able to instantly return to his senses thanks to a sudden jolt from his enormous spiritual sense.

A hint of frustration flashed through Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's eyes in the wake of this turn of events, but he quickly regained his composure.

Right at this moment, a ball of white light appeared out of thin air within the hall, and it was so bright that everyone was forced to avert their eyes.

In the next instant, the white light abruptly vanished, and a young woman in a palace dress appeared on the stone platform.

The woman appeared to be in her thirties with an oval face and a set of features that looked as if they had been taken straight from a masterful piece of artwork. In particular, her eyes were extremely seductive, and her tight-fitting white robe hugged her voluptuous curves to perfection.

Her entire body was giving off an overwhelming aura of seduction, captivating the beholder and lulling them into countless lustful fantasies.

Han Li was stunned by the woman's incredibly seductive qualities, and he immediately averted his gaze, not daring to look at her any longer. At the same time, he began to circulate his spiritual sense, and a cool and refreshing sensation spread through his mind, snapping him back to his senses.

"Xiong Shan pays his respects to Dao Lord Yun," Deputy Dao Lord Xiong greeted as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Han Li was initially rather surprised to hear this, but he quickly realized that this was only to be expected. After all, only one of the 13 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao could possess such a terrifyingly seductive aura.

He immediately extended a salute as well, while Qi Liang had already lowered his head in a deep bow, not daring to look at the white-robed woman at all.

Meanwhile, Bai Suyuan was staring at the woman in a complete daze, clearly already completely intoxicated by the woman's seductive aura.

It seemed that her seduction was effective on both men and women.

With a wave of the woman's sleeve, a hint of clarity immediately returned to Bai Suyuan's eyes.

She immediately noticed that Han Li and the others were all saluting the woman, and she hurriedly leaned forward to extend a bow as well, but the white-robed woman caught her before she could do so. "There's no need for such formalities, my child."

The woman gently pulled Bai Suyuan closer to her, and the more she looked at Bai Suyuan, the more pleased she became.

"Your name is Suyuan, right? Your Moonlight Immortal Physique pairs up quite nicely with my cultivation. Are you willing to become my disciple and cultivate under me?" the woman asked in a gentle voice.

Bai Suyuan immediately extended a deep bow upon hearing this. "I am. Suyuan pays her respects to her mistress."

"Great! From this day forth, you will be my fifth direct disciple. This fortune bracelet is a spirit treasure that I obtained some years ago, and I'm gifting it to you now in the hope that it'll protect you in your time of need."

A pleased smile appeared on the woman's face as she flipped a hand over to produce a white jade bracelet before slipping it onto Bai Suyuan's wrist. The bracelet was giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations, indicating that it was a top-grade spirit treasure.

Bai Suyuan was ecstatic, and she hurriedly expressed her gratitude. "Thank you, Mistress!"

Only then did the white-robed young woman turn to Deputy Dao Lord Xiong as she said, "I'm taking this child with me. Do you have any objections, Xiong Shan?"

"Of course now," Xiong Shan hurriedly replied with a smile. "Your cultivation art its a perfect match for her, so she's naturally much better off with you."

A faint smile appeared on the white-robed young woman, and she turned to Han Li and Qi Liang, with her gaze lingering momentarily on the former.

Xiong Shan noticed the white-robed young woman's gaze, and he immediately explained, "He's an itinerant cultivator by the name of Li Feiyu, and he's joined our sect using Blaze Dragon Token. I've just examined his aptitude."

The white-robed woman's gaze only lingered on Han Li for a moment before looking away in a disinterested manner as she said in a casual voice, "I see. I'll leave these matters to you then."

"Let's go, Suyuan." She latched onto Bai Suyuan's hand as she spoke, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of gentle white light that enveloped both of them.

Bai Suyuan hurriedly turned to Han Li, but in the next instant, her vision was obscured by a flash of white light.

The white light then vanished in an instant, as did Bai Suyuan and the white-robed woman.

Xiong Shan's smile instantly faded following the woman's departure, and he turned to leave with a dark look on his face.

"Deputy Dao Lord Xiong, what role is to be assigned to Fellow Daoist Li?" Qi Liang hurriedly asked.

"Do I have to tell you how to do everything? Just get him to serve as an ordinary attendant in the inner sect!" Xiong Shan replied in a cold voice, paying no heed to whether he was offending Han Li with his abrasive demeanor.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden light.

Following Xiong Shan's departure, Han Li fell into deep thought with an absentminded look on his face.

"Everyone's fate is different on the path of cultivation. It's already a remarkable feat that you were able to reach the True Immortal Stage, so there's no need to be envious of others," Elder Qi cautioned.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he knew that Qi Liang had most likely misconstrued his contemplative expression, but he didn't bother to explain himself, merely nodding in response.

"Seeing as Deputy Dao Lord Xiong has instructed me to instate you as an inner sect attendant, I must inform you of some of the sect's rules. As for some of the more specific details, I'll update you on that later," Qi Liang said with a smile.

"Thank you, Elder Qi. May I ask what duties I have to perform as an attendant elder of the inner sect?" Han Li asked.

"There are two options available to you, the first of which is to complete three regular elder missions released by the sect every century. Of course, if you have sufficient merit points to offset the missions, then you won't have to complete them," Qi Liang explained.

"What's the second option?" Han Li asked.

"The second option is to do what I'm doing and perform some daily duties in a certain pavilion in the sect. All you need to do is perform these duties for one decade out of every century. However, in order to not affect their cultivation, many elders choose to perform these duties for 100 consecutive years so that they can spend the next 900 years focusing on cultivation," Qi Liang replied.

"If they don't want their duties to get in the way of their cultivation, then why don't they just use merit points to exempt themselves from those duties instead?" Han Li asked.

"Firstly, merit points are extremely precious to the elders and disciple of the Blaze Dragon Dao, so no one is willing to use them to offset missions. Secondly, the sect doesn't permit one to use their merit points to exempt oneself from their daily administrative duties," Qi Liang explained.

"If these merit points are considered to be so precious, then they must be very difficult to obtain, right, Elder Qi?" Han Li asked with a contemplative expression.

"Indeed. Most of the sect's disciples can generally only earn some accolade points by tending to spirit farms for several years at a time, whereas elders can earn some merit points by performing monthly administrative duties," Qi Liang replied with a nod.

"Then what if I choose to complete regular elder missions instead?" Han Li asked.

"Each regular elder mission requires one to perform different tasks, and they also vary in difficulty, so the number of merit points that can be earned from completing each mission naturally varies as well. Generally speaking, mission rewards range from around a dozen to over 100 merit points.

“Of course, if you make some special contributions to the sect, then you'll be rewarded with additional merit points. You'll become more familiar with this system once you've been in the inner sect for a while," Qi Liang explained in a patient manner.

After some contemplation, Han Li decided, "In that case, I think I'll select the first option for my first 100 years in the sect."

"That's the option that the majority of new elders choose. Come with me. The Abode Assignment Palace just so happens to be nearby as well. I'll take you there so you can select a cave abode," Qi Liang said with a smile.

He led Han Li out of the Ostentatious Palace as he spoke, then rose up into the air before flying toward a nearby mountain.

In contrast with the mountain where the Ostentatious Palace was situated, this mountain was far more lively and bustling.

A cluster of red buildings that took up a massive area had been constructed on the mountain summit, with hundreds of palatial structures among them. The giant plaza outside wasn't exactly completely packed, but there was definitely a huge number of people on it.

Streaks of light could occasionally be seen whizzing through the air, either descending onto or flying up from the plaza.

"As the name suggests, the elders and disciples of the Abode Assignment Palace oversee cave abode assignment duties, as well as the distribution of resources, so it's always one of the busiest places in the entire inner sect," Qi Liang introduced to Han Li after the two of them landed on the plaza.

"No wonder there are so many people here. Looks like you'll have to wait with me for quite some time," Han Li said in an apologetic manner.

"Not to worry. I'm close friends with Elder Yu of the Abode Assignment Palace, so I can take you to see him right away," Qi Liang replied with a smile.

"Thank you, Elder Qi."

As the two of them passed through the plaza, many of the disciples would greet Qi Liang upon seeing the elder robes that he was wearing, and Qi Liang would respond with slight nods of acknowledgement.

Through the palace gates, Han Li could see that this was indeed an extremely busy place.

Under Qi Liang's guidance, Han Li was taken to a hall situated in the deepest part of the area.

At this moment, there were seven or eight people in the hall engaged in a spirited discussion, seemingly arguing about something.

"Brother Yu!" Qi Liang called out as he stepped into the hall with Han Li.

A large head with a bright, rosy complexion emerged from behind the seven or eight arguing figures, and the head took a glance at Qi Liang and Han Li, then disappeared back behind the small crowd, immediately following which a loud voice rang out.

"Alright, all of you can go back for now. Come back tomorrow and I'll make a decision on your cave abode reassignment requests."

The disciples could only cease their argument upon hearing this, then took their leave before exiting the hall.

Elder Yu was a portly man with a large head, and he said, "It's been quite a while since you paid me a visit. Who's this?"

Despite his unremarkable appearance, Han Li could sense that Elder Yu was also a True Immortal cultivator.

Chapter 189: Cave Abode and Mountain Guardian Beast

"Our Heavenly Star Palace isn't as busy as your Abode Assignment Palace, but I still don't get enough spare time to come and visit you whenever I please. It just so happens to be the case that we've welcomed a new elder into our sect. His name is Li Feiyu, and I've brought him here to complete the registration process and pick out a cave abode," Qi Liang replied with a smile.

"I see. That's not a problem at all. Greetings, Elder Li, my name is Yu Xiansheng, and I currently serve as the attendant elder of the Abode Assignment Palace. I'll get you registered right away," Elder Yu said with a smile

"Thank you, Elder Yu," Han Li hurriedly said.

Yu Xiansheng waved a hand in response, then summoned a brush that appeared as if it had been carved out of gold and jade with a flick of his wrist. He then made his way over to the table and began to quickly write something down onto a thick book that was glowing with azure light.

As he was writing, Yu Xiansheng suddenly paused for a moment, then raised his head as he asked, "Have you decided what you're going to do to fulfill your elder duties for the first 100 years, Elder Li?"

"I'll complete three regular elder missions," Han Li replied.

Yu Xiansheng seemed to have already anticipated this answer, and he nodded in response before continuing in his writing.

A short while later, Yu Xiansheng looked up again as he said, "The registration is complete. According to the rules of our sect, all inner sect elders and direct disciples are entitled to a mountain of their own. Hence, it's time for you to select a mountain to construct your cave abode on, Elder Li."

He then swept a sleeve through the air, and a green scroll that was over three feet in length appeared before him amid a flash of green light.

Immediately thereafter, the scroll began to slowly unfurl itself, revealing a piece of artwork depicting a stretch of scenery.

Han Li swept his gaze over the piece of artwork to find that it was extremely complex, complete with countless mountains and bodies of water.

Initially, he didn't find the scroll to be all that remarkable, but as soon as his gaze lingered for a moment one of the mountains, that section of the artwork would instantly expand before his eyes and become more vibrant and lifelike, as if he had been transported to the actual location, much to his amazement.

"This Inkspirit Scenic Scroll contains an artwork that depicts our Bell Toll Mountain Range. However, the mountain range is too vast to be encompassed in a single frame, so you're only seeing a part of the mountain range right now. If you want to see other areas, then you'll have to extend the scroll further," Yu Xiansheng explained with a smile.

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and the image in the scroll began to slowly move to reveal more of the landscape.

As more and more areas were revealed, Han Li noticed that different areas on the artwork had different background colors. Some were blue, some were green, some were golden, and some were pitch-black, as if ink had been inadvertently poured onto those areas.

There were also some areas that didn't display a real-life image, even after Han Li's gaze had lingered on them for a while.

"Why do these areas have different background colors? Do they serve different purposes?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The golden areas in the scroll depict the mountains where some of the most integral palaces of the sect are situated, and they're mostly distributed throughout the central region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, such as the Ostentatious Palace, the Merit Conveyance Palace, and the Abode Assignment Palace, while the silver areas are where the cave abodes of the direct disciples are situated," Yu Xiansheng explained.

He then swept his sleeve through the air once again, and the image in the scroll moved several hundred feet to the right before stopping at a blue area.

"The green area that you saw earlier was the western region of the mountain range, where the cave abodes of all of the outer sect elders and disciples are situated, while this blue area depicts the eastern region of the mountain range, where the cave abodes of all of the inner sect disciples and elders are.

“As for those gray areas, they mark out the sect's trial venues, such as the Snowmelt Forest and the Inexplicable Valley, and barring certain special circumstances, those areas are generally closed off to everyone," Yu Xiansheng continued.

"Are those black areas the restricted areas of the sect?" Han Li asked.

Yu Xiansheng nodded in response. "That's right. Aside from the dao lords and deputy dao lords, only a select few core elders and direct disciples are permitted to enter those areas. There are powerful restrictions set up around all of those areas, so there's no way you'll inadvertently stumble into them."

"I see. I've only just arrived in the sect, and I know next to nothing about this place. I have no idea which mountain to choose among this vast selection. Can you make some recommendations, Elder Yu?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"Of course," Yu Xiansheng replied with a nod.

He swept his sleeve through the air once again as he spoke, and the image in the green scroll abruptly accelerated in its movement, instantly traveling over 100 feet to reveal several mountains that extended all the way up into the clouds.

"This Sun Mountain Peak is only only around 100,000 kilometers in radius, but there's a spirit spring of an exceptional caliber on it, thereby allowing the mountain to naturally gather the world's origin qi, making it an exceptional place for cultivation. Roughly 250,000 kilometers away is this Sundrum Peak, which takes up a slightly larger area, but it has no spirit spring," Yu Xiansheng introduced as he pointed at two of the mountains on the scroll.

"It doesn't really concern me whether a mountain has a spirit spring or not. Is there a more peaceful and secluded mountain available?" Han Li asked.

After a moment of deliberation, Yu Xiansheng swept his sleeve through the air again, and this time, the image in the scroll moved for close to 1,000 feet before stopping.

"This Dawnfall Peak is situated in a rather secluded location, and it's also quite a short mountain. If I recall correctly, no elder has ever resided there. It's surrounded by many plains and valleys, so it's a lot more quiet than the other mountains. If you'd like to select this mountain, then you'll have to construct your own cave abode there," Yu Xiansheng said as he pointed at the scroll.

Han Li's gaze followed Yu Xiansheng's finger, and he stared at the Dawnfall Peak for a while without saying anything, seemingly not quite satisfied with the location.

Yu Xiansheng exchanged a glance with Qi Liang upon seeing this, then said, "That's alright, let's keep looking."

With that, he continued to introduce other mountains to Han Li.

Some time later, right as Yu Xiansheng was gradually losing his patience, Han Li's gaze was suddenly drawn to a corner of the scroll, where a lone mountain was standing, and he asked, "Elder Yu, can I choose this mountain?"

A peculiar look appeared on Qi Liang's face at the sight of Han Li's selection, and he asked, "You want to choose the Crimson Dawn Peak?"

Han Li noticed Qi Liang's reaction, and he asked, "Is there something wrong with this mountain?"

Before Qi Liang had a chance to reply, Yu Xiansheng explained, "No, there's nothing wrong with the mountain. It was previously occupied by another elder, and it's been vacant ever since that elder's passing. I suppose it's a good choice, considering it already has a cave abode completely with a medicine farm and a beast stable, all it needs is to be tidied up a little. You can go to the Cattail Spirit Valley later to pick out some servants to do that for you."

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, but he didn't say anything further, settling on this mountain as he expressed his gratitude to Yu Xiansheng.

With a flick of his wrist, a small seal appeared in Yu Xiansheng's hand, and he pressed the seal down onto the scroll where the Crimson Dawn Peak was situated.

As soon as the seal made contact with the scroll, a burst of peculiar fluctuations immediately swept over the Crimson Dawn Peak and the surrounding area, and when Han Li set his gaze upon, he discovered that he was no longer able to see a real-life image of the area.

Yu Xiansheng stowed the seal away, then flipped a hand over to produce a crimson badge and a storage bracelet as he smiled and said, "Alright, the Crimson Dawn Peak and the area close to 300,000 kilometers in radius belongs to you now, Elder Li. Here's your attendant elder badge and a storage bracelet that contains some information and resources."

Han Li accepted the two items and stowed the storage bracelet away before carefully inspecting the elder badge.

It was a palm-sized badge that seemed to have been constructed from a jade-like material, and the visage of a strange dragon was engraved onto one side, while the other side carried the word "Elder" inscribed in seal script.

"This elder badge is an important identification token, and it'll be required in many instances in our sect. In order to prevent it from being stolen, you need to mark it with your blood essence. The badge also contains 100 free merit points given out to all new elders, so make sure to keep it safe," Qi Liang said.

Han Li nodded in response, then brought his index and middle fingers together before tapping them onto the badge.

A burst of light flashed from his fingertips, and a drop of golden blood essence instantly emerged before quickly seeping into the badge.

A peculiar golden pattern instantly appeared on the surface of the badge amid a flash of light, and the pattern was giving off an aura that was unique to Han Li.

He then injected his spiritual sense into the badge, and sure enough, there were already 100 merit points inside.

"Elder Li, would you like me to take you to the Cattail Spirit Valley to select some servants, or to the Beast Rearing Fields to select a mountain guardian beast?" Qi Liang asked.

"What's a mountain guardian beast?" Han Li asked.

"They are spirit beasts that had been tamed by the sect. Given your cultivation base and your status as an inner sect elder, you're entitled to Body Integration Stage spirit beast to guard your mountain and cave abode," Qi Liang explained.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, and he asked, "Will I need to spend merit points for such a beast?"

"No, the mountain guardian beast is gifted to you by the sect free of charge, just like the servants. Most of the servants are outer sect disciples who wish to serve a True Immortal. It looks like you're quite interested in a mountain guardian beast, so how about I take you to the Beast Rearing Fields first?" Qi Liang proposed.

"I'm just intrigued as I've never heard of something like this before. Back when I was selecting my mountain, I noticed that the Imperial Dragon Peak that the Merit Conveyance Palace is situated on isn't too far away from here. I'd like to go and take a look there first," Han Li said.

Qi Liang faltered slightly upon hearing this, then said, "You're quite observant to have noticed that, Elder Li. The Imperial Dragon Peak appears to be not far away on the map, but it's actually quite some distance away in our Bell Toll Mountain Range. Are you sure you don't want to have everything organized in your cave abode first before you go to the Merit Conveyance Palace?"

"Truth be told, I've been yearning to see the scriptures in the Merit Conveyance Palace for a long time, and now that I've finally managed to join the sect, I simply can't suppress the urge to want to go and take a look there first," Han Li replied as he intentionally put on a bashful expression.

Chapter 190: Formless True Axis Scripture

Qi Liang was quite amused to hear this, and he said, "In that case, I'll take you to the Imperial Dragon Peak first."

Han Li hurriedly waved his hands as he refused, "I've already troubled you far too much today, Elder Qi. Now that I have this elder badge, I'll be able to take care of everything else on my own. You and Elder Yu haven't met for quite some time, so why don't you take the time to catch up and have a good chat?"

"That's very thoughtful of you, Elder Li," Yu Xiansheng chuckled. "The storage bracelet that I just gave you contains a map of our Blaze Dragon Dao, so you won't get lost."

Qi Liang hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then said, "In that case, I'll leave you to yourself, Elder Li. If you get some spare time, you can come and pay my Heavenly Star Palace a visit."

"I'll be sure to do so," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in a salute before departing.

Following his departure, a hint of mockery appeared on Yu Xiansheng's face as he mused, "Some people just don't know their limits. All of these new elders think that regular elder missions are easy to complete. Only after experiencing hardships will they come to realize that the most consistent long-term strategy is to oversee a palace like us."

Qi Liang merely smiled in response, neither agreeing nor disagreeing with this sentiment.

Meanwhile, Han Li emerged from the palace and arrived on the plaza outside, then flipped a hand over to pull the map of the Blaze Dragon Dao out of the storage bracelet that had just been given to him by Yu Xiansheng. After inspecting it closely for a moment, he stowed the map away again.

After that, he flipped his hand over again to pull out a jade slip that contained some information about all of the Blaze Dragon Dao's palaces, then pressed the jade slip against his own glabella.

Moments later, he stowed the jade slip away before abruptly rising up into the sky as a streak of azure light.

As Han Li was flying through the air, he was also taking the opportunity to inspect the landscape beneath him.

The undulating mountains were like waves that stretched as far as the eyes could see, and with the exceptions of some locations where sect palaces and pavilions were situated, the majority of the landscape was covered by a blanket of snow, giving the entire area the appearance of a glacial realm.

However, the rivers and creeks that passed through the mountain range were still slowly flowing, remaining unfrozen despite the low temperatures.

They were like a series of gentle and slow-moving pythons that were slithering through the mountain range.

Han Li had already seen several of the major rivers while on the way to the Blaze Dragon Dao, but their names were different from the names that they were referred to as here, and they were only the downstream tail-ends of those rivers.

Constantly staring at a monotonous white landscape proved to be quite disconcerting over time, so Han Li redirected his gaze to the sky instead as he flew toward the Imperial Dragon Peak at full speed.

……

15 minutes later.

The Imperial Dragon Peak was one of the tallest and most majestic mountains in the entire Bell Toll Mountain Range. At the same time, it was also one of the Blaze Dragon Dao's most important mountains. It was protected by an array all year round, and whenever any situations arose, the arrays would instantly be activated. Furthermore, there was more than one True Immortal cultivator stationed inside at all times.

The entirety of the Imperial Dragon Peak was riddled with dense clusters of buildings from head to toe, all of which housed the countless cultivation arts and secret techniques of the sect.

The buildings at the foot of the mountain were collectively known as the scripture library, and the scriptures they contained catered toward outer sect elders and disciples, whereas the buildings halfway up the mountain were known as the inner tome library, and they catered toward inner sect elders and disciples.

These two locations housed a vast number of books on an extremely diverse range of topics, and elders and disciples could find what they wanted through the library catalogs, then exchange for those scriptures using merit points.

There was only a single building on the mountain summit named the Merit Conveyance Palace, and it catered exclusively toward inner sect elders and direct disciples, housing the most important scriptures in the entire sect.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light descended out of the sky and onto the white jade plaza in front of the palace.

It was none other than Han Li, and after landing on the plaza, he took a moment to adjust his robes, which were slightly disheveled from his flight, then raised his head to look at the palace up ahead.

The Merit Conveyance Palace was very unremarkable in appearance, with seemingly no extra thought or care put into its construction, but upon closer inspection, one would quickly discover that there was more to the palace than met the eye.

Firstly, the Merit Conveyance Palace wasn't constructed from wooden or stone materials. Instead, the building consisted entirely of a special type of metal. Secondly, there were all types of complex runes engraved onto the outer walls and eaves of the palace, giving it a profound and mystical appearance.

Han Li speculated that this palace itself was most likely an extremely powerful spirit treasure, perhaps even an Acquired Immortal Treasure.

If that really were the case, then this would truly be an extraordinary spectacle.

After inspecting the building for a moment, he cast aside this train of thought before making his way inside.

Upon entering the palace, Han Li was surprised to find that even though there were no light sources such as lamps or candles inside, it was somehow even brighter in the palace than outside.

After looking around the hall, he discovered that aside from the wall that the door was attached to, the other three walls had been split up into countless metal grids, all of which were flashing with spiritual light and tightly sealed behind independent restrictions.

Directly across from him was a middle-aged man with graying hair huddled over a table. His attention was focused entirely on an ancient book with a green color and yellow pages, and he didn't seem to have noticed Han Li at all.

Han Li approached the man and was just about to say something when he noticed out of the corner of his eye that the entire book had been written in golden seal text.

The man looked up to reveal a set of calm features, and he said, "Judging from your attire, you're not an inner sect elder, nor are you a direct disciple, so what are you doing here?"

"I am Li Feiyu, and I was only just instated as an inner sect elder. I was in a hurry to get here, so I didn't get a chance to change into my elder robes," Han Li explained as he pulled out his elder badge before offering it to the man.

The middle-aged man accepted the badge and examined it for a moment, but didn't immediately return it to Han Li as he smiled and cupped his fist in a welcoming salute.

"It's fine. The first thing that many of the new elders like to do after joining the sect is to visit the Imperial Dragon Peak, so this is no surprise. My name is Fang Zhuan, and I am the attendant elder overseeing the Merit Conveyance Palace at the moment."

Han Li immediately returned the salute, and his expression remained completely unchanged, but he was feeling a little perplexed.

Fang Zhuan was only a Grand Ascension cultivator, so why was it that he had been assigned with such an important role?

"Have you come here to exchange for some cultivation arts or secret techniques? I don't mean to rain on your parade, but given that you've only just joined the sect, I'm assuming you only have 100 merit points, right? 100 merit points can perhaps get you a decent cultivation art from the inner tome library, but in here..." Fang Zhuan's voice trailed off here, but it was clear what he was implying.

"Thank you for the tip, Elder Fang. I've only come here this time to browse the catalog of cultivation arts so I know how many merit points I have to aim for," Han Li replied.

Fang Zhuan nodded in response, then asked, "I see. May I ask which cultivation art you'd like to inquire about?"

"Prior to joining the sect, I had already heard that our Blaze Dragon Dao had a cultivation art that could allow one to cultivate the laws of time. How many merit points will be required for that cultivation art?" Han Li asked.

Fang Zhuan seemed to have been rather taken aback to hear this, and he asked, "You mean the Formless True Axis Scripture?"

"Is there something wrong?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Instead of answering Han Li's question, Fang Zhuan asked, "Have you looked into the Formless True Axis Scripture at all prior to this?"

"I'm afraid not. Please enlighten me, Elder Fang," Han Li replied.

"Due to the fact that the cultivation art is related to the laws of time, it's considered to be one of the Blaze Dragon Dao's top three cultivation arts, but in reality, no one in the Blaze Dragon Dao has ever managed to attain the laws of time through this cultivation art. Almost everyone who decided to pursue the cultivation art gave up at the first level and switched to other cultivation arts," Fang Zhuan explained.

Han Li nodded in response, then asked in a casual voice, "I see. May I ask how many merit points are required to exchange for the Formless True Axis Scripture?"

"You still want to exchange for the cultivation art, even though the practical success rate of cultivating it is zero?" Fang Zhuan asked with a perplexed expression.

"I've been yearning for this cultivation art for a long time, so I can't bear to just give up on it before at least giving it a try. If it doesn't work, I can always switch to something else," Han Li replied with a smile.

Fang Zhuan was silent for a moment, then said, "In that case, I won't try to dissuade you any further. The Formless True Axis Scripture is split up into three levels, and elders and disciples are only permitted to exchange for one level at a time. The first level only costs 90 merit points..."

"Only 90 merit points?" Han Li was very surprised to hear this, and he couldn't help but cut Fang Zhuan off for confirmation.

"That's right, the first level only costs 90 merit points. Due to the special circumstances surrounding the cultivation art, it's the least popular of the sect's top three cultivation arts by far, so it's far cheaper than the other two," Fang Zhuan explained.

"Then what about the other two levels?" Han Li asked.

"The second level will cost 9,000 merit points, and it's only accessible to direct disciples and inner sect elders. As for the third level, that's only accessible to the dao lords and deputy dao lords, and it'll cost 900,000 merit points," Fang Zhuan replied.

"That's an extremely steep hike in price," Han Li mused.

"The reason why the first level is so easily accessible and so cheap is because the sect is hoping that someday, one of the sect's disciples will actually be able to attain the laws of time through it. Having said that, like I mentioned, no one has ever managed to succeed in this endeavor, so it's become even less popular over time," Fang Zhuan explained.

"Thank you for informing me of all of this, Elder Fang. I would still like to exchange for the first level of the Formless True Axis Scripture," Han Li said.

"Alright, if you've already made up your mind, then please wait for a moment," Fang Zhuan replied with a nod, then turned around and made his way toward the metal grids behind him.

Chapter 191: Servants

With a flick of his wrist, a round, palm-sized golden badge appeared in Fang Zhuan's grasp amid a flash of golden light.

The badge was riddled with runes, and it was made from the exact same material as the metal grids.

He chanted a brief incantation while making a hand seal with his other hand, and all of the spirit patterns on the golden badge instantly lit up, following which it released a beam of golden light straight onto one of the metal grids on the wall.

The layer of spiritual light enshrouding the grid rippled like water momentarily, following which a small metal box flew out of the wall before landing in Fang Zhuan's grasp.

He pressed his golden badge onto the box, and the latter immediately began to glow with bright golden light, forming a spherical light barrier that enveloped the entire box within.

Han Li could see golden runes constantly flashing over the light barrier like a series of miniature golden dragons, giving off an extremely peculiar aura in the process.

Moments later, the spherical light barrier abruptly faded, as did the golden light radiating from the box.

Immediately thereafter, the box slowly flew back into the grid on the wall, where it was sealed once again amid a flash of spiritual light, leaving only the golden badge continuing to hover in mid-air.

The box wasn't opened at all throughout this entire process.

It seemed that even though Fang Zhuan was serving as the attendant elder overseeing this place, even he was unable to open the boxes that contained the scriptures. Instead, it appeared that the most that he could do was replicate the contents of the scriptures.

Fang Zhuan picked up Han Li's elder badge and placed it against his round metal badge, then chanted an incantation.

Both of the badges flashed in unison, then quickly returned to normal.

"Alright, the merit points in the badge have already been deducted, and your blood essence aura has also been recorded by this spirit note badge. You will be the only one who can access the cultivation art recorded inside. Do not attempt to replicate the contents inside under any circumstances, or you'll have to bear the consequences," Fang Zhuan cautioned as he handed both badges to Han Li.

"Thank you, Elder Fang," Han Li replied with a nod as he accepted the pair of badges.

Right at this moment, someone else made his way into the palace as he yelled, "Senior Martial Brother Fang!"

Fang Zhuan was clearly very familiar with this newcomer, and he smiled as he greeted, "Ah, Junior Martial Brother Gu. It's been a while since I last saw you. What can I help you with today?"

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this.

This appeared to have been a normal occurrence, but it was very perplexing in his eyes as the man with the Gu surname was a True Immortal cultivator, so why was it that he was referring to a Grand Ascension cultivator like Fang Zhuan as his senior martial brother?

Fang Zhuan seemed to have noticed the perplexed look in Han Li's eyes, and a hint of dejection flashed across his face.

"It appears you have a guest, so I won't take up any more of your time, Elder Fang," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

"Farewell, Elder Li. If you need anything else, you can come back at any time," Fang Zhuan replied with a nod.

Han Li was still rather perplexed as he stroked his own chin, then gave the two men a slight nod before departing.

After leaving the Merit Conveyance Palace, he had originally planned to return straight to his cave abode on the Crimson Dawn Peak, but a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he made his way to the nearby teleportation hall instead.

……

The Cattail Spirit Valley was situated in the westernmost region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, and it was a massive horn-shaped valley that was stuck between a pair of side branch mountain ranges that extended toward the south.

There was a type of plant by the name of the Cattail Spirit Herb growing here, which was capable of gathering the world's origin qi in small amounts, hence the name of the valley.

Due to the special properties of the Cattail Spirit Herb, it was often used to weave cushions , and for a low-grade cultivator, having access to such a cushion would significantly enhance their rate of cultivation.

Of course, all of the Cattail Spirit Herbs in the valley were considered to be the property of the sect, and disciples were strictly prohibited from picking them without permission.

This valley was a rather special place in the Blaze Dragon Dao as the outer sect disciples participating in the decennial inner sect trials would generally gather here, then be taken by an attendant elder to trial areas such as the Snowmelt Forest.

Only a tiny number of people were able to pass each trial to become inner sect disciples, while the rest either perished during the cruel trials, or emerged riddled with injuries to continue serving as ordinary outer sect disciples.

Each outer sect disciple only had one opportunity to participate in the trial in their lifetime, so if they were to fail, then that would mean that the status of inner sect disciple was forever out of reach.

The majority of these outer sect disciples that had come from all parts of the Ancient Cloud Continent actually possessed decent aptitude, considered to be prodigies in their own clans. Otherwise, they wouldn't have even been selected to become outer sect disciples of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

After failing the inner sect trials, these outer sect disciples naturally weren't willing to just give up cultivation altogether, so the vast majority of them would choose to sign contracts in the Cattail Spirit Palace, hoping that they would catch the eye of one of the Blaze Dragon Dao's True Immortals and be fortunate enough to become their servant.

In their eyes, being able to become the servant of a True Immortal was an enormous opportunity that would elevate them to completely new heights.

If they were to be granted some cultivation resources by the True Immortal that they served, then it was entirely possible for exceptions to be made for them to be accepted as inner sect disciples at some point in the future.

However, the vast majority of True Immortals already had their own servants, and most of them liked to choose people from their own clans. Hence, very few of them came to visit the Cattail Spirit Valley. Of course, female cultivators with exceptional looks stood a better chance of being chosen then others.

Even so, whenever it became known that a True Immortal was about to arrive in the valley, countless disciples would still flock to the valley to try their luck.

At this moment, there were already thousands of people gathered in the valley, and there were still more people arriving by the second.

Not long ago, an attendant elder of the Cattail Spirit Palace had just announced that a True Immortal was going to be arriving to pick out some servants soon, and that was the reason why so many outer sect disciples were present.

The valley was lined with thickets of Cattail Spirit Herbs that were situated at least 1,000 feet away from one another. These herbs had thick and strong stems and leaves that resembled swords, and there were dozens or even over 100 gray-robed cultivators standing or sitting on each thicket.

It seemed that each thicket of Cattail Spirit Herbs was a circle of its own that was clearly separated from all others.

The vast majority of these people were at the Foundation Establishment or Core Formation Stage, but of course, there were quite a few Nascent Soul Stage disciples as well. Even as they were awaiting the arrival of the True Immortal, they were still meditating, not willing to waste any time that could be used for cultivation.

At the entrance of the valley, a gray-robed, honest-looking young man who appeared to have been in his twenties with a crescent-shaped jade pendant hanging from his waist made his way into the crowd, accompanied by three companions.

A round-faced fatso among the trio of companions turned to the honest-looking young man as he suggested, "Yungui, we should find a spot where it'll be easier for us to be seen. That way, there's a higher chance that we'll be chosen."

The best locations at the entrance of the valley had already been taken over by groups that were led by Nascent Soul Stage disciples, and there were only some vacant spots available deeper in the valley.

The honest-looking young man nodded in response, then pointed at a nearby thicket that was over 100 feet in size as he said, "It looks like there's some space there."

However, as soon as he stepped onto the thicket, he was met with a forceful shoulder barge that sent him stumbling to the side, and he turned around to discover a burly young man who was built like a brick house.

"Well, well, well, if it isn't Young Master Yungui. Have you come to try and fight over spots with us again?" the burly young man sneered.

The honest-looking young man's hands instantly balled up into tight fists, but he ultimately chose not to retaliate.

The burly young man before him was called Sun Buzheng, and they had come from the same rural nation, namely the Late Age Nation.

The Meng Clan that Meng Yungui belonged to was once the cultivating clan that was controlling the nation from behind the scenes, while Sun Buzheng was a member of the Late Age Nation's imperial family. Back when they were both children, they had been very close friends.

However, the Sun Clan was later overthrown during a revolution, and the Meng Clan was also attacked by a foreign cultivating power at around the same time, falling into decline as a result.

Sun Buzheng's birth name was Sun Hao, and he had always thought that his nation had fallen due to the lack of action taken by the Meng Clan, so he had developed an extremely deep grudge against the Meng Clan. As a result, after he was reunited with Meng Yungui in the Blaze Dragon Dao, he regarded his former friend as a bitter enemy.

In the beginning, Meng Yungui tried to explain what had happened to Sun Buzheng, but the latter refused to listen, so Meng Yungui eventually gave up.

Whenever he was faced with Sun Buzheng's provocation, he would always choose to deescalate the altercation, but this only made Sun Buzheng even more furious.

"Let's go somewhere else," Meng Yungui said to his entourage, then began to make his way toward another nearby thicket.

"Meng Yungui, are you a man or not? You're always cowering like a turtle every single time, and it pisses me off!" Sun Buzheng roared.

He made no effort to keep his voice down, and all of the nearby disciples immediately had their attention drawn to the altercation. Among them was an ordinary-looking young man who was quite tall in stature.

He was standing on a large thicket with some other outer sect disciples seated in small groups nearby, while he was the only one that was on his own.

This person was naturally none other than Han Li, who had just arrived from the Merit Conveyance Palace.

As opposed to going straight to the attendant elder of the Cattail Spirit Palace to pick out some servants from the list of names, he decided to enter the valley and take a look for himself.

Even though selecting servants was only a trivial matter, he still didn't want to run the risk of having others plant spies beside him.

He had suppressed his own aura to the Core Formation Stage, so no one paid any heed to him, merely regarding him as another outer sect disciple who had come to try his luck.

He took a glance at the approaching Meng Yungui, then quickly withdrew his gaze.

Right at this moment, a cold voice rang out up ahead. "Everyone, piss off! I'm taking this spot!"

The voice belonged to a menacing middle-aged man who appeared to have been around 40 years of age, and he was followed by a pair of cultivators, one male and one female, both of whom clearly regarded him as their leader.

The man was a late-Core Formation cultivator, so his cultivation base definitely stood out among the many nearby Core Formation cultivators.

The thicket that Han Li was situated on was occupied mostly by early-Core Formation cultivators, so despite their reluctance to comply, they had no choice but to leave with sour expressions.

It didn't take long before Han Li was the only one left, and Meng Yungui stopped in his tracks as his brows furrowed slightly at the sight of Han Li.

"I don't recall ever seeing you before. You must be a newbie, right?" the middle-aged man asked in a cold voice.

"Indeed, I only joined the sect not too long ago, and I heard that a True Immortal was coming to select some servants soon, so I decided to come here and try my luck," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

"Ha! So you're another idiot with an inflated sense of self-worth!"

"He must think of himself as some type of young prodigy!"

A burst of raucous laughter instantly rang out at Han Li's expense.

Chapter 192: Selecting Servants

"Even a newbie like yourself should still know the rules! Senior Martial Brother Shen told you to piss off just now, so why are you still here? Are you deaf, or are you pretending to be deaf?" the thin man beside the menacing middle-aged man yelled.

"To think that a mere early-Core Formation cultivator like yourself dares to display such insolence! You must have a death wish!" the seductive female cultivator on the other side of the middle-aged man scoffed.

Han Li paid no heed to their insults as he remained seated on the ground with his legs crossed.

Right at this moment, Meng Yungui made his way over to Han Li as he said, "It's not wise to oppose these people just for the sake of pride, Fellow Daoist. Given their terrible personalities, there's no way they'd be chosen by the True Immortal anyway."

In the process, he had wedged himself between Han Li and the middle-aged man, and his three companions also joined him as well.

"Meng Yungui, if I were you, I would stay out of this matter rather than stand up for someone I don't even know. Don't think that I would back down just because you managed to reach the late-Core Formation Stage by a massive stroke of luck," the middle-aged man threatened in a cold voice.

Meng Yungui wasn't backing down in the slightest as he declared, "Shen Biao, you and Lu Heng have always been picking on the members of our Meng Clan, and I've been meaning to confront you about this. There's no time like the present to settle our differences."

Right at this moment, another voice suddenly rang out. "Such majesty and prestige! As expected of Young Master Meng! When did you pick up the habit of sticking your nose into random business that has nothing to do with you?"

Everyone turned to discover a handsome young man with an arm wound around a female cultivator's slender waist. He was accompanied by an entourage of about a dozen people, and his peak late-Core Formation Stage aura was on full display.

The middle-aged man was ecstatic to see the new arrival. "Senior Martial Brother Lu, you're finally here!"

The atmosphere in the nearby area immediately became rather tense, and all of the disciples who didn't want to get involved hurriedly backed away to create some space between themselves and the two opposing groups of cultivators.

Han Li heaved a resigned sigh upon seeing this.

He had merely chosen this spot to sit at random, and he didn't think that it would stir up such a far-reaching conflict.

The cultivators accompanying Lu Heng were all at the Core Formation Stage as well, and with Shen Biao's trio thrown into the mix, this was quite a formidable lineup. In contrast, Meng Yungui only had his three companions to back him up.

Fearful looks had appeared on the faces of the round-faced fatso and the other two disciples, but seeing as Meng Yungui was still standing firm, they remained resolute in their stances as well.

Right as this completely lopsided battle was about to commence, another voice suddenly rang out. "Where's the glory in bullying others with a numbers advantage? Why don't you count me in as well, Senior Martial Brother Lu?"

The person who had spoken was none other than Sun Buzheng, who had provoked Meng Yungui earlier. He immediately arrived at the scene of the altercation as well, and his aura indicated that he was also a late-Core Formation cultivator.

"Sun Buzheng, aren't you and Meng Yungui sworn enemies? Are you going to meddle in this matter as well?" Lu Heng asked in a cold voice.

Sun Buzheng was displaying no fear at all as he smiled and replied, "Meng Yungui and I will settle our differences another time, but in the meantime, I can't just stand by and watch you pick on my fellow brethren of the Late Age Nation!"

Han Li was rather intrigued by this turn of events.

Right at this moment, Meng Yungui's voice rang out beside his ears through voice transmission. "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist, we'll take on Lu Heng and the others on our own. You stay out of this so you don't get injured."

"If you're gonna fight, then hurry up!"

"What's the hold-up?"

"Taking bets now! I'm putting my money on Lu Heng!"

A large crowd had gathered to watch the unfolding altercation, and the scene was becoming quite rowdy.

Lu Heng pushed the beautiful woman beside him away, then raised a hand as he commanded, "Go!"

Shen Biao and the others immediately summoned their respective treasures upon receiving this command, preparing to engage Meng Yungui and his group in battle.

Meng Yungui and his entourage also responded in kind, and the two groups of cultivators were just about to clash when Han Li suddenly appeared between them in a flash, moving at such an incredible speed that it was as if he had teleported there.

Meng Yungui and the others looked on in astonishment as Han Li casually swept a sleeve through the air, and the dozen or so opposing cultivators, including Shen Biao, were all sent flying by a burst of invisible force, then crashed into the distant mountain face before falling unconscious.

The rowdy bystanders instantly fell silent as if they had each taken a punch to the gut, and all of them were rooted to the spot as they looked on with stunned expressions.

Lu Heng's hand was still outstretched as he stared at Han Li with utter bewilderment.

At this moment, he was no longer able to sense Han Li's aura at all, as if it were only a mere mortal standing before him.

Even the Nascent Soul Stage disciples at the entrance of the valley were all looking on in dumbfounded shock.

After a brief silence, a hint of realization abruptly appeared in Meng Yungui's eyes, and he was the first to snap back to his senses as he hurriedly fell to his knees.

"Disciple Meng Yungui pays his respects to the esteemed elder!"

Immediately thereafter, all of the thousands of disciples in the area also sank to their knees one after another.

Lu Heng's forehead was pressed firmly against the ground, and his entire body was already drenched in cold sweat.

Han Li paid no heed to Lu Heng as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a gentle breeze that lifted Meng Yungui to his feet. "My surname is Li. From now on, you can remain by my side as my servant."

Meng Yungui faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which an ecstatic look appeared on his face, but that was then quickly replaced by a hesitant expression.

"If you have some qualms, then feel free to express them," Han Li said.

A slightly embarrassed look appeared on Meng Yungui's face as he said, "Elder Li, I have a young sister who's only just reached 18 years of age and recently progressed to the Foundation Establishment Stage. Would you be able to accept her as your servant as well?"

A cold look appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "The pursuit of the Great Dao is a cruel and lonely endeavor. If you do not sever your ties with the mortal world, you won't be able to truly embark on that journey. Do you understand?"

Meng Yungui hurriedly cupped his fist in a salute as he replied, "I do, it's just that my sister is still young, and if I leave her to her own devices here, I'm afraid that she'll... I understand that I'm asking too much. My sincerest apologies, Elder Li, but I won't be able to serve by your side."

Everyone was completely bewildered to hear this. In their eyes, it was nothing short of incredible that someone had passed up the opportunity to become a servant to a True Immortal.

If one could become a servant to a True Immortal, even the slightest bequeathments from the True Immortal would be enough to benefit them immensely on their cultivation journey, and that wasn't even to mention how invaluable the guidance of a True Immortal would be in one's cultivation.

With that in mind, one had to have either been insane or downright stupid to turn down such an opportunity!

However, to everyone's astonishment, Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "The Great Dao has no tolerance for emotional and sentimental ties, but at the end of the day, we are still human. How many people can truly be completely heartless and devoid of emotion? I'll accept both you and your sister as my servants. On top of that, you can pick out eight more people to serve by my side."

Meng Yungui shuddered violently as if he had been struck by lightning upon hearing this, and he was staring at Han Li with incredulity in his eyes.

The surrounding crowd had also erupted into a frenzy and were chattering spiritedly among themselves.

Virtually everyone immediately turned to Meng Yungui with imploring looks in their eyes, as if he were a god that would decide whether they got to live or die.

Meanwhile, Han Li sat down onto the ground with his legs crossed and closed his eyes to meditate, seemingly truly giving Meng Yungui full rein over who he was going to choose.

After taking a moment to collect himself, Meng Yungui pointed to the person standing directly before him as he said, "Meng Xiong."

Meng Xiong was the name of the round-faced fatso that had always been by his side, and he was so excited that tears were already beginning to swim in his eyes.

"Meng Xiong, go and fetch Qianqian for me. Meng Yu, Meng Guang, Fang Yao..."

After instructing the fatso to get his sister, Meng Yungui called out another six names, two of whom were also from the Meng Clan, while the rest were simply on good terms with him.

All of those who had their names called began to weep with joy as they made their way over to Meng Yungui's side.

Only then did Han Li open his eyes and take a quick glance at the people that Meng Yungui had chosen.

Aside from Meng Yungui's sister, who wasn't here yet, the rest of them were all Core Formation cultivators.

Right at this moment, Meng Yungui made his way over to a certain person and gave them the last spot.

"Sun Buzheng..."

Sun Buzheng was completely incredulous at the sound of his own name coming out of Meng Yungui's voice, and he turned to his former good friend with a perplexed expression.

"I will tell you this once again, Sun Hao: I do not get to decide the fate of a nation, and there are many complex circumstances involved. However, I always have and will continue to regard you as my friend," Meng Yungui said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Tears began to well up in Sun Buzheng's eyes, and to conceal his embarrassment, he put on a displeased look as he corrected, "Don't call me Sun Hao, I changed my name to Sun Buzheng long ago!"

After everyone was selected, Han Li didn't say anything as he led Meng Yungui and the others straight to the Cattail Spirit Palace for registration, and they were followed by several thousand disciples who were clearly still not willing to give up.

Given Han Li's status and cultivation base, he could've easily chosen dozens or even hundreds of servants, but he had no intention of doing that.

Right as they emerged from the Cattail Spirit Hall, a crisp and pleasant voice rang out from within the crowd. "Big Brother!"

A young woman then darted her way through the crowd in an agile manner like a little red sparrow, arriving beside Meng Yungui before latching onto his arm, and she was followed immediately by Meng Xiong.

"Elder Li, this is my sister, Meng Qianqian. Qianqian, pay your respects to Elder Li," Meng Yungui introduced with a slightly bashful expression.

Meng Qianqian hurriedly released her brother's arm upon hearing this, and she extended a deep curtsey toward Han Li with curiosity brimming in her large eyes. "Qianqian pays her respects to Elder Li."

Han Li smiled as he nodded in response, and he noticed that she was wearing a crescent-shaped jade pendant on her waist that seemed to have been identical to Meng Yungui's.

Looking at Meng Qianqian, he couldn't help but think of his little sister, and a barely detectable hint of warmth flashed through his eyes.

This was one of the reasons why he had agreed to accept both of them as his servants.

"Take this fire spirit pendant. It's not exactly an immortal treasure, but it can be worn to enhance the rate of cultivation for someone using fire-attribute cultivation arts." Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a fiery red penannular jade pendant as he spoke, then handed it to Meng Qianqian.

Meng Qianqian was initially quite taken aback, but she then hurriedly accepted the pendant as she expressed her gratitude.

She then strung the jade pendant onto her waist right next to the crescent-shaped pendant, and as she began to walk, the pair of pendants clattered together to produce a crisp and pleasant sound, much to the envy of all of the surrounding onlookers.

Chapter 193: Mountain Guardian Beast

After registering his servants with the attendant elder at the Cattail Spirit Palace, he took them to the nearby teleportation hall, then returned to the Crimson Dawn Peak.

The Crimson Dawn Peak was a lone mountain that was tens of thousands of feet tall. It was quite secluded in location, so it was quite far away from the nearest teleportation hall.

Even before arriving on the mountain, everyone could see that it was glowing with a red sheen, and not only was there no snow on the mountain, it was covered in lush greenery, presenting a vibrant sight to behold.

This was Han Li's first time seeing the mountain, and he found this to be rather strange, so he immediately released his spiritual sense to inspect the mountain as he said to Meng Yungui and the others, "The Crimson Dawn Peak has been vacant for a very long time, and the previous restrictions and arrays set up here have already become defunct from lack of maintenance.

“On top of that, there's a natural fire miasma on the mountain that will have a slight negative impact on all of you over time. Take these Clear Forest Pills, and you'll be exempt from those negative effects."

He flipped a hand over to produce a white jade vial as he spoke, then handed it to Meng Yungui.

Meng Yungui carefully accepted the vial with both hands, then distributed the pills inside to everyone.

All of them were exchanging glances with one another while holding the pills, seemingly reluctant to take them.

These Clear Forest Pills were naturally next to worthless in Han Li's eyes, but they were extremely beneficial for Core Formation cultivators attempting breakthroughs to the Nascent Soul Stage, and it felt like a massive waste to be taking them just to ward off the fire miasma on the mountain.

"Do I have to repeat myself?" Han Li asked in an indifferent voice.

"Please forgive us, Senior Li."

Meng Yungui immediately led by example, swallowing his pill first, and everyone else quickly followed suit.

Meng Qianqian was just about to take her pill as well, but she was stopped by Han Li, who told her, "You're only at the Foundation Establishment, so you don't have to take this pill. That fire spirit pendant has the natural ability to ward off the fire miasma for you."

Meng Qianqian nodded in response, then stowed the pill away.

"From now on, perform your rightful duties, and I'll be sure to treat you well. For now, I have some other matters to take care of, so follow Meng Yungui's lead and go clean up the cave abode," Han Li instructed.

"Yes, Senior Li."

Meng Yungui and the others descended onto the Crimson Dawn Peak, while Han Li flew back to the teleportation hall on his own.

……

The Beast Rearing Fields were where the tamed demon beasts of the Blaze Dragon Dao were kept, and they took up a massive area. At the center of the fields was the Beast Rearing Palace, which presided over the surrounding area in a radius of hundreds of thousands of kilometers.

The fields were split up into different areas with different environments, such as mountains, rivers, forests, and swamps.

Such a diverse array of environments hadn't come into existence naturally. Instead, most of them had been artificially created by the Blaze Dragon Dao, and each area was enshrouded within restrictions of different sizes. Even during the day, the glowing restrictions of different colors were still clearly visible, and different areas contained different numbers of spirit beasts.

There were specialized beast-taming cultivators overseeing the Beast Rearing Fields, and most of the spirit beasts kept in the sect possessed certain useful abilities, such as the ability to act as steeds, guard cave abodes, track enemies, explore perilous regions, and even assist their owners in battle.

It was exactly because of this that many of the disciples of the sect would choose to rent one of these spirit beasts before carrying out missions, but only direct disciples and inner sect elders were entitled to permanent ownership over these spirit beasts.

There was a teleportation hall near the valley that the Beast Rearing Fields were situated in, and at this moment, there were many people entering and exiting the building, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

Upon emerging from the teleportation hall, Han Li took a quick glance at his surroundings before making his way into the valley.

The first thing that he saw in the valley was a spacious plaza, on one side of which stood several tall buildings. Among them was a large palace, which bore a plaque that read "Beast Rearing Fields''.

As soon as Han Li set foot in the valley, he was immediately greeted by a gray-robed young man. "Greetings, senior martial brother. Have you come to rent a spirit beast?"

The man had a round face and large ears, coupled with a pair of bright eyes, giving him a clever appearance.

Han Li flipped a hand over to show the young man his elder badge, and the latter hurriedly extended an apologetic salute.

"My apologies, Elder."

Han Li waved a dismissive hand as he said, "I've only recently joined the sect, and I've come here to select a mountain guardian beast for my cave abode."

"According to the rules of the sect, inner sect elders claiming a spirit beast for the first time can do so free of charge. However, I must first verify your identity. Please pardon my intrusion, Elder," the young man said as he extended an apologetic bow.

Han Li offered no verbal response as he handed his elder badge to the young man, who apologized once again before flipping a hand over to produce an azure jade tablet, which he pressed against Han Li's elder badge while quickly chanting an incantation.

A burst of azure light appeared over the surface of the jade tablet, forming a light barrier roughly the size of a washbasin.

"Thank you for your patience, Elder Li. Please come with me to select a spirit beast from the Beast Rearing Fields."

The young man handed Han Li's badge back to him in a respectful manner, then led the way to the fields.

"Given how massive this place is, it'll take an eternity to see all of the areas one by one. Is there any other way to examine the spirit beasts here?" Han Li asked.

"There is. Please come with me, Elder Li," the young man immediately replied, then led Han Li to a large palace.

At this moment, there were many people in the palace seeking to rent spirit beasts, so it was rather noisy. The young man led Han Li to a quiet room, then pulled out a pair of jade books.

"The Beast Rearing Fields are split up into the outer fields and the inner fields, the former of which houses over 16,300 types of spirit beasts, while the latter houses over 1,800 types. All of them are recorded in these two jade books," the young man explained.

Han Li accepted the jade books from the young man before injecting his spiritual sense into them.

Sure enough, there was a vast selection of spirit beasts available, all of which had their own unique traits, putting the marvels of nature on full display.

Han Li had originally planned to only take a short time selecting a spirit beast, but the more he saw, the more intrigued that he became, and only after browsing through almost the entire catalog of spirit beasts in the Beast Rearing Fields did he finally withdraw his spiritual sense from the pair of jade books.

The round-faced young man had remained patiently by Han Li's side this entire time, and he asked, "Have you picked out any candidates, Elder Li?"

"There are a few spirit beasts that I'm interested in. Let's go to the inner fields," Han Li replied with a nod as he returned the pair of jade books to the round-faced young man.

According to the catalog, the Beast Rearing Fields were home to only around 40 to 50 types of Body Integration Stage spirit beasts. This was no surprise, considering the more powerful a spirit beast was, the more difficult they were to tame.

For him, a Body Integration Stage spirit beast wasn't necessarily all that useful, so he had only come here to broaden his horizons, and because there was no reason to pass up something given to him for free.

There were most likely some areas of the Beast Rearing Fields that he couldn't access given his current status, and perhaps those areas could've even been home to Grand Ascension or True Immortal Stage demon beasts.

It didn't take long before Han Li and the young man appeared before a golden desert with a radius of close to 500 kilometers, and the entire desert was enshrouded under an enormous azure light barrier.

The young man summoned an azure jade badge, which he waved through the air to release a burst of azure light.

A short while later, a clear cry rang out as a tornado that was several thousand feet tall erupted straight into the heavens while quickly approaching Han Li's duo. Immediately thereafter, a giant golden-winged bird that was 700 to 800 feet in size emerged from the tornado, flapping its wings as it circled around in the air, sending fierce gusts of wind sweeping in all directions.

"This Golden-winged Azure Light Falcon is at the mid-Body Integration Stage, and it possesses a hint of the true spirit Golden-winged Great Falcon bloodline, granting it extremely impressive speed," the young man introduced.

Han Li nodded in response, then observed the bird for a moment longer before making his way to a nearby valley.

Inside this area was an enormous rhinoceros-like spirit beast, which had a body that was entirely as white and translucent as jade. It moved around in slow, lumbering steps, and with each step that it took, an extremely heavy thud would reverberate throughout the entire valley.

"This is a Moonview Jade Rhinoceros. It possesses mid-Body Integration Stage power and wields various earth-attribute abilities," the young man introduced.

After observing the rhinoceros for some time, Han Li made his way to a canyon, where another spirit beast was residing.

This was a griffin-like creature that was 200 to 300 feet in length and around 70 to 80 feet tall. Its entire lion-like body was covered in thick fur, yet its legs were tipped with sharp eagle-like talons.

What was most remarkable about the creature was that it had two heads, one of which was purple, while the other was red, and both of them were snarling in a menacing fashion.

"This Two-headed Griffin is only at the early-Body Integration Stage, yet it possesses powers of two different attributes, namely lightning and fire," the young man introduced.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression, then decided, "I'll take this one."

"Fantastic choice, Elder Li! This Two-headed Griffin isn't all that powerful right now, but it has the most potential out of all of the Body Integration Stage spirit beasts here," the young man said with a smile.

Han Li also smiled in response, offering no reply.

"This is the Two-headed Griffin's bonded badge. You won't need the badge to control this beast, but if you're going to give this to your servants, then it's best to be cautious. This spirit beast has already been tamed, but there's still a chance that it could become violent," the young man said as he flipped a hand over to produce a dark purple jade badge, which he handed to Han Li.

There was a layer of crimson light over the surface of the badge, upon which was the image of a miniature Two-headed Griffin, which was moving occasionally as if it were a living creature.

The Two-headed Griffin let loose a low roar as it stared intently at the dark purple badge.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out from the entrance of the canyon. "That griffin looks pretty good, Senior Martial Brother Ye."

Immediately thereafter, a group of seven to eight people descended into the area.

Aside from a square-faced outer sect disciple of the Beast Rearing Fields, everyone else in the group appeared to have been inner sect disciples.

They were led by a tall dark-skinned young man who appeared to be rather thin and frail, but had a sharp and piercing gleam in his eyes, and he was the only Grand Ascension cultivator of the group.

The person who had just spoken was a purple-haired man accompanying the dark-skinned young man, and there was a fawning look on his face.

The dark-skinned young man's eyes also lit up at the sight of the Two-headed Griffin, and he nodded as he remarked, "This beast possesses a lightning bloodline, so it suits me very well. I'll take it!"

Chapter 194: Re-emergence of the Aura

The square-faced cultivator of the Beast Rearing Fields was just about to say something when he spotted the jade badge in Han Li's hand out of the corner of his eye, and the smile on his face instantly stiffened slightly.

The square-faced man took a hesitant glance at Han Li, then said, "Senior Martial Brother Ye, it looks like this Two-headed Griffin has already been rented by this senior martial brother. Would you like to take a look at some other spirit beasts instead?"

The dark-skinned young man's brows furrowed slightly as he turned to Han Li with a hint of befuddlement in his eyes.

He discovered that even with his spiritual sense, Han Li's aura was completely undetectable to him.

The young man took a glance at the jade badge in Han Li's hand, then directed his gaze toward the purple-haired man beside him.

The latter immediately stepped forward, cupping his fist in a salute as he said, "I don't recall ever seeing you before, Fellow Daoist. May I ask which elder you're a disciple to?"

"Who I am doesn't really concern you. I chose this Two-headed Griffin first, so I suggest you go pick out another spirit beast," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

He then turned to the round-faced young man, paying no further heed to the purple-haired man as he said, "I still have other matters to attend to, so undo the restriction here and release the beast."

The round-faced young man took a hesitant glance at the dark-skinned young man and his entourage, but in the end, he still did as he was told, flipping a hand over to produce that azure jade tablet.

The dark-skinned young man's expression immediately darkened slightly upon seeing this, and the purple-haired man instantly flared up with rage.

"How insolent of you! Do you know who Senior Martial Brother Ye Feng is? How dare you speak to him like this? If you know what's good for you, then you'll hand over this Two-headed Griffin right away, and we'll give you twice the rent as compensation. Otherwise..."

"Otherwise what?"

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he released his aura, instantly causing the purple-haired man to choke on the rest of his words.

He had concealed his own aura this entire time in order to avoid attracting attention. After all, a new True Immortal was bound to catch a lot of attention, but it seemed that aura concealment wasn't always the best policy to avoid trouble.

With that in mind, Han Li took a step forward, and a burst of terrifying spiritual pressure erupted out of his body, causing the surrounding space to tremble as ripples that were visible even to the naked eye surged through the air.

The derisive sneers on the faces of the group of Body Integration cultivators instantly turned to shock and horror, and they were forced back by the burst of tremendous spiritual pressure, unable to find steady footing even after stumbling back for over 100 feet.

Yellow light flashed from the purple-haired man's body as he summoned a yellow jade scepter, which conjured up a yellow light barrier around him, but even so, he was still forced to stumble back quite a distance before finally managing to steady himself.

The only one who was able to remain unmoved by Han Li's aura was the dark-skinned young man. At his moment, arcs of silver lightning were flashing all over his body, giving him the appearance of a deity of lightning, but despite this, his face had still paled slightly.

Han Li had intentionally controlled the burst of spiritual pressure so that it didn't affect anyone aside from the dark-skinned young man and his entourage. However, the Two-headed Griffin was extremely sensitive to auras, and a look of awe and veneration instantly appeared in its eyes as it descended out of the sky before laying itself flat against the ground while trembling in fear.

Right at this moment, a hint of barely detectable elation flashed through Han Li's eyes as he turned his gaze to the dark-skinned young man.

It was very faint, but the man was carrying a hint of Daoist Xie's aura.

Han Li took a deep breath, and his expression instantly returned to normal, while the burst of immense spiritual pressure also faded.

The group of Body Integration cultivators were finally able to steady themselves, but there was more than a hint of lingering fear in their eyes.

The purple-haired man was sweating profusely while kicking himself internally.

In the past, he had always been able to pick on others thanks to his affiliation to Ye Feng, but he had really picked out the wrong target this time.

The silver lightning around the dark-skinned young man's body faded, and he was standing in silence, seemingly at a slight loss for what to do.

He was quite a powerful cultivator in his own right, but he knew his own limits, and he was aware that there was no way he could contend against a True Immortal.

A tense silence instantly descended upon the entire area, but it was soon broken by Han Li, who turned to the round-faced young man as he asked, "Who is he? I've yet to encounter such an arrogant disciple."

"He is Ye Feng, a disciple of Elder Mo Xie of the Immortal Origin Palace. He's already reached the pinnacle of the Grand Ascension Stage, and I've heard that he's planning to attempt an ascension tribulation soon, making him an extremely prominent figure among inner sect disciples," the round-faced young man explained.

"I see, no wonder you're strutting around like you own this place. You want this Two-headed Griffin, right?" Han Li asked with a casual smile.

At this point, Ye Feng had already put on a smile, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "Seeing as you chose it first, it naturally belongs to you, Elder Li. Please forgive me for the rudeness that I displayed earlier."

"You cultivate lightning-attribute abilities, while this Two-headed Griffin possesses quite a powerful lightning bloodline, so it's no wonder that you want it. Even though I'm an elder, I'm not one to pick on those below me. How about this? I'll stand here and take one of your attacks without using any treasures. If you can make me move even a single step from this spot, then I'll concede this Two-headed Griffin to you. What do you say?" Han Li proposed with a smile.

Ye Feng faltered slightly upon hearing this, unsure of why Han Li was suddenly extending this olive branch.

However, he quickly came to the realization that it had to have been because the round-faced young man had just informed Han Li that he was a disciple to Elder Mo Xie.

Elder Mo Xie was extremely renowned among the inner sect disciples, having already reached the late-True Immortal Stage and was overseeing the Immortal Origin Palace. The fact that Han Li was an attendant elder indicated that he was most likely an itinerant immortal who had only just joined the sect, so he had no backers to rely on, and it stood to reason that he didn't dare to cause any offense to Elder Mo Xie.

With that in mind, Ye Feng's confidence was instantly restored, and a warm smile appeared on his face as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li.

"It would be rude of me to turn down such a kind offer, so please pardon me, Elder Li."

He had absolute confidence in his own offensive prowess, even in the face of a True Immortal.

Everyone else immediately backed away upon hearing this exchange, creating a large, open area for the two combatants.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release several dozen streaks of yellow light, which landed in the surrounding area to form a massive semi-transparent yellow light barrier around himself and Ye Feng.

Immediately thereafter, Ye Feng let loose a long roar while making a hand seal, and thick bolts of silver lightning surfaced over his body amid a string of rumbling thunderclaps.

In the next instant, he opened his mouth, and a thumb-sized silver bead flew out of his mouth. Despite its small size, the bead was giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations and flashing with silver lightning as it hovered above his head.

He then raised his hands up into the air, and all of the silver lightning flashing over his body converged toward the bead, causing it to revolve rapidly as it conjured up a giant ball of silver lightning that was over 1,000 feet in size.

The ball of lightning resembled a dazzling silver sun and was giving off extremely formidable lightning pressure.

Even through the yellow light barrier, the purple-haired man and the others were still struck by the terrifying pressure emanating from the ball of lightning, causing them to retreat a few steps further with awestruck looks on their faces.

The Two-headed Griffin was separated from Han Li and Ye Feng by two light barriers, but even so, it had begun snarling with unease.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but his heart stirred slightly at the sight of the silver ball of lightning.

All of a sudden, countless arcs of silver lightning began flashing over his body as well, and they weren't as bright as the silver lightning released by Ye Feng, but they were extremely fast and agile, resembling countless spirit snakes that were springing in all directions.

Immediately thereafter, countless arcs of purple lightning that were giving off a wild and violent aura also appeared over Han Li's body.

The auras emanating from the silver and purple lightnings were completely different, clearly indicating that they were two different types of lightning, yet they were intertwining with one another in an extremely harmonious fashion. Not only were they not rejecting one another in the slightest, they were displaying signs of fusing into one.

Rings of silver and purple lightning proliferated in all directions from Han Li's body, presenting a formidable sight to behold.

Ye Feng's expression instantly changed slightly upon hearing this. He hadn't anticipated that Han Li would also be adept at wielding the power of lightning, and it seemed that Han Li's lightning manipulation was more masterful than his own.

His heart sank slightly as a dark look appeared on his face, and he let loose a loud roar as another layer of silver lightning appeared over his body before surging into the ball of lightning above his head, causing it to expand even further in size.

Immediately thereafter, Ye Feng swung his arms through the air in a hurling motion, sending the massive ball of silver lightning hurtling directly toward Han Li.

The giant ball of lightning reached Han Li in the blink of an eye, crashing down with devastating force like a meteorite, sending powerful shockwaves surging through the air.

Han Li's expression remained calm and collected as he made a grabbing motion with his left hand.

The silver and purple lightning around his body converged toward his arm, forming a huge lightning sword that was over 1,000 feet in length. Countless tiny silver and purple lightning runes then appeared over the surface of the blade, pulsing and flashing incessantly.

With a swing of his arm, the lightning sword was slashed through the air to clash against the ball of lightning amid an earth-shattering boom.

The two opposing bodies of lightning intertwined to send devastating shockwaves sweeping through the surrounding area, only to be contained by the yellow light barrier.

An impasse immediately ensued, and it seemed that the lightning sword and the ball of lightning were evenly matched.

Ye Feng shuddered in the face of the violent impact, and only after stumbling back a few steps was he able to steady himself.

Meanwhile, Han Li's right hand was still clasped behind his back, and he was looking as relaxed as ever.

Ye Feng's expression darkened even further upon seeing this, and he made a rapid series of hand seals before opening his mouth to release a burst of liquid-like silver light that vanished into the ball of lightning in a flash.

The giant ball of lightning churned violently as it glowed with scintillating radiance, and around a dozen enormous silver lightning runes flew out from within.

Every single one of those lightning runes was roughly the size of a millstone, and they were giving off faint law fluctuations as they hurtled directly toward the giant lightning sword.

With each rune that struck the lightning sword, the latter would shudder violently, and the light radiating from its surface would dim a little.

After being struck by the dozen or so lightning runes in succession, the massive lightning sword had dimmed significantly, but Han Li paid no heed to this. Instead, he was staring at the silver ball of lightning in an absentminded manner.

Chapter 195: Discovery of the Fire Vein

Ye Feng gritted his teeth upon seeing this, and he continued to make a rapid string of hand seals before releasing two more mouthfuls of silver light that surged into the ball of lightning.

Arcs of lightning were surging over the surface of the ball of lightning as it expanded even further in size while radiating dazzling silver light, gradually beginning to overwhelm the giant lightning sword.

Thick bolts of silver lightning were shooting out of the ball lightning like a series of massive devilish claws, itching to tear Han Li into pieces.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes suddenly lit up, and it seemed that he had only just returned to his senses.

The fingers of his left hand moved in succession, and the giant lightning sword instantly began to radiate dazzling silver and purple lightning while giving off a burst of violent rumbling.

In the blink of an eye, the lightning sword swelled to around twice its original size, and not only was it able to keep the giant ball of lightning at bay, it was able to instantly gain the upper hand.

Ye Feng's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, yet before he had a chance to do anything, the huge lightning sword lit up once again, and the lightning runes on its surface swelled drastically in size.

As a result, the semi-transparent lightning sword instantly took on a far more substantial appearance, and it began to release an incredibly sharp aura as it came crashing down with devastating might.

The silver ball of lightning was sliced into two by the lightning sword with ease, revealing the silver bead inside, which was giving off dazzling radiance.

The lightning sword struck the bead with unerring accuracy, scattering the lightning around it, and the bead was instantly sent flying back, while the spiritual light radiating from its surface dimmed significantly, having clearly had its spiritual nature damaged by the blow.

Ye Feng immediately threw up a small mouthful of blood, while the giant ball of lightning exploded into countless arcs of silver lightning that erupted in all directions, forming a sea of silver lightning that was several hundred feet in radius.

What everyone failed to notice was a wisp of near-transparent silver light rising discreetly up from the ground before vanishing into Ye Feng's body.

The lightning sword didn't pause for even a single moment as it continued to come crashing down toward Ye Feng's head, and an alarmed and horrified look appeared on his face as he tried to resist, but the entire surrounding space had been completely enshrouded under the terrifying pressure released by the giant sword, rendering him immobilized.

However, the lightning sword drew to an abrupt halt around a foot above his head, and it continued to flash with lightning.

Ye Feng was staring intently at the lightning sword as he gulped nervously, not daring to move even a single muscle.

In the next instant, the giant lightning sword disintegrated into countless arcs of silver and purple lightning that flowed back into Han Li's body.

"Looks like you still have a way to go," Han Li remarked in an indifferent voice, then made a hand seal to dispel the surrounding yellow light barrier.

"Your powers are truly astounding, Elder Li. I concede my inferiority," Ye Feng said with a dark expression, then drew the silver bead back to himself before promptly departing.

The purple-haired man and the others hurriedly followed along, and the square-faced cultivator from the Beast Rearing Fields also took his leave.

Meanwhile, Han Li was watching their departing figures with a contemplative look in his eyes.

At this point, the round-faced young man had already opened the restriction around the Two-headed Griffin's enclosure, and the creature made its way over to Han Li before crouching down in an extremely tame and timid manner.

Han Li patted the beast's neck as a faint smile appeared on his face, then released a burst of azure light with a sweep of his sleeve to envelop the giant beast's entire body.

The huge Two-headed Griffin rapidly shrank into a ball of spiritual light, then vanished into a spirit beast pouch hanging from his waist in a flash.

"Please pardon me for offering unsolicited advice, Elder Li, but Ye Feng's master, Elder Mo Xie, is a True Immortal who has attained the power of laws, and it's said that he's even run for the position of deputy dao lord in the past, so do be careful," the round-faced young man cautioned in a quiet voice.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then asked, "What else do you know about this Ye Feng?"

"I only recently joined the Blaze Dragon Dao, so I don't know too much about Senior Martial Brother Ye Feng. However, I've heard that he previously had very ordinary aptitude and was only a normal inner sect disciple who wasn't remarkable in any way. However, in the past three years, he had somehow managed to attain a set of extremely powerful lightning-attribute abilities, and his cultivation base had progressed rapidly as a result.

“Only then did he catch the eye of Elder Mo Xie, and he's currently one of the prominent figures among all of the inner sect disciples. His rise has been quite meteoric, so its story is known to almost everyone in the Blaze Dragon Dao," the round-faced young man replied.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

The round-faced young man stood off to the side in silence, not daring to interrupt him.

It didn't take long before Han Li returned to his senses, then summoned a white jade vial that he tossed at the round-faced young man as he said, "You've accompanied me for an entire day, so you can have these pills as thanks for your efforts."

The round-faced young man hurriedly caught the jade vial, then removed the stopper, upon which an ecstatic look immediately surfaced in his eyes.

"Thank you, Elder Li!"

Meanwhile, Han Li had already flown away into the distance as a streak of azure light.

……

Half a day later.

A streak of azure light shot forth from the distance, landing on the summit of the Crimson Dawn Peak before fading to reveal Han Li.

The mountain summit was quite spacious, with a courtyard that was close to 10 acres in area situated directly next to the mountain face. Inside the courtyard were all types of antiquated-looking buildings and bridges that were enshrouded in cloud and mist, giving the entire place the appearance of an immortal abode.

On the mountain face directly neighboring the courtyard was a pair of tightly shut stone doors, which appeared to have been used for seclusion purposes.

To the left of the courtyard was a completely empty spirit medicine field. It seemed that following the demise of the elder who had previously lived here, the spirit medicines growing in the field had been harvested by the sect, while the field had been left completely untended to since then.

At this moment, Meng Yungui and the others were in the process of cleaning up the courtyard and the spirit medicine field, and they hurriedly stopped what they were doing at the sight of Han Li's return before gathering around him.

"Elder Li!"

Han Li gave them a slight nod, then handed the dark purple jade badge and the spirit beast pouch on his waist to Meng Yungui. He then instructed them to create a cave halfway up the mountain for the Two-headed Griffin to reside in before departing on his own to take a stroll over the Crimson Dawn Peak.

This was where he was going to live from now on, so he naturally had to make a thorough inspection of the place.

It didn't take long before Han Li arrived at the foot of the Crimson Dawn Peak, and the closer he got to the ground, the denser the surrounding fire miasma became, and the higher the air temperature.

Now that he had reached the ground, he could feel a scorching aura surging up at him from beneath the earth, releasing waves of sweltering heat.

A hint of elation and intrigue appeared in his eyes upon seeing this.

While inspecting the Inkspirit Scenic Scroll, he identified from the terrain of the mountain and the state of the Crimson Dawn Peak that there seemed to have been a strong fire vein here, and that was why he had chosen this particular mountain.

As it turned out, he was correct, and judging from what he could see at this moment, the fire vein here was even more powerful than he had anticipated.

All of a sudden, a hint of surprise appeared in his eyes as he turned to the left, then began to fly in that direction, arriving in front of the waterfall after just a few seconds.

The waterfall resembled a massive sheet of silver fabric that was tumbling down from the heavens amid a loud rumbling sound, sending a watery mist erupting in all directions upon crashing into the pond down below.

A solemn look appeared on Han Li's face as he cast his gaze forward, and he raised a finger to release a bolt of silver lightning as thick as an adult human arm, which hurtled directly toward the waterfall.

As soon as the bolt of silver lightning struck the waterfall, it instantly vanished without a trace.

A vindicated smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

This waterfall had been conjured up by an illusory restriction that had the ability to conceal itself from spiritual sense detection.

Prior to this, he had inspected the entire Crimson Dawn Peak with his spiritual sense, but still failed to notice this place. However, the restriction was a little damaged, so the concealment effect had been compromised, and Han Li just so happened to have been nearby. Otherwise, he most likely still wouldn't have been able to discover the secret here.

Blue light flashed within Han Li's eyes as he peered into the waterfall, and a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Moments later, azure light flashed over his body as he flew straight into the waterfall, vanishing in a flash just like that bolt of silver lightning from before.

The space near the waterfall immediately began to ripple, and a string of rumbling booms rang out from within as bursts of light of different colors erupted out of the rippling space before flying away in all directions.

The surrounding space was beginning to ripple more and more violently, while the lights shooting out from within were also becoming brighter and brighter.

Close to an hour later, a resounding boom rang out as the waterfall abruptly shuddered before shattering like a mirror.

Han Li reappeared in mid-air, and his face was slightly pale, clearly indicating that breaking this restriction had not been an easy task, even for him.

After taking a pill, he cast his gaze toward the spot where the waterfall used to be, and he was greeted by the sight of a small valley, in which the ground and the rocks were all of a crimson color.

There was a scorching aura emanating out of the valley, and boundless crimson fire miasma was surging out from within. It seemed that this was the source of the fire miasma that enveloped the entirety of the Crimson Dawn Peak.

Han Li flew into the valley, arriving directly at its deepest part.

The temperature here was even higher, and the surrounding air was warping and shimmering from the scorching heat.

In the deepest part of the valley was a huge fiery red cave that was 70 to 80 feet tall. The walls of the cave were of a reddish-black color, and there were waves of scorching heat surging out from within alongside fire miasma that resembled dense smoke.

Bursts of dull rumbling could also be heard ringing out inside the cave, and Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this as he flew straight into the cave.

Inside the cave was a long passageway that extended underground, and gusts of scorching wind were blowing out from within. There were also cracks on the wall, seeping out of which was dense red fire miasma that drifted out of the cave with the wind.

The entire passageway was filled with incredibly sweltering heat, and the average cultivator would've instantly been incinerated into ashes here, but this amount of heat posed no threat to Han Li, and he continued onward.

At the same time, he raised an arm to release a ball of silver flames, which transformed into his Essence Fire Raven.

As soon as the fire raven appeared, it immediately cast its gaze deeper into the cave with excitement in its eyes, then spread its wings and flew on ahead.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he followed along behind the fire raven in an unhurried manner.

The main reason why he had chosen the Crimson Dawn Peak as the site for his cave abode was for the sake of his Essence Fire Raven.

The fire raven was currently nowhere near the peak of its powers, and it hadn't had a chance to recuperate. During his travels, Han Li wasn't able to aid it in its recovery, and now that he had a relatively stable place to stay, he naturally had to consider ways to help the fire raven recover.

Mo Guang had previously mentioned that Flames of Essence were extremely renowned even in the Immortal Realm, so he was confident that the fire raven would be of great help to him once it made a full recovery.

As soon as he arrived in the Bell Toll Mountain Range, he had already detected that there were several rich underground fire veins here.

The Crimson Dawn Peak was very secluded in location, so the fire vein here was most likely only a branch of the enormous fire veins in the Bell Toll Mountain Range, but as long as he was willing to invest sufficient time, the Essence Fire Raven should've been able to eventually make a full recovery.

Chapter 196: Setup

As Han Li continued to descend deeper and deeper underground, the air temperature was also rapidly rising, while the passageway was becoming wider and wider. At this stage, its highest point was already over 100 feet tall.

Han Li continued to follow along behind the fire raven while inspecting the walls of the cave on either side of him.

The cave walls were quite even and smooth, and there were many signs of sections having previously been repaired.

Was the previous elder inhabiting this mountain carrying out these repairs? Han Li speculated.

Given how abundant the fire-attribute energy here was, it was most likely the case that the previous elder was using fire-attribute cultivation arts, and by that logic, it was very likely that he was the one who had set up the illusory restriction outside.

After flying for another 15 minutes, the dull rumbling was becoming louder and louder, as if countless thunderclaps were ringing out in succession.

For some reason, the Essence Fire Raven suddenly sped up by about twofold here, and Han Li naturally picked up the pace as well.

Shortly thereafter, a massive fiery red world appeared before his eyes. It was an enormous underground cavern that was tens of thousands of feet in size.

The roof of the cavern was riddled with crimson stalactites that were burning incessantly with a layer of flames.

Down below was a huge lake of magma, hovering above which was a fiery crimson cloud.

The magma in the lake was churning incessantly, and a series of massive air bubbles would appear occasionally before popping amid a sound that resembled a rumbling thunderclap.

Numerous fist-sized balls of red light would then emerge from the bubbles before spreading through the surrounding area.

That's fire essence!

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this.

The entire underground space was filled with this fiery crimson light, and even the very air seemed to have been set alight. The temperature here was incredibly hot, to the point that even Han Li was feeling quite parched in the mouth despite his Profound Immortal physique.

The gusts of scorching wind blowing from the surface of the lake were causing a stinging sensation against Han Li's skin, yet the Essence Fire Raven was ecstatic in this incredibly hostile environment.

The fire raven spread its wings as it flew around the entire space as a silver shadow, eagerly gulping down the balls of fire essence in the process. It would even occasionally dive straight into the lake of magma down below, vanishing in a flash only to re-emerge from another part of the lake an instant later in an elated manner.

The underground fire vein here was far more abundant than Han Li had anticipated, and it was no wonder that the previous elder had set up that restriction to conceal it.

He was confident that the Essence Fire Raven would be able to quickly recover to the former peak of its powers here, but there was still something missing.

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release several hundred bursts of red light, each of which contained a fiery red array flag, and they landed in the air above the lake of magma to form a huge array.

He then began to chant an incantation while releasing a series of incantation seals, and the entire array was activated. Each array flag released numerous bursts of red light, which came together form a massive red array.

The Essence Fire Raven instantly realized what Han Li's intentions were, and it immediately stopped playing as it flew onto the center of the array.

In the next instant, all of the power of fire in the entire underground space was drawn toward the array, forming layer upon layer around the Essence Fire Raven, and before long, a huge fiery red cocoon had taken shape.

Han Li rose up into the air, reaching a certain part of the underground cavern's wall in a flash, then flipped a hand over to produce a giant red brush, using which he quickly inscribed countless massive runes onto the wall, forming a flame-shaped design.

Immediately thereafter, he appeared in front of another section of the cavern wall in a flash and did the same thing.

A short while later, eight flame designs had been inscribed onto the cavern wall by Han Li, surrounding the massive cocoon from all directions.

Only then did Han Li stow the giant brush away before beginning to chant an incantation.

The eight flame designs engraved onto the wall began to glow in unison, quickly connecting together to form another massive array that enveloped the giant cocoon.

The two arrays were resonating with one another, and the underground space shuddered slightly as even more power of fire converged from all directions before surging into the fiery cocoon.

At this moment, Han Li could clearly sense the power of the Essence Fire Raven being slowly elevated every single second, and a pleased look appeared in his eyes.

He made a lap around the cavern to ensure that the two arrays were operating with no problems, and only after that did he return the same way that he had come to emerge on the outside again.

After taking a brief glance at his surroundings, he swept a sleeve through the air to release numerous bursts of light that descended into the nearby valley, quickly forming a massive array that encompassed the entire valley again.

Now that the Essence Fire Raven had a place to cultivate, Han Li was in a great mood, and instead of immediately flying back to the summit of the Crimson Dawn Peak, he decided to explore the region around it.

The entire area in a radius of 300,000 feet around the Crimson Dawn Peak was going to be his territory from this day forth, so he naturally had to take a good look around and make some preparations.

It took Han Li close to half a day to explore the entirety of his territory, and he set up some sensory arrays at various points to alert him if anyone tried to sneak onto his land.

As the core of the entire territory, the Crimson Dawn Peak was the place where all of the spirit veins in the area converged, and the world's origin here was more abundant than anywhere else.

However, aside from this mountain, Han Li had also discovered two small spirit areas that were of a decent size for Northern Glacial Immortal Region standards, as well as around a dozen good ore veins.

The ore veins had already been mostly exhausted of ore, while the two spirit areas had been split up into blocks of spirit farmland, but they had clearly been completely abandoned and neglected for a very long time.

Another True Immortal elder in Han Li's shoes would've most likely sent some servants to tend to these ore veins and plots of spirit farmland as a form of long-term spirit stone revenue stream, but Han Li had no interest in doing this.

At the very least, he had no plans of doing this for the moment, and he quickly returned to the summit of the Crimson Dawn Peak.

At this moment, Meng Yungui and the others were all gathered at the entrance of the courtyard, and they extended deep bows toward him in unison.

The entire mountain summit had already been cleaned up, and it was looking pristine and spotless everywhere.

The pavilions and bridges had also been given a new lease on life, and schools of golden fish could be seen swimming through the creeks between the bridges, darting playfully between the vibrant green lotus leaves.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then assigned the rooms around the cave abode to Yun Mengui and the others before dismissing them to go and rest.

After that, Han Li examined the cave abode, setting up some restrictions before arriving at the spirit medicine field.

This spirit medicine field was situated on the outside, so he naturally wasn't going to be planting any important spirit medicines here. Having said that, leaving it vacant would've aroused suspicions as well.

Hence, after some contemplation, Han Li split the field up into several sections, then planted some ordinary spirit medicine seeds onto it.

He had already done this countless times, so he had become extremely proficient, and it didn't take very long at all before a brand new medicine field took shape.

After that, he flipped a hand over to produce a jade flagon, and an azure spirit liquid flowed out of the flagon at his behest before raining down onto the medicine field.

He then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the entire spirit medicine field, and tiny green seedlings quickly sprouted out of the soil.

A faint smile appeared on his face upon seeing this, and he turned before making his way through the courtyard and into the cave abode.

From the outside, the cave abode appeared to have been completely unremarkable, but the inside was a different story. Within the cave abode were around a dozen rooms, including the likes of a pill refinement chamber and tool refinement chamber, thereby saving Han Li a lot of work.

In contrast with the courtyard up front, Han Li naturally preferred the environment in here, and the same had most likely applied to the previous owner of the cave abode as well.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he began to make some personal touches, modifying the most obscure stone chamber in the cave abode into a small medicine garden. He then dug out another stone chamber near the mountain face on the outside, then punched countless tiny holes into the wall so that starlight and moonlight could filter into the room to be absorbed by the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Only after all of these preparations were complete did Han Li emerge from the cave abode once again with the plan to set up a few more restrictions.

However, right as he was about to do this, his expression suddenly stiffened as he directed his gaze toward the spirit medicine field beside the courtyard.

For some reason, most of the seedlings that had just sprouted from the soil had already wilted, and there were only a few that were still alive.

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face as he hurried over to the field before pulling out one of the wilted seedlings.

The root of the seedling had completely wilted and turned black in color, as if it had been burned.

He pulled out a few more seedlings to find the exact same thing. However, there were also several types of seedlings that were growing very well and showed no signs of wilting at all.

He immediately released his spiritual sense, and it didn't take long before he discovered the potential cause behind this phenomenon.

Due to the fact that the underground fire veins had remained unchecked for many years, the abundant fire-attribute spiritual power that they contained had gradually seeped up into the earth. As a result, all of the soil on and around the Crimson Dawn Peak had been imbued with a great deal of fire-attribute spiritual power.

This type of environment was perfect for fire-attribute spirit plants, but made it impossible for spirit plants of any other attributes to survive.

Han Li turned his attention to the seedlings that were still standing, and sure enough, they were all of the fire attribute.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, clearly not anticipating this problem.

It was no wonder no one else had claimed the Crimson Dawn Peak and why both Yu Xiansheng and Qi Liang had displayed rather peculiar reactions when he decided to choose this place.

However, this wasn't too much of a problem for Han Li.

It seemed that this was quite a troublesome situation, but it wasn't one that was completely untenable. All he had to do was set up some separation arrays to prevent the soil from being further affected by the underground spirit veins.

That would negatively impact the spirit herbs' absorption of spiritual qi from the underground veins, but that wasn't much of a concern to him, seeing as he was relying almost solely upon his Heaven Controlling Vial to mature his spirit plants.

As for the spirit medicine field beside the courtyard, that was only going to be used as a red herring anyway, so all he had to do was plant some fire-attribute spirit plants there.

With that in mind, he didn't consider this matter any further and returned to work.

Chapter 197: Mantra Axis Scripture

Inside a dimly lit hall, there were countless dark azure chains littered all over the ground, giving off a dark azure gleam under the light of the eerie green flames.

Seated on a black chair at the center of the hall, the zombie-like man was leaned forward slightly, and his face just happened to have been obscured by the shadows cast by the green flames, making it impossible to see his expression.

Right at this moment, the thick and heavy stone doors of the hall began to open inward from the outside amid a burst of dull rumbling, and the thunderous sound of churning sand flooded into the hall.

Standing at the entrance of the hall was a tall and imposing figure that was close to 10 feet in height.

The man had a square face with yellow skin, and there was an antiquated copper headguard on his head. He was wearing a dark yellow robe that resembled a cloak, and it was covered in yellow sand that seemed to have come straight from the sandstorm that was raging outside.

As the man made his way into the hall, the heavy stone doors swung shut again, shutting out all of the commotion that was raging outside.

The man strode into the hall with heavy footsteps, causing all of the dark azure chains on the ground to clatter and rustle incessantly.

He arrived before the black chair, then fell to one knee as he declared in a respectful voice, "Master, I've visited the place where Fang Pan met his demise."

"Did you find anything there?" the zombie-like man asked in a raspy voice as he leaned back slightly in his chair.

"I'm afraid not. His killer made sure to clean up the site very thoroughly," the man replied with a dark expression.

"Fang Pan's death most likely has to do with a powerful enemy that he was pursuing 300 years ago. I'll leave it to you to investigate this matter," the zombie-like man said.

"Yes, Master."

……

That night.

The courtyard on the summit of the Crimson Dawn Peak was brightly lit, and thanks to the efforts of Meng Yungui and the others, the entire place was inhabitable again.

At this moment, Han Li was in a secret chamber deep in the cave abode. He had already put on his Blaze Dragon Dao inner sect elder robe and was seated on a cushion with his legs crossed.

Next to him was a palm-sized round metal plate, which contained the first level of the Formless True Axis Arts.

After some time, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, and he made a grabbing motion to draw the spirit note badge into his grasp before pressing it against his own glabella.

The round metal badge flashed momentarily, and a passage of dense golden text instantly appeared in his mind.

The passage of golden text was split up into roughly two parts, the first of which was an introduction of sorts, while the second part was the actual first level of the Formless True Axis Scripture.

According to the introduction, the Formless True Axis Scripture was split up into a total of three levels, and full mastery of the cultivation art could allow one to attain an ability called the Mantra Treasured Axis.

When facing enemies in battle, this ability would allow one to slow down all attacks that came near the Mantra Treasured Axis, thereby robbing opponents of any speed advantage.

The nature of the ability didn't change from level one to level three of the cultivation art. Instead, it would still grant one the same ability, but to an increasing extent of potency.

Apparently, mastery of the first level of the cultivation art could allow one to unleash a Mantra Treasured Axis that roughly halved the opponent's speed. Mastery of the second level would allow one to reduce an opponent's speed by 90%, and as for mastery of the third level, the effect wasn't outlined, but it presumably would've made the ability even more astonishingly potent.

This was already an extremely stunning revelation to Han Li.

Even just slowing down an opponent's attacks by half was already an incredibly potent ability in battle, let alone slowing down enemy attacks by 90%. If he had already mastered his ability during his battle against Fang Pan, then he wouldn't have struggled anywhere near as much as he did.

He suppressed his excitement as he turned his attention to the second part of the passage, but his brows were soon tightly furrowed with befuddlement.

Having already mastered the golden seal text long ago, he was able to read the passage of text just fine, but when strung together, the words were completely incomprehensible to him.

For some reason, the usage of phrases and method of language formulation employed in the text was massively different from that of those pages of the Golden Jade Tome that Han Li had obtained, thereby making it extremely difficult to understand. [1]

Even after poring over the passage of text for a long time, he had still only read less than 1% of its content, and even then, the meaning of that tiny piece of text was still not entirely clear to him.

He was feeling rather disheartened, but he wasn't willing to give up as he carefully recalled what he had seen in the Golden Jade Tome while comparing it to this passage of text as he continued to read arduously.

The next morning, Han Li removed the spirit note badge from his glabella, feeling utterly mentally drained. He massaged his own glabella as a slightly frustrated look appeared on his face.

The cultivation art was far more profound than he had anticipated, and even after an entire night, he was still yet to even understand all of its content. He felt as if he had grasped onto something, but at the same time, he felt as if he understood nothing.

He shook his head as he flipped a hand over to stow the spirit note badge away, and he was just about to get up when a thought suddenly occurred to him.

As he was leaving the Merit Conveyance Palace the previous day, Elder Fang had told him that he could visit the palace anytime he needed something.

At the time, he felt like Elder Fang had been implying something, and it seemed that his intuition had been correct.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he stood up and exited his secret chamber, then flew out of his cave abode as a streak of azure light.

……

The light of the rising sun was shining down upon the Imperial Dragon Peak, basking the entire mountain and the Merit Conveyance Palace in a warm, golden glow.

Han Li descended out of the heavens onto the white jade plaza in front of the Merit Conveyance Palace in his elder robes, and his entire body was giving off a golden sheen under the radiance of the sun, giving him an ethereal appearance.

After landing on the plaza, he immediately made his way into the palace without pause.

Just like the day before, the palace was quite empty, and Fang Zhuan was still seated behind the table, poring over the same ancient azure-covered text.

The only slight difference was that there was a purple clay teacup, which was filled with green tea that was releasing a faint aroma across the entire palace.

Upon spotting Han Li making his way into the palace, Fang Zhuan set down the book in his hand, then took a small sip of tea as he smiled and said, "Welcome back, Elder Li."

"I presume you already know why I'm back, right, Elder Fang?" Han Li asked as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Fang Zhuan.

"To tell you the truth, everyone who's previously exchanged for the Formless True Axis Scripture has come back to the Merit Conveyance Palace within seven days. You're among one of the fastest to come back," Fang Zhuan replied in a casual voice.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"The content of the Formless True Axis Scripture is extremely difficult to understand. Without the accompanying annotation scripture, it's virtually impossible to even comprehend the scripture, let alone cultivate it. All of the people I mentioned have either come back to switch to other cultivation arts, or have returned for the annotation scripture," Fang Zhuan explained.

Han Li was a little speechless upon hearing this. "Why didn't you inform me of this yesterday, Elder Fang?"

"In the past, I informed everyone of this, but my words mostly fell upon deaf ears, and a lot of people regarded me as just a Grand Ascension cultivator who was speaking out of turn, so I eventually stopped. Once they discover the problem on their own, they'll naturally come back to me, and I'll no longer have to convince them of the validity of my claims," Fang Zhuan explained with a smile.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he replied, "I suppose that does make sense. How many merit points are required to exchange for this annotation scripture, and is it actually useful?"

"It costs exactly 10 merit points. The annotation scripture is a collection of all of the insights derived by those who have attempted to cultivate the scripture in the past, so the content varies in quality and consistency. As for exactly how useful it is, that's not known to me," Fang Zhuan replied.

"Alright, I'll take it," Han Li said as he handed his elder badge over to Fang Zhuan.

After securing the copy of the annotation scripture, Han Li chatted with Fang Zhuan for a while longer before returning to the Crimson Dawn Peak.

Upon his return, he wasted no time, entering his secret chamber right away.

He studied the annotation scripture for half a day, and only after seeing the annotations made by many past cultivators of the Formless True Axis Scripture did he finally develop an understanding of what the cultivation art was about.

As it turned out, the original name of the Formless True Axis Scripture was the Mantra Axis Scripture, and the content of the original cultivation art was even more difficult to understand. The barrier to entry was extremely high, and just the hurdle of manifesting the Mantra Treasured Axis was enough to keep out 90% of cultivators.

Among the remaining 10%, even those who were fortunate enough to manifest Mantra Treasured Axes were only able to cultivate this scripture to the second level at the very most, but at that level, it was impossible to master the laws of time through the cultivation art. At the very least, no one from the Blaze Dragon Dao was known to have cultivated the scripture to the third level.

Among the many cultivators who had previously encountered bottlenecks in the cultivation art, some had inadvertently discovered a shortcut that allowed one to avoid the hurdle of having to manifest a Mantra Treasured Axis.

Those people used materials that contained the power of laws to craft a Mantra Treasured Axis, then engraved some special runes that they had derived onto the treasure, thereby allowing them to unleash all types of unforeseen abilities through it.

Due to the vast contrast between this method and the conventional cultivation method, the Mantra Treasured Axes refined had almost no effect when it came to slowing down attacks. However, it was able to unleash other abilities depending on the different law powers contained in the materials used to refine the axis.

For example, if the materials used contained the power of metal laws, then the sharpness of the axis would be significantly enhanced. If the materials used contained the power of speed laws, then the speed of the attacks unleashed by the axis would be greatly elevated.

Following the discovery of this "shortcut", virtually everyone chose to employ this method over the original cultivation method, and it was exactly because of this that the cultivation art's name was altered from Mantra Axis Scripture to Formless True Axis Scripture, denoting the fact that it had no set form and could be molded as the cultivator saw fit.

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this, and only after a long while did he continue to slowly read through the text while consulting the annotations.

[1]. For more information on the Golden Jade Tome, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1166: Golden Jade Tome.

[Back]

Chapter 198: Extraordinary Luck

Several days passed by in a flash.

There was a secluded snow-covered valley in the eastern part of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and it had always been very rarely frequented due to its close proximity to the Snowmelt Forest.

There were many cedar trees that were over 1,000 feet tall growing in the valley, and whenever there was any snowfall, the trees would be completely covered in snow, giving them the appearance of pristine white snowy pagodas from afar.

At this moment, there were thunderclaps ringing out incessantly within the valley, interspersed by the sound of snapping tree trunks and branches.

Due to the soundwaves, the snow that had been accumulating on the slopes on either side of the valley began tumbling down into the center of the valley, eventually culminating in a violent avalanche.

Due to the sheer volume of accumulated snow, the avalanche only gradually subsided after it had spilled all the way out of the valley, and there were still countless particles of fine, powdery snow drifting through the air.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light flew down from the heavens, landing at the edge of the valley before fading to reveal Han Li in his inner sect elder robes.

Yet another rumbling thunderclap rang out, and Han Li cast his gaze deep into the snowy valley to find a massive pillar of silver lightning erupting into the sky.

"Looks like I've come to the right place," he murmured to himself, then flipped a hand over to produce a High Zenith Invisibility Talisman.

A burst of purple light appeared around him, and his body gradually became more and more indistinct until it disappeared altogether.

Inside the snowy valley, the avalanche had snapped countless cedar trees, and there were broken trunks and branches littered throughout the snow.

On an elevated stone cliff in the deepest part of the snowy valley was a thin dark-skinned young man. He was looking directly up ahead with a bright gleam in his eyes, and it was none other than Ye Feng, who had engaged in an altercation with Han Li just a few days ago at the Beast Rearing Fields.

At this moment, countless arcs of silver lightning were surging incessantly over his body, and it was clear that he was in the process of cultivating a very powerful lightning secret technique.

Everything in a radius of several thousand feet around him, regardless of whether it be the cedar trees or the exposed stone ground, were all charred black with plumes of white smoke rising up into the air.

Ye Feng couldn't help but burst into elated laughter as he could feel that his lightning powers had become even more formidable.

However, his laughter had only just begun to ring out when he was suddenly completely rooted to the spot, and all of the lightning surging over his body also vanished in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of space fluctuations emerged ahead of him, and Han Li appeared out of thin air before bringing his index and middle fingers together and pressing them against Ye Feng's glabella.

At the same time, mesmerizing blue light was glowing within Han Li's eyes, and he was using a soul search technique on Ye Feng

Back at the Beast Rearing Fields, he had already planted a soul mark on Ye Feng.

However, he had been busy studying the Formless True Axis Scripture these past few days, while Ye Feng had also remained in his cave abode the entire time. Only on this occasion, where Ye Feng was testing out his lightning powers, did Han Li finally get the opportunity to swoop in.

As the soul search progressed, Han Li's expression was displaying slight changes. Initially, his expression was quite wary, but that was soon followed by a look of a surprise, then transitioned into a wry smile.

Moments later, the blue light in his eyes gradually faded, and he removed his fingertips from Ye Feng's glabella as he remarked, "You've really had some extraordinary luck. Seeing as you played no part in what happened to me 300 years ago, I'll let you be, but it's about time that you returned what's rightfully mine."

He reached out and removed the storage bracelet from Ye Feng's wrist as he spoke, then inspected it momentarily before stowing it away.

After that, he rose up once again as a streak of azure light and vanished into the distance in a flash.

Following Han Li's departure, Ye Feng slowly returned to his senses, and he was finally able to close his mouth. His cheeks were a little sore from having his mouth agape for so long, and there was a disoriented look in his eyes, clearly indicating that he had no recollection of what had just happened.

However, a panicked look then appeared on his face as he noticed his own bare wrist, and he hurriedly scrambled to his feet, frantically rummaging all over his own body before releasing his spiritual sense to scour his surroundings.

A short while later, a heart-wrenching cry of despair rang out within the valley.

……

Meanwhile, Han Li returned to his cave abode without pause, then made his way straight into the secret chamber. On the way, Meng Qianqian extended a joyful curtsey to him, but he completely failed to notice, leaving the girl feeling dejected for quite some time.

After taking a seat at the center of the secret chamber, he immediately pulled out the storage bracelet, then refined it briefly before producing an egg-sized golden ball from inside.

At first glance, the golden ball didn't appear to have been remarkable in any way, but through his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, Han Li was able to see that the ball was riddled with extremely faint yet intricate patterns, which were interconnected to form a series of mysterious images.

Furthermore, the ball was giving off an extremely familiar aura.

He held the golden ball on the palm of his hand as blue light flashed within his eyes, and a spiritual sense thread emerged from his glabella before slowly entering the ball.

The golden ball shuddered slightly before all of the patterns on its surface lit up in unison, filling the entire secret chamber with dazzling golden radiance.

Immediately thereafter, several deep crevices split open on the ball as if it were a mechanical, modular unit, and a series of thin metal limbs emerged from those crevices as it transformed into a palm-sized golden crab.

"Fellow Daoist Xie," Han Li hurriedly called out at the sight of the golden crab, yet he received no response.

However, moments later, a familiar voice rang out within his consciousness.

"Fellow Daoist Han... You've finally found me..."

Even through spiritual sense communication, Daoist Xie's voice was still extremely feeble, sounding as if it could falter into silence at any moment.

An indescribable feeling welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this.

Han Li suppressed his emotions as he asked, "Do you recall what happened 300 years ago, Fellow Daoist Xie? How have you become like this?"

"Has it already been... 300 years?" Daoist Xie asked in a rather wooden voice.

After taking a moment to rest, its voice became a lot more stable, and it began to give Han Li a recount of everything that happened 300 years ago.

Initially, Han Li remained quite calm and collected, but the more he heard, the darker his expression became, and his hands involuntarily balled up into tight fists, with bulging veins visible on the backs of his hands.

As it turned out, back then, he had already encountered another formidable foe prior to being attacked by Fang Pan's trio.

That person's cultivation base and immortal spiritual power had been far superior to his, and at a very early stage in the battle, they were already able to seal Daoist Xie and Han Li's 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords with ease.

Han Li had sustained severe injuries during the battle, and he was only able to just barely escape with the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch, Mo Guang, and the others doing everything in their power to hold off the enemy.

Mo Guang and the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch were able to join forces to temporarily keep the enemy at bay, but Daoist Xie was forced to self-detonate its immortal puppet body to break the seal, leaving only a puppet core behind that fled with the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

"... At some point, the spiritual power in my core was exhausted, and I became unable to control the flying swords, so I could only watch as they flew away on their own. After that, I lost consciousness, and I've only just been awakened by you. What happened after I fell unconscious?" Daoist Xie asked.

"After you fell unconscious, your core was picked up by someone and sold at a market near the Blaze Dragon Dao. It was sold to an inner sect disciple with mediocre aptitude as an ordinary tool refinement material, and that disciple managed to discover some obscure spirit patterns engraved on your core by chance using his spiritual sense.

“In doing so, he was able to derive a powerful lightning secret technique, launching him on a meteoric rise to become the star of the inner sect. It was also by chance that I noticed some strange signs in his lightning techniques, and that's how I eventually managed to find you," Han Li explained.

"I see..."

"Initially, I was worried that he would have some ties to the powerful enemy that you spoke of, but after conducting a soul search, I found out that he was merely extremely lucky. Prior to this, I've already slain two of the enemies that tried to hunt me down all those years, and I learned that there's a mastermind behind them.

“I'm assuming that's the person that you were referring to. However, I was unable to uncover that person's identity. Do you recall what they looked like or who they were?" Han Li asked.

After hearing Han Li's question, the golden crab sitting on the palm of his hand suddenly clutched its pincers to its head as it began to tremble in a pained display.

Only after a long silence did Daoist Xie's voice ring out within Han Li's consciousness again.

"Somehow, something seems to have gone wrong with my memory. I only vaguely remember a rough outline of the person, but I can't recall their exact appearance. The only things I can recall are that their immortal spiritual power was far superior to yours, and they seemed to have been wielding an inkstone immortal treasure that was capable of controlling the power of shadows."

"Unfortunately, I'm not surprised. Not only are you unable to recall what that person looks like, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang and I have no recollection of them, either. In fact, we've forgotten everything that's taken place in the past 300 years," Han Li said.

"It sounds like we're in a very bad situation," Daoist Xie said in a concerned voice.

"My guess is that the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords are currently in the Bell Toll Mountain Range as well, but I haven't been able to track them down. Now that I've found you, I'll be sure to find a way to refine a new body for you. However, I'm not sure if it'll be up to the same standard as your previous body," Han Li said with a contemplative look on his face.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Han. Aside from that, don't forget the agreement that we made back in the Spirit Realm," Daoist Xie reminded.

"Of course not. I'll fulfill the agreement once I attain the power required to do so," Han Li replied with a nod.

Daoist Xie didn't say anything further upon hearing this, and it reverted back into a golden ball amid a flash of golden light before being stowed away by Han Li.

Chapter 199: Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plate

After stowing the golden ball away, a contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face.

He carefully sorted through all of the information that he had obtained up to this point in his mind, but he still couldn't identify any leads that could've been connected to the mastermind behind all of this.

A long while later, he gently exhaled as he shook his head.

Whoever this formidable foe was, the fact that they were able to force him into such dire straits back then was an indication that he was most likely no match for them as he currently was, so the best course of action to take for the time being was to avoid this enemy at all costs.

Seeing as even Fang Pan was able to find him, this even more powerful mastermind who was pulling the strings behind scenes had to have been capable of tracking him down as well. The only potential saving grace for Han Li was that this enemy perhaps wasn't aware that he had returned to the Immortal Realm.

In any case, he had to attain more power as quickly as possible in order to deal with all of the unforeseen circumstances that could arise.

In order to accomplish this objective, there was something that he had to address.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to summon his Twin Starshift Plate.

The Blaze Dragon Dao was an immeasurable distance away from the Black Wind Sea, and the connection between the pair of array plates had become extremely tenuous, making it impossible to transfer any further heavy water.

Not only was this affecting the rate at which his Earthly Deity Avatar was deriving heavy water, he was also running out of an important resource required to refine more Heavy Water Veined Lightning.

Both of these things were very important to him, so he had to find a way to get them back on track.

Ever since arriving on the Ancient Cloud Continent, this was a problem that had always been on his mind, and now that he had settled into the Blaze Dragon Dao, he finally had a chance to address it.

Thus, he immediately put on outer garment to conceal his elder robes, then summoned his Transient Guild mask before putting it on.

He had purchased the Twin Starshift Plates from the Transient Guild, so he had to turn to the Transient Guild for a solution to this problem. Back in the Spirit Realm, he wouldn't even have bothered to consider the idea of transferring treasures over such massive distances, but this didn't seem all that far-fetched of a notion in the Immortal Realm.

The main reason for this had to have been related to the power of laws. Treasures of this nature would inevitably draw upon the power of space laws to a certain extent, or relied on spirit materials that contained the spatial power.

An azure light screen was released from the mask, and countless diagrams and lines of text of different sizes appeared on its surface.

Han Li immediately turned to the item exchange section before conducting a thorough search.

It didn't take long before he spotted what he was looking for, and he pointed at a spot on the light screen, then began to wait in silence.

Only after a full hour had passed did a burst of azure light emerge from the light barrier, then took on the form of a projection of a male figure wearing an azure feathered robe and a tiger mask.

The tiger-masked man looked at Han Li for a moment, then said, "May I ask... Ah, I remember who you are, you once purchased a set of Twin Starshift Plates from me, right? Have they served you well?"

"They've been alright," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"Could it be that you encountered some type of problem while using the plates?" the tiger-masked man asked.

"The function of the array plates is just as you describe, but you never told me about their distance limitations," Han Li said as a hint of displeasure crept into his voice.

"Ah, my forgetfulness got the better of me and I forgot to tell you that the array plates can only work across a distance of roughly one continent. If you go beyond that, the teleportation function of the array plates will be significantly diminished or even disabled altogether," the tiger-masked man replied in an apologetic voice.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he said, "It's fine. I contacted you today to ask if there's a way to increase the effective teleportation distance of the Twin Starshift Plates."

It was clear that the tiger-masked man had intentionally withheld this information, but at the same time, he failed to ask about this matter. Now that the transaction had already been made, there wasn't much that could be done.

"I'm afraid not. A distance of one continent is the limit of the Twin Starshift Plates' teleportation capabilities. However, there are other ways through which you can teleport items over longer distances," the tiger-masked man said.

"Would you care to elaborate?" Han Li asked.

"This pair of array plates was a replica refined by a good friend of mine based on an immortal treasure, and it's only around 1% to 2% as effective as the original. After many attempts since then, he's been able to craft a replica that's one tenth as effective as the original immortal treasure, and he's named them the Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plates. Is that something that interests you, Fellow Daoist?" the tiger-masked man asked.

Han Li nodded in response, then asked, "How much will those plates cost?"

If these new plates really were five to ten times as effective as the Twin Starshift Plates, then they would be sufficient for his current needs.

"I can sell them to you for 6,000 top-grade spirit stones," the tiger-masked man replied.

"What a preposterous price! That's more than 10 times the price of the Twin Starshift Plate!" Han Li said as a cold look appeared on his face.

"You can't compare them like that. The Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plates are indeed rather expensive, but you're definitely getting more value for your spirit stones," the tiger-masked man chuckled.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then said, "I can't scrounge together so many spirit stones at once right now. This is already the second time we've done business together, so can you give me a discount?"

"Well... I don't mean to be cold, but this is truly an extremely precious treasure. If it wasn't for the fact that this friend of mine is in urgent need of spirit stones right now, he wouldn't even be selling them," the tiger-masked man replied with a shake of his head.

After some more rounds of bartering, Han Li was able to negotiate the price down to 5,300 top-grade spirit stones, but after that, the tiger-masked man refused to go even a single spirit stone lower.

In the end, Han Li heaved a faint sigh, then asked, "Can I get back to you in seven days?"

"Sure," the tiger-masked man replied with a smile and a nod, then instantly vanished from the spot.

Han Li removed his mask, and the light screen around him faded as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Moments later, he injected his spiritual sense into the storage bracelet on his wrist.

Everything inside the storage space had already been split up into roughly a dozen categories, including demon beast materials, spirit plants, ore, spirit stones, pills, treasures, cultivation arts, and scriptures.

Prior to leaving the Black Wind Sea, he had sold virtually everything that he owned for spirit stones, so most of these things had been pillaged from Fang Pan's storage bracelet.

At the moment, he had roughly 3,200 top-grade spirit stones, which was still over 2,000 spirit stones under the asking price, so he naturally had to sell a lot of things to make up the gap.

He didn't dare to sell Fang Pan's belongings carelessly in case they fell into the wrong hands and exposed him to be Fang Pan's killer. However, such qualms weren't necessary if he were to sell these things in the Transient Guild.

Originally, the majority of the items in Fang Pan's storage bracelet had been unfamiliar to him, and he was only able to recognize a small portion of them. Thankfully, he met Sun Ke on the way to the Ancient Cloud Continent.

While on the lightning boat, he had indirectly enquired Sun Ke about all of the things that he didn't recognize, and he was able to figure out what most of them were.

As a mid-True Immortal cultivator who had managed to grasp the laws of speed, Fang Pan had managed to amass a decent fortune, and there was no lack of precious items in his storage bracelet. If Han Li were to sell everything, then he would've most likely been able to acquire sufficient spirit stones for the Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plates and still have some leftover.

Thus, he immediately emptied most of the contents of the storage bracelet with the intention of selling them in batches over the coming few days. Right as he was about to withdraw his spiritual sense out of the storage bracelet, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he pulled out a pair of boxes, one larger than the other.

The larger one of the two boxes was crafted from jade and contained a huge white egg. Due to the fact that the jade box was able to continuously provide spiritual qi, the egg was still very much alive.

The other smaller box was around 10 feet in length, within which were three arrow-like azure feathers that were glowing faintly with azure light, giving them a rather mysterious appearance.

Both of these things had been carefully stored in Fang Pan's storage bracelet, and it was clear that they were no ordinary objects.

Even Sun Ke failed to identify these two things, so Han Li decided to release an appraisal mission in the Transient Guild to see if anyone could tell him what these things were.

……

Seven days later.

Inside his secret chamber, Han Li had donned his Transient Guild mask, and he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up the azure light screen before immediately contacting the tiger-masked man.

"Have you gathered the required spirit stones, Fellow Daoist?" the tiger-masked man asked with a smile.

Han Li pulled out a storage pouch as he replied, "Here are the 5,300 top-grade spirit stones you asked for. Do you have the array plates with you right now?"

The tiger-masked man's eyes immediately lit up as he nodded in response. "Of course."

The transaction was quickly completed, and Han Li received a pair of new array plates for his 5,300 spirit stones.

The array plates were of a bright blue color and were giving off a watery blue glow. Furthermore, their surfaces were riddled with patterns that were far more complex than the ones on the Twin Starshift Plates.

On each array plate were seven eye-catching white dots that formed the Big Dipper constellation.

Embedded into each array plate were eight Starshift Stones of a significantly darker color than the ones on the Twin Starshift Plates, and the light that they were giving off was also more radiant, indicating that they were Starshift Stones of a higher caliber.

A pleased look appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the two array plates, but his brows then immediately furrowed slightly.

While he had obtained the new array plates, the fact of the matter was that he was still an immeasurable distance away from the Black Wind Sea, so how was he supposed to send one of these Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plates to his Earthly Deity Avatar?

"Is there something wrong with the array plates, Fellow Daoist?" the tiger-masked man asked with a perplexed expression.

"No, but there's something else I'd like to ask you. Is there really no way to increase the teleportation distance of the Twin Starshift Plates? Even just once?" Han Li asked.

The tiger-masked man took a glance at the pair of array plates in Han Li's hands, and he quickly understood what Han Li's intentions were. "It looks like you want to send one of the array plates elsewhere. There is a way to accomplish your goal."

"What is it?" Han Li immediately asked.

"It's very simple. All you need to do is fit the Twin Starshift Plate in your possession with second-grade Starshfit Stones, then forcibly activate the array plate, and you'll be able to temporarily increase its teleportation distance several times over. However, you'll only be able to use the Twin Starshift Plate like that once before it's destroyed," the tiger-masked man explained.

"What are second-grade Starshift Stones?" Han Li asked.

"They're the Starshift Stones on the Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plates. The ones on the Twin Starshift Plates are only first-grade Starshift Stones," the tiger-masked man replied.

Han Li nodded in response. As long as he could teleport one of these Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plates back to the Black Wind Sea, it didn't matter if he had to sacrifice his Twin Starshift Plate.

Thus, he purchased some second-grade Starshift Stones from the tiger-masked man, leaving him with some leftover as backup in addition to the ones required to power the Twin Starshift Plate.

Chapter 200: Emergence of the Treasured Axis

After parting ways with the tiger-masked man, Han Li released an appraisal mission for the giant egg and the azure feathers in the Transient Guild, then removed his mask.

After stowing his mask away, he immediately pulled out his Twin Starshift Plate and removed the Starshift Stones on it, replacing them with eight second-grade Starshift Stones before activating the array plate.

The Twin Starshift Plate immediately began to glow with dazzling light, but it also began to tremble violently as it gave off an unprecedented type of spatial fluctuations.

Having already been warned by the tiger-masked man, Han Li wasn't surprised by this at all, and after a brief hesitation, he placed one of the Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plates and half of his second-grade Starshift Stones onto the array plate before initiating the teleportation.

The light radiating from the Twin Starshift Plate instantly brightened even further, while the spatial fluctuations emanating from it were becoming extremely unstable, oscillating wildly in power.

A few seconds later, the Twin Starshift Plate finally exploded into pieces, but prior to that, the Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plate had vanished within the light.

Han Li was still feeling a little anxious upon seeing this. After all, this pair of new array plates had exhausted the majority of his assets, and it would've been extremely unfortunate if it had been destroyed by the spatial fluctuations.

With that in mind, he hurriedly chanted an incantation to activate his Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plate.

The profound runes on the surface of the array plate lit up one after another, forming a radiant blue array amid a faint buzzing sound. Countless white specks of light then appeared within the array, much like stars in the night sky.

The space at the center of the array then began to warp slightly, and a large ball of black water appeared.

The teleportation process was extremely smooth and fast.

Han Li was extremely relieved to see this, and he stowed the ball of heavy water away with a sweep of his sleeve.

The Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plate flashed over and over again as one ball of heavy water emerged after another, and it only took less than an hour to transfer all of the heavy water that the Earthly Deity Avatar had derived over these past years.

Han Li patted the True Water Pouch strapped to his waist as he gave a pleased nod.

The heavy water inside was almost enough to fill two small streams at this point, and with this much heavy water, he would be able to do many things.

Even though the array plates had cost a fortune, they had resolved a problem that had stumped him for years, so they were worth the investment.

After stowing the Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plate away, he sat down with his legs crossed to meditate for a day, priming himself into his best mental condition before pulling out the Mantra Axis Scripture and commencing his cultivation.

Three months flew by in the blink of an eye.

Inside his cave abode, Han Li remained seated with his legs crossed like a statue, but his entire body was enveloped in a faint golden glow.

A long while later, he slowly opened his eyes as an elated look appeared on his face.

The Mantra Axis Scripture was extremely complex and difficult to understand, but during the past three months, his cultivation progress had been remarkably smooth. He had managed to bypass all of the potential bottlenecks denoted in the annotation scripture with ease, and they hadn't posed any obstacle to him at all.

The first time this happened, he had thought that he had perhaps just been lucky, but after the second and third time, he couldn't help but wonder if perhaps his constitution just so happened to have been perfectly suited to this cultivation art.

It was no wonder that he would think this. After all, according to the annotation scripture, every single bottleneck laid out would stump the cultivator for at least several years, and even delays of several decades or centuries weren't all that uncommon. As a result, many people chose to give up on the cultivation art.

Unless there was some type of special reason for this, there was no way that progress could've been so smooth for him.

However, throughout his entire cultivation journey, his aptitude had always been inferior to the vast majority of cultivators, and he certainly didn't possess any constitution that granted him exceptional aptitude.

Despite this, he was able to bypass every single bottleneck laid out in the annotation scripture with barely any trouble at all, and he was feeling both perplexed and ecstatic.

In any case, being able to make such smooth progress definitely wasn't a bad thing.

At this rate, he was on track to successfully manifesting a Mantra Treasured Axis in just a few years, whereas countless others had failed in his place even after centuries or millennia of arduous cultivation.

Han Li took a deep breath to rid himself of these thoughts, then continued in his cultivation.

Three years flew by in the blink of an eye.

Countless tendrils of clouds were drifting over the Crimson Dawn Peak as the sun began to slowly rise in the east, basking the entire mountain summit in a warm, golden glow.

Everything remained unchanged on the Crimson Dawn Peak with one exception, which was that the fire miasma that had originally permeated over the entire mountain had receded quite a bit.

Everything from the foot of the mountain to halfway up the mountain was still enveloped in fire miasma, but there was no further fire miasma present above that point.

Meng Yungui and the others arrived on the mountain summit at first light, performing some meditation in the face of the rising sun before carrying out their respective duties in cleaning up the mountain summit.

Everyone's role was very clear-cut, and even though there were only 10 of them, they were able to keep the massive courtyard, the nearby spirit medicine fields, and the cave of the mountain guardian beast halfway up the mountain in a very clean and orderly condition.

The spirit veins of the Crimson Dawn Peak weren't that exceptional in the context of the entire Bell Toll Mountain Range, but the abundance of the world's origin qi here still far exceeded that of other places on the Ancient Cloud Continent, making it an exceptional place of cultivation. On top of that, thanks to the pills that Han Li had bestowed upon them, all of them had progressed in their cultivation bases to different extents.

In particular, Meng Qianqian had made two breakthroughs in rapid succession, taking her to the late-Foundation Establishment Stage, and she was only one step away from the Core Formation Stage.

In contrast with three years ago, much of the childish aspects of her features had faded, and she had become even more beautiful.

"Elder Li has been in seclusion for quite some time, hasn't he?" Meng Qianqian remarked as she took occasional glances at the cave abode while cleaning up the spirit medicine field.

"At Elder Li's level, it's quite common to go into seclusion for centuries or even millennia. Have you run out of spirit stones and pills now that you're on the cusp of the Core Formation Stage?" Meng Yungui asked.

"No, I haven't," Meng Qianqian replied in a slightly grumpy voice.

"Qianqian, you must remember at all times that we are already extremely fortunate to have been chosen to serve Elder Li. Elder Li has always been quite lenient and amicable to us, but as servants, we must never forget our place," Meng Yungui said in a meaningful and heartfelt voice.

"I understand," Meng Qianqian replied as she lowered her head slightly.

Meng Yungui's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and he patted Meng Qianqian's head as he said, "I still have some spirit stones here, you can take them..."

All of a sudden, a burst of violent rumbling suddenly rang out, and the entire Crimson Dawn Peak began to shudder and quake, causing many of the birds and beasts residing on the mountain to flee in a panic.

Immediately thereafter, large swathes of dark clouds suddenly appeared in the originally bright and clear sky, tumbling and surging incessantly.

The world's origin qi surged violently as it converged toward the mountain summit, forming an enormous vortex, and the center of the vortex was directly above the cave abode on the mountain peak.

Meng Yungui and Meng Qianqian were both quite surprised by this phenomenon, but they weren't overly alarmed, and the same applied to everyone else as well.

They had no idea what types of cultivation arts Han Li was using, but what they did know was that he would regularly trigger this type of astonishing phenomena. In fact, something like this happened virtually once a month, so they were already accustomed to this.

Meng Yungui's brows furrowed slightly as she looked up at the dark clouds in the sky, and he felt like this phenomenon seemed to have been different from previous ones.

However, he then immediately shook his head and returned to work as he self-reprimanded, I was just telling Qianqian to not get overly involved with Elder Li, yet here I am, speculating about his cultivation. I need to focus on performing my duties as a servant and nothing else. Ignorance is the best policy.

Inside his secret chamber, Han Li's entire body was enveloped in dazzling golden light, to the point that his facial features appeared rather blurry and indistinct.

As the world's origin qi continued to converge from all directions, the golden light radiating from his body became brighter and brighter, forming an incandescent sea of golden light that inundated the entire secret chamber.

Enormous spiritual power fluctuations surged through the surrounding area in waves, only to be contained by the restrictions set up in the cave abode.

Only after a full two hours had passed did the rate at which the world's origin qi was gathering begin to slow.

The dark clouds above the Crimson Dawn Peak gradually faded to reveal the clear, blue sky, and it was as if the phenomenon that had just unfolded had never taken place at all.

Inside the secret chamber, the massive sea of light shuddered before surging into Han Li's body and was completely absorbed in just a few seconds.

A speck of golden light that was fluctuating in brightness appeared on Han Li's lower abdomen, glowing as radiant as the sun one moment, then almost completely fading the next.

The golden speck of light was like a tiny mouth, and with each flash, a vast amount of the world's origin qi was devoured.

At the same time, a light golden wheel that was around a foot in size appeared behind him before slowly revolving on the spot.

A series of lustrous golden clouds appeared around the wheel, resonating strongly with the surrounding world's origin qi. At the same time, the sound of heavenly music rang out, as if to praise the emergence of the golden wheel.

The golden clouds revolved rapidly around the wheel, gradually transforming into countless semi-transparent threads of light that converged together to form a pair of semi-transparent runes that engraved themselves onto the wheel.

The runes were extremely lively and were constantly flashing and moving as if they were living creatures while emanating faint law fluctuations.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes before taking a glance at his own body, and his gaze lingered on the speck of golden light as an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

After three years of arduous cultivation, he had finally opened up his first immortal acupoint, thereby taking the first step on his cultivation journey as a True Immortal.

As for the golden wheel behind him, that was none other than the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Chapter 201: Unforeseen Turn of Events

According to the Mantra Axis Scripture, the two semi-transparent runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis were Time Dao Runes, which were a manifestation of the laws of time.

The more Time Dao Runes there were, the more powerful the Mantra Treasured Axis was going to be.

Under normal circumstances, someone who had manifested a Mantra Treasured Axis would have the chance to attain a new Time Dao Rune with each immortal acupoint that they opened up, but the probability of this happening each time was only around 50%.

After opening up 12 immortal acupoints, one would reach the mid-True Immortal Stage, and only after attaining six Time Dao Runes would one be considered to have mastered the first level of the Mantra Axis Scripture. Furthermore, only with six Time Dao Runes would the Mantra Treasured Axis be able to halve the speed of enemy attacks.

If a cultivator were struck by misfortune and attained fewer than six Time Dao Runes, then they would never be able to cultivate the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

There were already extremely few people in the history of the Blaze Dragon Dao that had managed to successfully manifest Mantra Treasured Axes at all, and those who had reached the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture were even rarer, but that certainly wasn't due to lack of trying.

Furthermore, six was a cardinal number when it came to the number of Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis, so even if one fell just short and had only five Time Dao Runes on their Mantra Treasured Axis, the slowing effect would be virtually non-existent.

As for those who had taken the shortcut and used treasures in the place of Mantra Treasured Axes, their probability of attaining Time Dao Runes on their faux axes would be significantly diminished. It was often the case that after mastering the first level of the cultivation art and opening up 12 immortal acupoints, one would only have attained two or three Time Dao Runes on their faux axis.

However, the advantage to using faux axes refined from materials that contained other law powers was that there was a chance to attain dao runes of other laws. However, the number of such dao runes that appeared were entirely down to luck and the materials used to refine the faux axis.

Those who were fortunate could add seven or eight dao runes of other laws onto their faux axis, granting it power that wasn't inferior to that of an Acquired Immortal Treasure, while those on the other end of the scale could only attain one or two such dao runes, thereby making their faux axis next to useless.

Han Li was both ecstatic and incredulous to see the two Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Even if he were in luck, there should've only been a single Time Dao Rune attained from the opening of his first immortal acupoint, yet somehow, he had managed to attain two.

In any case, this was most definitely a good thing, and it would significantly lessen his cultivation pressure in the future.

With that in mind, Han Li took a deep breath before activating the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him, and it immediately sped up in its rotation while releasing a burst of faint golden ripples that instantly encompassed the entire surrounding area within a radius of around 100 feet.

The space in the area encompassed within the golden ripples trembled slightly, then instantly returned to normal, and looking at it from the outside, nothing seemed to have changed.

Han Li closed his eyes as he sensed the changes in his surroundings, and he discovered that everything around him seemed to have slowed down a little, including the flow of air and soundwaves, as well as even the circulation of the world's origin qi.

Upon first glance, it appeared to have a similar debilitating effect to the laws of speed and gravity.

Han Li couldn't help but be amazed by the effects of the laws of time, but unfortunately, the effects were virtually negligible at the moment.

Hence, in its current form, it wouldn't even have been as effective as a faux axis in battle, and that was presumably why so many cultivators were willing to compromise and refine faux axes instead.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and the golden light glowing from his body faded alongside the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him.

He rose to his feet and emerged from his secret chamber before arriving in another room, where there was an azure transmission array plate on the table.

The array plate was currently buzzing incessantly while giving off a watery azure glow that formed an azure light barrier, within which were two white transmission talismans were darting around in a haphazard fashion like a pair of headless flies.

Han Li made a beckoning motion, and the azure light barrier faded, following which the two transmission talismans flew into his grasp, and he injected his spiritual sense into them.

During the past three years, aside from in the final year and a bit, in which he had focused all of his attention on breaking through his cultivation bottleneck, he had explored the Blaze Dragon Dao the rest of the time to search for his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords. For this purpose, he had used his Bonded Eight Spirits Vat on numerous occasions as well, but to no avail, as if his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had completely vanished.

Even though he wasn't able to accomplish his main objective, he had familiarized himself with True Immortals of comparable status to himself in the sect during his exploration, and he was currently on good terms with several attendant elders who had also previously been itinerant cultivators in the past.

As it turned out, the two transmission talismans had been sent to him by two of the inner sect elders that he was friendly with, inviting him to go on missions with them. He immediately pulled out a pair of blank transmission talismans and tactfully turned down their invitations without a second thought.

He was in no mood to be going on any missions at the moment.

Shortly thereafter, he appeared in the medicine garden in his cave abode, and he was in the process of carefully inspecting the Heaven Controlling Vial in his hand. Beside him stood a giant ape puppet that was around 10 feet tall.

During the final stage of his seclusion, he naturally didn't get a chance to continue to manifest those crystals that contained the laws of time. However, he didn't waste the green liquid, either, instructing the giant ape puppet to nurture several 10,000-year-old spirit herbs with the spirit liquid in case the need for those spirit herbs arose.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he crouched down and dripped a drop of green liquid onto one of the spirit herbs in front of him, and right as he did so, an unforeseen turn of events suddenly unfolded.

A burst of faint golden light abruptly appeared over his body, immediately following which his Mantra Treasured Axis emerged on its own without any warning.

The 10,000-year-old spirit herb that was closest to him in the medicine garden immediately began to tremble slightly as a layer of translucent light appeared over its surface, seemingly resonating with the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li was quite startled by this as he sprang to his feet.

The golden light radiating from his body vanished in a flash alongside his Mantra Treasured Axis, and the 10,000-year-old spirit herb instantly returned to normal as well.

A bewildered look appeared on Han Li's face, and after some contemplation, he crouched down once again to get closer to that 10,000-year-old spirit herb.

Sure enough, the spirit herb began to tremble once again, while a layer of translucent light reappeared over its surface.

The Mantra Treasured Axis also appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, and it was as if the two were resonating with one another.

What is going on?

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he made his way even closer to the medicine garden.

In the next instant, all of the several spirit herbs in the garden that had exceeded 10,000 years of age began to tremble in unison, and the older the spirit herb was, the more severe the tremors it displayed. In contrast, the thousand-year-old spirit herbs didn't display much of a reaction.

After a brief moment of contemplation, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he rose to his feet before flipping a hand over to produce a pair of jade boxes, then removed the lids of the boxes.

Each box contained a spirit herb that was giving off extremely rich spiritual qi, and they were both also over 10,000 years of age.

The dark green spirit herb in the jade box on the left began to quickly began to tremble, while the light red spirit herb in the box on the right remained completely still.

The dark green spirit herb had been matured using the green liquid, while the light red spirit herb had come from Fang Pan's storage bracelet.

"Could it be that this has something to do with how smoothly my cultivation of the Mantra Axis Scripture has gone, and why I was able to manifest two Time Dao Runes at once?" Han Li murmured to himself as he stowed the pair of spirit herbs away.

......

One year later, on the Crimson Dawn Peak.

The light of the dying sun was spilling down onto the entire mountain summit, basking it in a gentle, warm glow.

All of the shadows in the spacious courtyard on the mountain summit were all elongated, presenting a rather dim yet serene sight to behold.

On a stone stool next to a stone table in the courtyard sat a beautiful young woman in red. She was resting on the stone table with her slender jade-like hands folded over one another beneath her chin, looking rather sullen and dejected.

Meng Qianqian had just emerged from seclusion close to half a day ago, having successfully reached the Core Formation Stage, and she wanted to share this piece of good news with her brother, but she discovered that everyone seemed to have been busy cultivating, leaving her feeling rather disappointed.

"I wonder what Elder Li is doing..." she murmured to herself as she turned her gaze toward the cave abode.

Aside from Meng Yungui, Han Li was the one that she most wanted to share the good news of her breakthrough with.

Everyone else, including her brother, held a great deal of awe and veneration toward Han Li, but she was the only one who felt like Han Li wasn't as cold and high-and-mighty as the other elders in the sect. Instead, he was more like a brotherly figure.

……

At this moment, inside Han Li's secret chamber.

The white beads embedded into the walls were giving off a bright white glow, illuminating the entire secret chamber.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on a cushion in his elder robes.

In front of him was a square, dark azure array plate that was hovering mid-air. Two of the Starshift Stones embedded into the array plate were glowing brightly to form a blue array, and it didn't take long before a burst of peculiar fluctuations began to emanate out of the array.

The space at the center of the blue array rippled slightly, following which a fist-sized ball of heavy water appeared.

Han Li made a beckoning motion to draw the ball of heavy water into his grasp, then stowed the Big Dipper Heavenly Star Plate away.

The ball of heavy water wasn't very large, but in contrast with the heavy water that had previously been delivered to him, this ball of heavy water contained a hint of law powers that Han Li had instructed his Earthly Deity Avatar to inject into it.

What he was planning to do was to refine a faux Mantra Treasured Axis using this heavy water that contained the power of laws.

In reality, he had already decided that he was going to refine a faux axis as soon as he noticed the abnormalities in his Mantra Treasured Axis and Time Dao Runes.

He couldn't be completely sure that this was definitely related to his Heaven Controlling Vial's maturation ability, but even so, he couldn't allow anyone else to discover this connection. Otherwise, he would've been in a world of trouble.

With that in mind, Han Li drew the ball of heavy water into his grasp while sweeping his other hand through the air, releasing a palm-sized piece of black meteoric iron, a watery blue jewel, a drop of blue liquid that resembled a drop of beast blood, and a piece of Water Shade Ore that was giving off a black glow.

Chapter 202: Heavy Water True Axis

All of these materials had been recently secured by Han Li through various means, and none of them were extremely precious or powerful spirit materials, but it had still taken him a great deal of time and effort to gather them.

The refinement method for a faux axis wasn't difficult to find. It was laid out in the annotation scripture, and there was more than one method outlined.

The true axis was quite difficult to refine, but the faux axis was quite practical, so there were many people who had attempted to refine it in the past, and as a result, there were many pieces of insight collected from many past cultivators in the annotation scripture.

Due to the different materials used, the refinement process would always differ slightly from person to person, but the overall process was quite uniform.

At this moment, Han Li had already engraved the array necessary to refine a faux axis onto the ground. It resembled an ancient copper coin of the mortal world that was round on the outside and square on the inside. Its appearance was quite ordinary, but there was far more to the array than met the eye. [1]

Han Li placed the four types of spirit materials onto the four corners of the array's inner square, then opened his mouth to release a ball of nascent flames the size of a human head right onto the center of the array.

As he began to chant a low incantation, the Formless True Axis Scripture was activated in his body, and bright radiance erupted from the array on the ground as it fused as one with the ball of nascent flames.

The sound of rushing wind rang out within the secret chamber, and the ball of nascent flames began to rapidly revolve, forming a miniature fiery tornado that was giving off bursts of scorching heat.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air, and the piece of Water Shade Ore rose up into the air before falling into the fiery tornado, where it quickly became extremely red and virtually completely transparent.

The drop of blue liquid then also fell into the fiery tornado at Han Li's behest, dripping onto the piece of Water Shade Ore.

A loud sizzling sound rang out as plumes of white smoke rose up into the air, and the piece of Water Shade Ore instantly melted into a liquid form.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li directed the other two materials into the flames as well, then switched to a different hand seal, and the fiery tornado instantly transformed into a massive fireball that enveloped all of the materials.

At the same time, the air temperature in the secret chamber cooled significantly, as if the majority of the fire's heat had been encapsulated within the ball of flames.

What came next was a long fusion process.

All he had to do from here onward was to control the nascent flame, so he pulled out the Mantra Axis Scripture and continued to study it.

Several dozen days passed by in a flash, and Han Li remained in his secret chamber the entire time, tending to the fireball in front of him.

Right at this moment, he slowly brought his hands apart in front of him, and the fireball slowly elongated, reverting back into a fiery tornado.

At the center of the fiery tornado was a crimson round plate-like object that was around a foot in size, and it was riddled with countless fine and complex spirit patterns.

However, judging from its aura, it appeared to have only been a treasure of a decent caliber, and there didn't seem to have been anything special about it.

With a flick of Han Li's wrist, the ball of heavy water that contained the power of water laws was sent flying through the air before slowly descending onto the crimson plate within the fiery tornado from above.

A dull thump rang out, both in the secret chamber and directly in Han Li's heart.

The crimson plate shuddered as it was instantly enveloped by the ball of heavy water, and it rapidly turned from crimson to black in color.

At the same time, many of the runes on the plate dissolved one after another into a hollow state, while a ball of watery blue light lit up on the edge of the plate, forming a Water Dao Rune on its own.

A long while later, the entire plate was already riddled with hollow runes, out of which were emanating an aura of water laws.

Han Li opened his mouth upon seeing this, and the ball of nascent flames flew back into his mouth.

The faux axis was already complete at this point, and without the fiery tornado to support it, it plummeted straight onto the ground with a resounding boom.

The ground in the entire secret chamber caved in drastically while countless deep cracks appeared, extending all the way to the surrounding walls.

The entire cave abode and courtyard were also affected, resulting in violent, earthquake-like tremors. Meng Yungui and the others were all startled by these tremors, and they hurriedly ceased their cultivation as they rushed out to see what was happening.

A resounding commotion rang out on the Crimson Dawn Peak, and countless birds flew up into the air in a panic, obscuring a large section of the sky.

Thankfully, the Crimson Dawn Peak was quite secluded in location, so no one else in the sect was alerted by the tremors.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already gotten up in his secret chamber, and he subsequently pulled the faux axis out of the ground as well.

After a close examination, he discovered that the faux axis wasn't imbued with any power of time laws, but it contained extremely pure water law powers. Furthermore, due to the injection of heavy water into the faux axis, it was far heavier than it appeared.

"Given its properties, I'll call it the Heavy Water True Axis," Han Li murmured to himself as he examined the faux axis in his hands with a pleased expression.

A short while later, the gates of the cave abode were abruptly opened, and Han Li emerged from within.

The first thing that he did was pay a visit to the fire vein cave at the foot of the mountain, where the Essence Fire Raven was still thoroughly enjoying itself.

It had devoured an enormous amount of the fire vein's spiritual qi, resulting in a massively elevated aura. However, due to the fact that it had only been residing in the cave for a short time, its aura still hadn't stabilized yet, so Han Li was unsure of exactly how much it had recovered.

However, through their spiritual connection, Han Li could tell that the fire raven was very happy with the area, so there was no need for him to be concerned.

After that, he returned to the courtyard of his cave abode and assembled Meng Yungui and the others before handing out some pills to them. He also answered some of their questions in cultivation before departing from the Crimson Dawn Peak to search for his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Several days later, Han Li's search proved to have been completely fruitless, and he returned to the secret chamber in his cave abode to continue cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture.

At the moment, this was his primary cultivation art, and the power of time laws was also the law power that he most wanted to master.

However, he would always make sure to go out every once in a while to scour the entire Bell Toll Mountain Range for his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, but his search proved to be futile every single time.

Four years passed by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, countless black clouds suddenly appeared in the sky above the Crimson Dawn Peak once again.

The world's origin qi converged in a frenzy, and another massive energy vortex was formed.

A long while later, the dark clouds in the sky slowly faded, and the enormous spiritual qi vortex also disintegrated into countless specks of spiritual light of different colors before vanishing into nothingness altogether quickly thereafter.

Inside the secret chamber of his cave abode, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and there was an elated look on his face.

There were two specks of golden light on his lower abdomen, indicating that he had successfully opened up a second immortal acupoint.

If anyone in the Blaze Dragon Dao were to hear that he had opened up two immortal acupoints in just seven years, they would’ve been astonished beyond belief, particularly considering he was cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture, which was renowned for its inaccessibility.

After reaching the True Immortal Stage, one's cultivation progression was completely different from back when they were at or below the Grand Ascension Stage. Normally, it would've taken several centuries to open up a single acupoint, and for those with mediocre aptitude, it wasn't all that uncommon to take over 1,000 years to achieve such a feat.

Even in the history of the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, there were very few instances of anyone opening up two immortal acupoints in seven years, let alone in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Han Li was also astonished by his own rate of progression, and he couldn't help but think of the Big Dipper Origin Arts that he had cultivated back in the Spirit Domain Realm.

At the time, he had refined his own body using starlight to open up the seven profound acupoints in his body, thereby becoming a Profound Immortal.

That cultivation art had been passed down by Patriarch Cold Flame from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and perhaps there was some type of connection between the two.

However, he didn't dwell too much on this thought as he closed his eyes to examine the pair of immortal acupoints.

Only after close to two hours had passed did he reopen his eyes, and a peculiar look appeared on his face.

A burst of dazzling golden light surfaced over his body, and this Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him at his behest, giving off a gentle golden glow.

Two more Time Dao Runes had appeared on the treasured axis, much to Han Li's elation and bewilderment.

At the same time, he couldn't help but wonder whether two Time Dao Runes would appear every single time he opened up an immortal acupoint. If that were the case, then wouldn't be able to attain 24 Time Dao Runes once he opened up the 12 immortal acupoints required for him to reach the mid-True Immortal Stage?

Of course, this was nothing but baseless speculation, but if this really were to eventuate, then this treasured axis of his would be incredibly powerful.

Han Li felt the faint buzzing ringing out from the four Time Dao Runes, and it seemed that they were resonating with one another in some way.

In the next instant, the Mantra Treasured Axis flashed with golden light, and a burst of golden ripples that were far brighter than before spread through the surrounding area.

After a brief examination, a wry smile appeared on Han Li's face.

Even with four Time Dao Runes, the effects of his Mantra Treasured Axis were still virtually negligible. It seemed that he would have to test it again after attaining six Time Dao Runes, which would hopefully be achieved with the opening of his next immortal acupoint.

Han Li suppressed the hint of excitement that had welled up in his heart, and the golden light radiating from his body faded alongside his Mantra Treasured Axis.

He then rose to his feet and made his way into the guest hall outside. As he did so, a thought seemed to have occurred to him, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

His cultivation of the Mantra Axis Scripture had been extremely smooth, but that seemed to have used up all of his luck, and he wasn't able to find any trace of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords during the past four years.

He had virtually scoured the entire Bell Toll Mountain Range with no luck whatsoever, and he was beginning to grow a little agitated.

Right at this moment, a streak of white light flew in from outside, and it was a voice transmission talisman.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he caught the talisman, then injected his spiritual sense into it, and his expression changed slightly as he immediately rose to his feet and exited his cave abode.

[1]. If you're curious about what the coins mentioned here look like, search up ancient Chinese copper coin in Google Images.

[Back]

Chapter 203: First Visit to the High Profound Palace

After emerging from his cave abode, Han Li discovered Meng Yungui standing outside, accompanied by none other than Qi Liang.

"Please pardon my intrusion, Fellow Daoist Li," Qi Liang said with a warm smile.

"Please come in, Brother Qi. What brings you here today?" Han Li hurriedly invited Qi Liang into his cave abode, then instructed Meng Yungui to brew them some tea.

Qi Liang was also an itinerant cultivator, and he had been Han Li's first connection in the Blaze Dragon Dao, so the two of them had been quite close during Han Li's time here, but this was the first time that Qi Liang was visiting his cave abode.

Qi Liang made his way into Han Li's cave abode, then took a casual glance at his surroundings as he remarked, "I've known you for quite a few years up to this point, but only now am I discovering that you're quite a frugal cultivator, Elder Li. It's quite impressive that just these 10 servants of yours have been able to keep your cave abode in such good order."

"You're far too kind, Brother Qi. My cave abode is indeed in good order, but only because there's barely anything in it," Han Li chuckled.

His guest hall was extremely bare with no furnishings or ornaments aside from a table and some chairs.

He had visited Qi Liang's cave abode in the past, and it was far more extravagant and lavish than his own.

"As True Immortals, neither of us is truly attached to these materialistic things. I admire you greatly for focusing wholeheartedly on your cultivation and now allowing yourself to be distracted by materialistic indulgence, Brother Li," Qi Liang chuckled.

"So what brings you here today, Brother Qi?" Han Li asked.

"I just came over from the High Profound Palace, and I decided to come and pay you a visit on the way back. By the way, you still haven't heard about the mission released by Deputy Dao Lord Xiong today, right?" Qi Liang asked as a hint of excitement appeared in his eyes.

The High Profound Palace was where missions were released and taken in the Blaze Dragon Dao's inner sect, and Han Li was naturally aware of its existence, but he had been busy cultivating and searching for his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords this entire time, so he had no intention of taking on any missions, and as a result, he hadn't visited the High Profound Palace even once.

"What mission's gotten you this excited, Brother Qi?" Han Li asked.

"Deputy Dao Lord Xiong is searching for 10 True Immortal cultivators who are proficient in the art of flying sword manipulation to help him refine a treasure. He's offering a huge reward of this number of merit points to each person after the mission is completed," Qi Liang said in a mysterious manner as he held up five fingers.

"50 merit points?" Han Li asked.

"500! I know you're far more proficient in the art of flying sword manipulation than I am, and that's why I invited you to come with me," Qi Liang said as the excitement in his eyes grew even more pronounced.

Han Li was also rather tempted upon hearing this.

Even though he had never been to the High Profound Palace, he knew that 500 merit points was an extremely opulent reward for a single mission.

"It's been a very long time since there's been a mission with such a lavish reward and no danger involved. Many elders who are only slightly familiar with the art of flying sword manipulation have already signed up, I'm sure you're not going to pass up an opportunity like this, right, Brother Li?" Qi Liang asked with a smile.

Han Li contemplated the offer for a moment, then nodded as he replied, "You've already come to invite me in person, so it would be rude of me to refuse."

He wasn't in the mood to be carrying out any missions, but Qi Liang had come to extend an invitation to him in person, and they were on good terms with one another, so it would've been unbecoming of him to refuse. Furthermore, 500 merit points was a very tempting reward.

Thus, the two of them quickly departed from the cave abode, and Han Li instructed Meng Yungui to look after the Crimson Dawn Peak, following which he and Qi Liang quickly flew away into the distance as two streaks of light, leaving Meng Yungui to look on with deep admiration in his eyes.

……

The High Profound Palace was situated on the Cloud Piercing Peak, and just as the name suggested, the mountain was extraordinarily tall, extending all the way up into the clouds.

Furthermore, vegetation was extremely sparse along the entire mountain, and the rock faces of the mountain were extremely smooth. As a result, even monkeys found it extremely difficult to climb.

A sea of rainbow clouds had been conjured up to conceal the mountain summit, and it was giving off rainbow radiance that could be clearly seen even from hundreds of kilometers away.

The High Profound Palace was situated atop the sea of rainbow clouds, and it was over 100 feet tall and entirely of a dark azure color. Its walls, bricks, and tiles were all made from extremely dense and sturdy materials, giving one the feeling they were looking at a heavy mountain, leading one to worry about whether the sea of rainbow clouds down below would be able to support its weight.

In front of the palace was a massive bluestone plaza with around a dozen thick stone pillars standing on its edges.

The pillars had all types of extremely life-like exotic beasts engraved onto them, including the Heavenly Dragon, the Rainbow Phoenix, the White Tiger, and the Xuanwu Turtle.

The view from the plaza was completely uninhibited, and the blue sky was as clear as a mirror, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

The High Profound Palace was one of the liveliest places in the entire Blaze Dragon Dao. There was a teleportation pavilion situated on the plaza, with people occasionally making their way in and out of the building.

There were also streaks of light that were hurtling through the air from all directions before landing on the plaza.

Strictly speaking, there were no restrictions when it came to the status of those coming to accept missions here, so even outer sect disciples could come here for missions if they felt that they were up to the task, but the vast majority of people here were inner sect disciples.

Right at this moment, two streaks of light arrived from the distant sky, then landed on the plaza to reveal Han Li and Qi Liang.

Respectful looks immediately appeared on the faces of the nearby disciples at the sight of their inner sect elder robes, and everyone gave Han Li's duo a wide berth.

Han Li took a glance at his surroundings, and he was forced to reevaluate his impression of the Blaze Dragon Dao's overall power.

The people entering and exiting the High Profound Palace were of a wide array of different cultivation bases, with the vast majority of them above the Nascent Soul Stage, and even some Body Integration and Grand Ascension cultivators could be seen.

It could be said that just the cultivators at the High Profound Palace at this moment would've already been countless times more impressive than the overall collection of cultivators of a major sect in the Spirit Realm.

Qi Liang was clearly already accustomed to this, and he strode directly toward the High Profound Palace.

Han Li trailed along behind him, and they quickly arrived in front of the palace before stepping inside.

As soon as they did so, Han Li instantly felt his field of view widen significantly, as if the space inside the palace had suddenly expanded by tenfold, and it was a rather indescribable feeling.

From the outside, the palace didn't appear to have been all that large, but its interior space wasn't much smaller than the plaza outside.

Could it be that there's some type of spatial law restriction cast upon the palace? Han Li speculated to himself.

After making his way into the palace, Qi Liang only paused for a moment before making his way deeper inside.

The most eye-catching things inside the palace were three massive stone walls situated at its center. Each wall was around 200 to 300 feet tall and over 100 feet wide, and one of them was white, the second one was azure, and the last one was golden in color.

The three walls were standing next to one another in the sequence of white, azure, and golden from left to right.

The white wall was situated closest to the outside of the palace, the azure wall was standing at the center, while the golden wall was situated in the deepest part of the palace.

Each wall had lines of clear text that were glowing with spiritual light displayed on their surface, denoting a series of missions.

Judging from the numbers of the lines of text, the white wall had the most number of missions, with over 1,000 in total, while the azure wall had fewer missions, and the golden wall had the least number of missions.

"The three walls hold missions of different levels of difficulty. The missions on the white wall are the easiest to complete and are generally suitable for those at or below the Deity Transformation Stage, the azure wall holds missions that generally cater to those at or above the Spatial Tempering Stage, while the golden wall is for True Immortal cultivators like us," Qi Liang explained as he made his way straight to the golden wall down the back.

There were even more people in the hall, and it was rather crowded. In particular, there were many people gathered near the white and azure walls.

However, there were only a few True Immortal Stage elders standing in front of the golden wall, and it seemed that none of the inner sect disciples dared to approach the wall.

Han Li had acquainted himself with some inner sect elders during the past few years, but he didn't know who these elders were.

In contrast, Qi Liang clearly had a larger network of acquaintances than Han Li, and he greeted all of the other elders in a friendly fashion, to which the elders responded in kind.

"Everyone, this is Fellow Daoist Li Feiyu. He joined our sect just a few years ago, and he currently resides on the Crimson Dawn Peak. Elder Li, these are..."

Qi Liang gave Han Li an introduction of all of the elders, and Han Li greeted them one by one, then engaged in some small talk before directing his gaze toward the golden stone wall.

Meanwhile, Qi Liang was still chatting with the other elders, and it seemed that he was quite socially outgoing.

There were quite a few missions on the golden wall, and sure enough, all of them were quite difficult to complete. Furthermore, the rewards also weren't very alluring, ranging from only several dozen to under 200 merit points per mission.

Han Li was rather concerned upon seeing this.

It seemed that earning merit points was going to be far more difficult than he anticipated. The second level cultivation art of the Mantra Axis Scripture was going to cost 9,000 merit points, and he didn't know how many missions he would have to complete to get to that number.

There were some missions that offered higher rewards, namely the dozen or so missions at the very top of the stone wall. These missions were denoted in special red text, in contrast with the white text of normal missions, and they were special missions released by the sect.

All of these special missions offered extremely lavish rewards, with even the lowest reward standing at 800 merit points, while the majority of the missions boasted rewards in excess of 1,000 merit points, but all of them were extremely difficult and perilous to complete.

Among these missions, the one that offered the lowest reward required one to slay a Windfire Fox at the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage and bring back its complete carcass.

Han Li had read about Windfire Foxes in the past. They were a type of social spirit beast that resided in the northernmost region of the Ancient Cloud Continent. These foxes possessed Deity Transformation Stage power from birth, as well as both wind and fire-attribute abilities. Upon reaching full maturity, they would attain Body Integration Stage power, and only a Windfire Fox Monarch would be able to reach the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage.

Han Li had witnessed the power of that late-True Immortal Stage octopus sea beast, and he knew that at his current level of power, he wouldn't have been able to slay such a creature, much less slay a Windfire Fox Monarch at the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage among an entire pack of spirit beasts.

As for the other missions, they were even more difficult, such as venturing into extremely perilous places to search for near-extinct materials or hunting down certain notorious evil immortals who were said to have already reached the Golden Immortal Stage.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face. At the moment, all he could do was examine these missions to broaden his horizons, but there was no way that he could take on any of them.

However, in the next instant, his gaze fell upon one of the red missions.

This mission was tucked in between a pair of missions with lengthy descriptions, so he had failed to notice it earlier. The mission description was extremely simple and concise: "Cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture to the second level".

Despite this, it boasted an extremely high reward of 5,000 merit points!

Chapter 204: Conflict Between Factions

A hint of befuddlement flashed through Han Li's eyes at the sight of this mission.

The mission description didn't state any other requirements. Could it really be that all that was required to earn those 5,000 merit points was to cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture to the second level?

This mission may have appeared to have been extremely difficult for other people in the Blaze Dragon Dao, but given how smooth his progression in the cultivation art had been thus far, reaching the second level certainly didn't seem out of reach.

The 5,000 merit points was very alluring, but if he were to claim this reward, countless troubles would most likely follow. At the very least, he most likely wouldn't have been able to continue to keep a low profile while cultivating in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Furthermore, he had already successfully opened up two immortal acupoints and attained four Time Dao Runes during the past few years, and this was extraordinary progress that he didn't want anyone to know about.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately dismissed any thought of taking on this mission and shifted his gaze away.

After briefly reading through the remaining red missions, he returned his attention to the white mission and began to quickly read through them as well.

There were many missions outlined in white on the wall, but Qi Liang had already told him what to look for, so it didn't take long for him to track down the missions released by Deputy Dao Lord Xiong, and sure enough, the reward was 500 merit points.

"What do you think?" Qi Liang asked as he approached Han Li with a smile.

"The mission is exactly as you described, Elder Li," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"In that case, we need to make haste. I heard from the others that quite a few elders have already taken on this mission. If we wait any longer, there could be no spots left for us," Qi Liang said in a slightly urgent voice.

He flipped a hand over to produce his elder badge as he spoke, then pointed it at the golden stone wall, and a streak of light immediately flew out of the mission in question before entering his elder badge.

Han Li did the same thing, and another streak of light flew out to enter his elder badge as well, upon which a strange design appeared on the surface of the elder badge.

After accepting the mission, the two of them promptly departed from the High Profound Palace without any delay.

Having already been in the Blaze Dragon Dao for countless years, Qi Liang was naturally far more familiar with the layout of the sect than Han Li, and he was leading the way throughout this entire process.

First, the two of them departed using a teleportation array in the teleportation hall, then flew for close to half a day before arriving near a huge mountain.

The world's origin qi here was far more abundant than that of Han Li's Crimson Dawn Peak.

The mountain stretched all the way up into the clouds and was entirely golden in color, seemingly formed by some type of ore. Furthermore, the mountain was remarkably straight and even down the sides, resembling a giant golden sword that was piercing up into the heavens when viewed from a distance.

Concealed within the clouds and mist on the mountain summit were a series of undulating palaces that were basked in an indistinct golden glow, lending them an air of mystery.

There was also a slightly smaller mountain near this one, and some palaces were situated on the summit of this shorter mountain as well. Both mountain summits had restrictions placed upon them, so there was no snow gathered on either of them.

The two mountains were connected by a long golden bridge that resembled a glowing band of golden light hovering in mid-air, presenting a majestic sight to behold.

"This is the Heavenly Sword Peak, home to Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's cave abode," Qi Liang introduced as he pointed at the giant mountain from afar.

"It's certainly a breathtaking place," Han Li praised.

"Indeed. Deputy Dao Lord Xiong is a man of many rules, and the main peak is a restricted area that outsiders are not permitted to set foot on. All visitors must first go to the secondary peak, where they're then teleported to the main peak to meet Deputy Dao Lord Xiong," Qi Liang said in a low voice.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, but then quickly nodded in response.

Moments later, the two of them descended onto a flat area on the summit of the shorter of the two mountains.

The area on the summit of the secondary peak wasn't very large, with only a few side halls and pavilions constructed on it. However, they were arranged in an extremely intricate fashion and didn't appear shabby in the slightest.

Han Li's duo was quickly greeted by a white-robed young man who appeared to have been a servant of Xiong Shan's, and he said in a respectful voice, "Welcome, elders. Have you taken on the mission from the High Profound Palace?"

"Precisely. Would you be able to inform Deputy Dao Lord Xiong of our arrival?" Qi Liang asked.

"He's currently on the main peak right now, please come with me," the white-robed young man said, then led the way toward the main peak.

Qi Liang and Han Li exchanged a glance before following along.

The white-robed young man led them onto the golden bridge before stepping onto it, and Qi Liang asked, "Is it alright for you to take us straight to Deputy Dao Lord Xiong without consulting him first?"

"Master Xiong has instructed me to take all elders who have taken on his mission straight to the main peak without delay," the white-robed young man replied in a respectful voice, and Qi Liang nodded in response.

"How many elders have already accepted the mission?" Han Li asked.

"27," the white-robed young man replied.

Qi Liang's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. There were only 10 spots available.

"It's alright. The fact that he's taking us there indicates that Deputy Dao Lord Xiong still hasn't decided who he's going to recruit yet. I presume we'll need to undergo some type of examination, and it won't be a case of first come first served," Han Li communicated to Qi Liang through voice transmission.

"Indeed. Thank you for the reminder, Brother Li," Qi Liang replied as a hint of embarrassment appeared on his face.

He had reached a critical point in his cultivation and desperately needed the 500 merit points, so in his urgency, he had somewhat lost his sense of reason.

Beneath the golden bridge was vast abyss that was filled with cloud and mist, a sight that would've been sure to give a mortal intense vertigo.

This was naturally not a problem for Han Li's trio, and they quickly crossed the golden bridge before arriving on the main peak.

The area on the summit of the main peak was over 10 times the size of that of the Crimson Dawn Peak, and it was littered with exquisite palaces and spires, as well as countless pavilions, gardens, and bodies of flowing water.

All of the buildings and even the ground had been constructed from precious materials, the most commonly used of which was the golden material that the mountain was entirely comprised of.

The palaces and buildings were all giving off bright radiance that further contributed to a sense of opulence, and under the guidance of the white-robed young man, Han Li and Qi Liang made their way down a wide white jade path for around 15 minutes before arriving in front of a golden palace.

This was a guest hall where the other 27 elders were already assembled, and they were split up into two circles that were seated to the left and to the right of the hall, with each side displaying some slight animosity toward the other.

The dozen or so people on the left were quite relaxed, and they were chatting amicably with one another with a hint of superiority on their faces, while the group on the right remained silent for the most part.

Most of the people in the hall immediately turned to Han Li and Qi Liang upon their arrival, but due to the fact that Han Li had only recently joined the sect, everyone looked away after taking only a brief glance at him.

Among the group on the right, a man with a coarse beard stood up and approached Han Li's duo as he said, "I knew you definitely wouldn't pass up a mission like this, Brother Qi. Why have you only just gotten here?"

"I'm not as well-informed as you are, Brother Nan. I came here as soon as I heard about this mission, but you still managed to beat me here," Qi Liang replied with a smile.

"I just have an impatient personality. There's no benefit to arriving early, all I've done is sit around and twiddle my thumbs," the bearded man chuckled, then turned his gaze to Han Li.

"Who's this?"

"This is Brother Li, an inner sect elder who only joined our sect a few years ago, and he currently resides on the Crimson Dawn Peak," Qi Liang introduced.

"I've heard much about you, Brother Nan," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Come take a seat, Brother Li," the bearded man said as he dragged Han Li and Qi Liang to the circle on the right.

As soon as Qi Liang sat down, quite a few people immediately approached to greet him.

Han Li recognized one or two of the other elders present, but he wasn't very familiar with them at all, and they only exchanged a few nods and some small talk.

All of a sudden, the atmosphere on the right side of the hall had livened up a little, and those on the left side of the hall were rather displeased to hear the chatter ringing out from the other side. In fact, someone even cleared their throat to express their displeasure.

Han Li didn't recognize the people on the left side of the hall, but he had a rough idea of who they were.

Most of these people were former inner sect disciples who had managed to reach the True Immortal Stage through countless millennia of cultivation, and many of them were direct lineal descendants of certain major clans in the Blaze Dragon Dao, thereby granting them the status of inner sect disciple from birth.

These were people who had grown up in the Blaze Dragon Dao their entire lives, and they had always looked down on outsiders like Han Li, most of whom were formerly itinerant cultivators.

In addition to their status granting them a sense of superiority, they were also opposed to the existence of these outsiders who had joined the sect as they had to compete with these outsiders for cultivation resources.

Even though Han Li had only been in the Blaze Dragon Dao for several years, he had already developed a clear sense of the conflict and animosity between these two factions.

The higher-ups of the Blaze Dragon Dao were naturally aware of the situation, but they hadn't displayed any intention of mitigating this conflict. Instead, they were encouraging this type of competition as it was conducive for overall improvement.

This was one of the important reasons why the Blaze Dragon Dao had been able to churn out so many powerful cultivators of late.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the left side of the hall, and his attention was quickly drawn to a man who appeared to have been in his thirties.

He was wearing a golden crown and stood with his back ramrod straight, with a pair of wide shoulders that gave him an imposing appearance. His eyes were long and thin, and there was a sharp gleam flashing within them, much like the gleam of a sword.

Even though he was just sitting there, he clearly stood out from the crowd, and it felt as if everyone else were merely stars that paled into insignificance compared with the moon that he was.

Qi Liang noticed the direction of Han Li's gaze, and he introduced in a low voice, "That man's name is Zhu Feng. He managed to open his 12 immortal acupoints to reach the mid-True Immortal Stage as early as 10,000 years ago, and he cultivates a sword dao scripture.

“He resides on the Langya Peak, so he's known as the Langya Sword Immortal, and he's quite renowned among inner sect elders. Given his proficiency in the art of the sword, he's almost certainly guaranteed one of the 10 available spots for the mission."

Han Li nodded in response.

Zhu Feng appeared to have been quite an arrogant man, only speaking when spoken to by those around him, and he didn't even spare a single glance toward Han Li and the others.

Han Li observed Zhu Feng for a moment long before withdrawing his gaze as he closed his eyes to meditate.

Close to a day quickly passed by, and during this time, seven or eight more elders arrived one after another.

As a result, the number of people in the hall swelled to over 40, and almost all of the seats had been taken.

This was the equivalent of nothing more than the blink of an eye for True Immortal cultivators, and they were waiting for someone of a very lofty status, so no one displayed any impatience.

However, at this point, the hall was far more quiet than before, and most people had ceased their conversations, choosing to meditate with their eyes closed instead.

Chapter 205: Origin Defying Stone Sword

After roughly another two hours had passed, the sound of footsteps rang out from inside the palace, and Xiong Shan's short and stocky figure emerged.

A pleased look appeared on his face at the sight of the 40 or so elders gathered in the palace, and everyone rose to their feet in unison before extending respectful bows toward him.

"We pay our respects to Deputy Dao Lord Xiong!"

"No need for formalities. Come with me, everyone," Xiong Shan said with a dismissive wave of his hand, then made his way toward a door in the corner of the hall.

Everyone in the hall hurriedly followed along, while Xiong Shan made his way out of the hall and through a long corridor, then arrived in what appeared to have been a drill ground.

The area was over 10,000 feet in size, and it was completely empty aside from 10 huge stone swords laid flat against the ground.

Every single one of these stone swords was around 70 to 80 feet tall, and their blades were extremely thick with countless complex patterns engraved upon them, giving off a peculiar aura that resembled sword qi, but was also completely different.

Han Li swept his gaze over the stone swords, and a hint of surprise appeared in his eyes, followed by a look of realization.

"I'm sure all of you already know what this mission is about. I require 10 fellow daoists who are proficient in the way of the sword to help me refine a treasure. There are more than 40 of you here, so I've arranged a trial to examine your level of proficiency in the art of the sword," Xiong Shan declared in a direct and straightforward manner.

Everyone present had already roughly guessed that this would be the case, so no one was surprised by this announcement. However, the animosity between the native and non-native elders had only become more pronounced in the wake of this declaration.

Zhu Feng suddenly stepped forward with a smile as he said, "Deputy Dao Lord Xiong is the number one swordsman among all of the 36 deputy dao lords, so I'm sure just participating in this trial alone will be extremely beneficial to our future cultivation. How thoughtful of you, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong."

He was very cold and arrogant to everyone else, but in the presence of Xiong Shan he had adopted a humble facade paired with a fawning smile.

Many people immediately turned to look at Zhu Feng upon hearing this, and Xiong Shan's gaze was also drawn to him.

His expression remained unchanged, but a hint of warmth had crept into his cold eyes, and he continued, "The trial that I've arranged is very simple. These stone swords here are Origin Defying Stone Swords that I personally refined using special methods.

“There are special restrictions set up in the swords, making it so that only those who are truly skilled in the art of sword manipulation can control them. You can all come and give them a try, and the outcome of your trial will depend on the number of stone swords that you manage to control."

Everyone directed their attention toward the stone swords upon hearing this.

This was a very unique examination.

This was the first time that everyone had heard of these Origin Defying Stone Swords, and even though there were only 10 of them present, Xiong Shan's words clearly implied that this was not going to be an easy trial, so everyone was feeling rather hesitant. No one was willing to go first, and even Zhu Feng was looking a little unsure of himself.

Qi Liang approached Han Li with a slightly uneasy look in his eyes as he asked through voice transmission, "What do you think, Brother Li?"

"I don't see anything amiss for now, but there's definitely more to these Origin Defying Stone Swords than meets the eye, and I presume they won't be easy to control at all," Han Li replied.

Everyone else was also communicating with one another through voice transmission.

Xiong Shan was rather displeased by the hesitance that everyone was displaying, and he said in a cold voice, "I only want 10 people who can meet my standards. Once the 10 spots are filled, the trial will be over."

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this, and they knew that they couldn't hesitate any longer.

A balding inner sect elder instantly flew over to the stone swords as he volunteered, "I'll go first!"

Xiong Shan gave a slight nod upon seeing this.

"When are you preparing to have a go, Brother Li?" Qi Liang asked through voice transmission.

"There's no hurry. Despite what Xiong Shan's saying, the fact that he's offering such a large reward for this mission indicates that he'll definitely want the best possible team that he can assemble. Hence, he'll definitely wait until everyone's attempted the trial before deciding who to select. Let's allow these people to go ahead of us so we can learn by observing them," Han Li replied.

An enlightened look appeared in Qi Liang's eyes upon hearing this. "That's a great idea, Brother Li!"

There were a few other people who seemed to have arrived at the same conclusion as Han Li, and they were looking on with relaxed expressions, seemingly in no hurry to attempt the trial.

Right at this moment, the balding elder gently exhaled, and a burst of faint white light appeared over his body, releasing a bone-chilling aura through the air.

A burst of dazzling white light then erupted out of his body before forming a projection of a giant white sword.

The sword projection was giving off glacial sword intent, and countless snowflakes immediately appeared in the nearby space, dancing through the air in a beautiful sight to behold.

Han Li couldn't help but be rather impressed with the balding elder's mastery over the way of the sword.

These snowflakes appeared to have been rather unremarkable, but they hadn't been formed by freezing the moisture in the air. Instead, they had been manifested by the countless streaks of sword qi that he had unleashed, and an exceptional degree of control was required to accomplish this feat.

The balding elder let loose a low roar as he made a hand seal with one hand while pointing directly forward with the other, and the giant sword projection above his head instantly split up into two, with one of the split sword projections flying into one of the stone swords.

The original sword projection instantly shrank a little as a result.

A layer of glacial white light appeared over the surface of the stone sword, yet right at this moment, the runes on the sword began to glow with faint black light while flashing rapidly like dancing flames.

Most of the white light clinging to the sword was instantly dispelled like a layer of melting ice.

The balding elder hurriedly made another string of hand seals upon seeing this, and another sword projection that was several times larger than the previous one split off from the giant sword projection above his head before surging into the stone sword in a flash.

The giant sword projection shrank down significantly once again, while a layer of bright white radiance appeared over the stone sword alongside countless white runes that resembled tiny swords.

At the same time, a layer of black light re-emerged over the surface of the stone sword to combat the white light, but on this occasion, the white light was far more resolute and was able to hold its own.

"Up!" the balding elder yelled in a forceful voice, and the stone sword shuddered momentarily before slowly rising up into the air.

Even though it had risen up from the ground, the black light released by the stone sword hadn't faded. Instead, it was only beginning to flash even more insistently, causing the stone sword to tremble incessantly.

A solemn look appeared on the balding elder's face, and he made a rapid string of hand seals, expending a great deal of effort to finally stabilize the stone sword.

After doing all of this, a faint sheen of sweat had appeared on his forehead as he cast his gaze toward the other stone swords.

Upon witnessing the trouble that the balding elder was having with the trial, everyone was becoming quite apprehensive.

Meanwhile, a layer of faint blue light appeared within Han Li's eyes, and he was staring intently at the stone sword that was hovering in mid-air, seemingly contemplating something.

The balding elder wasted no time as he made another string of hand seals, and a white sword projection vanished into a second stone sword, while his complexion gradually grew paler and paler.

White light flashed erratically over the surface of the second stone sword for a long while before it finally rose up into the air as well.

At this point, sweat was pouring down the balding elder's face, which had become as pale as a sheet of paper, as if he were under extreme strain.

After taking a moment to catch his breath, he gritted his teeth and turned to a third stone sword as he began to make a string of hand seals.

Controlling two stone swords was already close to his limit, and now that he was diverting his attention to a third sword, the two stone swords that were hovering in mid-air immediately began to tremble.

He let loose a low roar, doing everything in his power to stabilize the two airborne stone swords while focusing on lifting the third stone sword as well.

At this point, the giant sword projection above his head had already shrunk down significantly, and it flew through the air before vanishing into the third stone sword in its entirety.

The surface of the third stone sword began flashing with white light, and it looked as if it were about to rise up into the air, but right at this moment, the three stone swords shuddered in unison while emitting bright black light as if they were resonating with one another.

The white light on the surfaces of the three stone swords dissipated in unison, and the two airborne stone swords came crashing back down, plunging themselves deep into the ground.

The balding elder was panting heavily as a look of deep disappointment appeared in his eyes.

"Two stone swords," Xiong Shan declared in an indifferent voice with a slight shake of his head.

Everyone had fallen completely silent with grim looks on their faces.

The balding elder's heart immediately sank at the sight of Xiong Shan's reaction. He knew that there was most likely no chance that he would be chosen, and he heaved a faint sigh before backing away from the stone swords.

"Let me have a go!"

As soon as he stepped down, he was replaced by a red-haired young man, who strode toward the stone swords as dazzling red light began to radiate from his body.

Streaks of sword qi shot forth through the air, forming a massive crimson lotus flower around him. Every single flower petal was formed by countless streaks of crimson sword qi, and he was completely concealed within the lotus flower.

All of a sudden, a burst of crimson ripples erupted out of the lotus flower's stamen before surging into one of the stone swords.

A layer of crimson light instantly appeared on the surface of the stone sword, but just like before, a layer of black light emerged as well to viciously combat the crimson light.

I see... So this is why they're called Origin Defying Stone Swords.

Han Li nodded slightly to himself as blue light flashed within his eyes.

"You were right, Brother Li, there's definitely more to these swords than meets the eye. Can you tell what's so special about them?" Qi Liang asked through voice transmission.

"If I'm not mistaken, the patterns on the stone swords aren't just one type of restriction. Instead, they're able to react differently to those trying to control them in a bid to disrupt any such efforts," Han Li replied.

Qi Liang nodded with a contemplative expression upon hearing this.

While the two of them were conversing with each other, the red-haired young man had already picked up two stone swords, yet this seemed to have been his limit, and the crimson lotus flower around him was already beginning to waver.

Yet another burst of crimson ripples shot out of the lotus flower before surging into a third stone sword, and the stone sword shuddered momentarily, looking as if it were about to rise up into the air as well.

However, right at this moment, the three stone swords began to resonate with each other once again, and the two airborne stone swords instantly came plummeting back down onto the ground.

"Two stone swords. Next," Xiong Shan declared in an expressionless manner.

The crimson lotus flower faded to reveal the red-haired young man, who backed away with a dejected expression.

It looks like controlling three stone swords at once is a bottleneck, Han Li remarked to himself.

A third person immediately stepped up to the plate, but his proficiency in the art of sword manipulation was rather mediocre, and he was only able to lift one stone sword before backing away in embarrassment.

Before long, eight people had attempted the trial, but the most that anyone could lift at once was two stone swords, while the third stone sword stood before everyone like an insurmountable obstacle.

Chapter 206: Moderation

After the eighth person stepped down, a seductive figure took his place.

It was a gorgeous white-robed woman with an extremely alluring figure, but her expression was as cold as ice.

She began to chant an incantation while making a series of hand seals, and rays of white light began to spread from her body like flowing water, forming a ball of white light that began revolving on the spot.

In the next instant, she suddenly switched to a different hand seal, and the ball of white light around her split up into three before surging into three stone swords at once.

Everyone was quite surprised by this approach, and they were looking on intently to see whether she would be able to successfully raise three stone swords at once.

Dazzling white light was glowing around the white-robed woman as she chanted a rapid incantation while flashing through a string of lightning-fast hand seals.

A white halo appeared around each stone sword, wrapping around their blades before lifting them up from the ground.

The three stone swords shuddered in unison, and it appeared that they were about to rise up into the air at once.

However, immediately thereafter, the patterns on the surfaces of the stone swords began to radiate dazzling black light, which pierced into the surrounding white light like sharp swords themselves.

The three white halos flashed erratically, but were able to withstand the assault and slowly lift the three stone swords up from the ground, much to everyone's amazement.

Someone had finally managed to control three of the stone swords at once!

Han Li was also quite impressed.

He recognized this woman as one of the non-native elders, and as a result, all of the elders who were exclaiming in amazement and approval were all formerly itinerant cultivators, while the native elders were far from impressed.

Instead, they felt as if they were being outmatched by the opposing faction, and it was far from a good feeling.

Three swords was clearly already the white-robed woman's limit, but she still attempted to control a fourth sword.

However, as soon as a fourth white halo appeared around the fourth stone swords, all four stone swords began to resonate once again, releasing black light that was far brighter than before and tore the white halos apart with ease.

"Three stone swords," Xiong Shan announced with a slight nod.

The woman heaved a faint sigh of relief, then stepped away from the stone swords.

The trial continued, and with the example set by the white-robed woman, everyone seemed to have been inspired, with the subsequent elders putting up better and better results. Out of the next dozen or so elders, three of them were ultimately managed to control three swords, one of whom was a non-native elder, while the other two were both from the opposing faction of native elders.

Even though this was only a trial, both sides were still treating this as a competition, but they were more reserved than they otherwise would've been had Xiong Shan not been present, only extending some quiet words of praise and encouragement to members of their respective factions.

At the moment, the two factions were evenly matched.

Xiong Shan was aware of the competition that was taking place, but he had no interest in which side was going to come out on top.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Qi Liang, and he closed his eyes, seemingly having been struck by a moment of enlightenment.

A few moments later, his eyes abruptly sprang open again, and an excited look had appeared on his face.

Having observed the proceedings up to this point and taken Han Li's subtle pieces of advice onboard, he was now confident that he would be able to lift three stone swords.

Han Li took a meaningful glance at Qi Liang, then cautioned through voice transmission, "Three swords alone may not be able to guarantee your selection. If you want to ensure that you'll claim a spot, you'll have to go a step beyond that."

"I'm well aware of that, but controlling four stone swords is far too difficult. Given my current level of mastery in sword manipulation, I may not be able to pull off such a feat even if I cultivate arduously for another 1,000 years," Qi Liang replied with a wry smile.

"There's no need to truly lift the fourth sword. All you have to do is use some tricks to put up a performance that's better than the other three sword elders," Han Li said, giving Qi Liang another vital tip.

Qi Liang's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he fell into deep thought once again.

While the two of them were conversing with one another, most of the elders had already undertaken the trial. The number of three sword elders had reached seven at this point, four of which were native elders, while only three were non-native.

The native elders were naturally quite pleased with this, and they were looking at the opposing faction with a hint of derision in their eyes, while the non-native elders were clearly not so happy.

Up to this point, no one had been able to control four stone swords.

"It looks like there's far more to this set of Origin Defying Stone Swords than meets the eye, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong. Allow me to give it a go," Zhu Feng said as he suddenly stepped forward and cupped his fist in a salute toward Xiong Shan.

Xiong Shan was clearly displaying a different attitude toward Zhu Feng compared with the other elders, and there was a hint of anticipation in his voice as he said, "I wasn't the one who invented these Origin Defying Stone Swords. Instead, they're a type of special treasure formerly used by the vastly renowned Boundless Sword Sect of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region to examine the level of sword mastery of its members.

“I managed to obtain them by chance, and it took me a great deal of effort to refine them. It's said that only those who have reached the very pinnacle of sword mastery will be able to control all 10 swords at once. You possess a good level of sword mastery, try and see if you can reach the four sword level."

"I'll do my best," Zhu Feng replied in a respectful voice.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing mention of the Boundless Sword Sect.

Through his past readings, he had learned that this was an ancient sword cultivating sect that championed the way of the sword above all else, and an avid proponent of the idea that a single sword was all that was required to defeat even the most formidable of foes.

What was quite special about this sect was that it had extremely few members, never exceeding 10 members at a time, thereby making it a very mysterious organization.

The reason why the sect was so renowned was because its sect master, the Boundless Daoist, had left behind countless stories of legendary victories across the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

However, for some reason, the sect suddenly fell into obscurity over 1,000,000 years ago, and it had completely disappeared at this point.

As these thoughts were running through Han Li's mind, Zhu Feng had already sprung into action as bright blue light erupted out of his entire body.

Countless thin blue threads then shot forth from his body, while waves of blue light proliferated outward in all directions, and the entire Heavenly Sword Peak was instantly enveloped by an incredibly sharp burst of sword intent.

Everyone present felt as if there were countless tiny blades piercing and slicing to their skin, while a bone-chilling sensation reached straight into the deepest parts of their hearts.

This amount of sword intent naturally felt like nothing more than a gentle spring breeze to Han Li, but Qi Liang abruptly shuddered as he was snapped back to his senses, and a hint of anger flashed through his eyes.

He was on the verge of grasping onto something after receiving those tips from Han Li, but he had been cut off at the most crucial juncture.

Qi Liang took a glance at the situation unfolding before him, then gave a cold harrumph before closing his eyes again as he continued to meditate.

Meanwhile, Zhu Feng was making a string of hand seals, sending countless blue threads sweeping through the air before surging into three of the stone swords at once.

The three stone swords trembled in unison before slowly rising up into the air.

Bright black light erupted from the stone swords in an attempt to struggle free from the blue threads, but the threads were extremely resolute, remaining firmly intact despite the vehement resistance.

There was a serious look on Zhu Feng's face, but he didn't appear to have been under much strain, and he opened his mouth to release another plume of thin blue threads that wrapped themselves around a fourth stone sword.

The four stone swords lit up in unison as streaks of black sword qi were released, slicing viciously against the blue threads.

Most of the blue sword threads were instantly severed, and Zhu Feng's complexion instantly paled as he gave a muffled groan.

As opposed to just ordinary sword threads, these threads were formed by a combination of his essential energy and spiritual power. Hence, the damage inflicted upon them was reciprocated straight to his soul.

Even though most of the blue threads had been severed, there were still some that were clinging on stubbornly, and a sharp gleam flashed through Zhu Feng's eyes as he let loose a loud roar.

The remaining threads instantly began to radiate dazzling blue light before latching onto the fourth stone sword, lifting it out of the ground and into the air.

In the next instant, streaks of black sword qi that were even more formidable than the previous ones emerged, severing all of the remaining blue threads with ease.

Zhu Feng's complexion paled even further as he threw up a mouthful of blood, but an excited look had appeared on his face.

Even though it was only for a moment, he really had managed to control four stone swords.

"With each additional Origin Defying Stone Sword, the difficulty increases by tenfold. Even though it was quite forced, you have reached the four sword level, which is already quite impressive, given the amount of time that you've been cultivating for," Xiong Shan said with an approving nod.

"Thank you for your kind praise, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong," Zhu Feng said as he cupped his fist in a gleeful salute.

"Next," Xiong Shan said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

Zhu Feng stepped away before swallowing a pill, and his complexion quickly recovered.

As soon as he stepped away, he was immediately surrounded by all of the other native elders who showered him with praise.

In stark contrast, the non-native elders were looking far from pleased, feeling as if they were being outmatched by their competition.

The trial continued, and there were fewer than 10 elders left. However, having observed the proceedings for so long, all of the remaining elders had developed some insight into how best to conduct the trial, and it didn't take long before three more elders capable of controlling three swords emerged, two of which were from the non-native elders' camp.

Thus, each side had five three sword elders, but thanks to Zhu Feng's four sword performance, the native elders held a clear edge.

Qi Liang's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this. If he wanted to be selected, then he would have to go beyond just a three sword performance.

Right at this moment, Han Li's voice rang out from beside him. "I'll go take my turn now, Brother Qi."

"Given your powers, this trial is definitely no problem for you. If possible, please attempt a fourth sword to show those other elders what we're made of," Qi Liang replied through voice transmission.

"I'll do my best," Han Li said with a wry smile.

He then took a deep breath, seemingly to steel himself before striding toward the stone swords.

Having observed the proceedings up to this point, his concern wasn't that he wouldn't be able to control enough swords to be selected. Instead, he was worried about attracting too much attention if he were to control too many swords.

In the face of Xiong Shan, who was at the pinnacle of the True Immortal, he had to exercise moderation in order to not stand out excessively.

Xiong Shan faltered slightly at the sight of Han Li, following which a hint of recognition appeared in his eyes. Prior to this, he hadn't noticed Han Li in the crowd.

Thinking back to the pitiful aptitude that Han Li had displayed back at the Ostentatious Palace, Xiong Shan averted his gaze with a derisive look on his face.

Chapter 207: The Fourth Stone Sword

Han Li inhaled slightly as he stood in front of the Origin Defying Stone Swords, then began to chant an incantation while making a series of hand seals.

Streaks of azure spiritual light flew out like swords, surging into the first stone sword in a flash.

All of the non-native elders were rather disappointed to see Han Li adopting such a mundane approach, while all of the native elders looked on with mockery on their faces.

In their eyes, Han Li would've been lucky to control even a single stone sword with such a clumsy approach.

In fact, many of the elders had already turned their eyes elsewhere in disinterest.

The stone sword was enveloped by a layer of azure light, then slowly rose up into the air.

It was constantly releasing black light to combat the azure light, but the latter remained resolute, even though it was flashing erratically.

Han Li pointed a finger forward upon seeing this, and more streaks of azure swordlight surged out of his fingertip before vanishing into a second stone sword.

A burst of azure swordlight enveloped the second stone sword as well, and it also slowly rose up into the air.

Many people turned to Han Li with surprise in their eyes upon this, and they finally returned their attention to the ongoing trial, realizing that they had underestimated Han Li.

Han Li's face had paled slightly after lifting two stone swords, but he didn't appear to have been struggling very much at all.

Is this going to be another three sword performance?

Meanwhile, Qi Liang was watching with a confident smile. He was more aware of Han Li's sword mastery than anyone else present, and he knew that three swords definitely wasn't a problem for Han Li.

What he was concerned about was whether Han Li would be able to lift a fourth sword and rebuke the native elders.

Han Li took a moment to catch his breath, then extended a finger yet again to send a streak of azure light surging into a third stone sword.

Following a string of hand seals, the third stone sword rose up into the air as well, but it did so in a far more sluggish manner than the first two swords, indicating that Han Li was approaching his limits.

"That's three swords!"

A chorus of surprised voices rang out from the elders of both camps.

Xiong Shan was also quite taken aback to see this, and a hint of intrigue had appeared in his eyes.

It seemed that despite Han Li's terrible attitude, he was quite a master of sword manipulation.

The black light released by the three stone swords was causing the azure light to flash erratically, looking as if it would shatter at any moment.

Han Li's complexion paled even further as large beads of sweat appeared on his forehead.

He made a rapid string of hand seals to release one streak of azure light after another, most of which surged into the first three stone swords to stabilize them, while the rest began surging into the fourth stone sword.

The surprise in Xiong Shan's eyes grew even more pronounced upon seeing this, while the chatter among the elders grew even louder.

Even Zhu Feng's brows had furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Qi Liang couldn't help but take a step forward as he stared at the fourth stone sword with a tense look on his face, as if he were the one taking the trial instead of Han Li.

A layer of dazzling azure light appeared over the fourth stone sword, and everyone was watching with bated breath.

The fourth stone sword shuddered slightly before rolling over on the ground and rising up in a shaky fashion. However, in the next instant, dazzling black light erupted from all four of the stone swords in unison, tearing all of the azure light apart.

The four stone swords fell back down onto the ground, while Han Li gave a muffled groan as blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips.

Everyone present was displaying different reactions to Han Li's performance, including elation, disappointment, relief, and surprise.

Qi Liang lowered his head as he heaved a long sigh, while Zhu Feng remained as expressionless as ever, but the looks in his eyes clearly betrayed his relief.

A wistful look appeared in Xiong Shan's eyes as he nodded and said, "I didn't think you would possess such outstanding aptitude in sword manipulation. You're not far away from the four sword level."

"Thank you for your kind praise, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong, I'm still far from reaching that level," Han Li replied in a modest manner.

"It's quite remarkable that you were able to reach this level as an itinerant cultivator. Make sure to work hard in your cultivation so you don't waste your talent," Xiong Shan praised in an uncharacteristic fashion.

Han Li felt this change in Xiong Shan's aptitude to be rather strange, but he still nodded in response.

A dark look appeared in Zhu Feng's eyes upon seeing this, but he quickly composed himself.

Han Li stepped away from the stone swords before taking a seat on the ground with his legs crossed, then took a Core Formation Stage pill that he was planning to bestow upon Meng Yungui and the others to aid in his recovery.

Some of the non-native elders were about to approach him to strike up a conversation, but they could give up on the idea upon seeing this.

The trial continued, and up to this point, Xiong Shan hadn't selected anyone, so it was clear that he was waiting until the end.

Upon making this realization, those who had gone earlier in the trial were left regretting their decision. Perhaps the outcome would've been different for them had they observed for a while longer.

As for those who were still yet to participate in the trial, they were all content to continue to observe, so no one stepped up to take Han L's place.

Xiong Shan's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this. "Why is no one stepping up? Are you forfeiting your right to take the trial? In that case, the trial concludes here..."

"I'll go next, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong," Qi Liang declared, then took a deep breath before striding toward the stone swords.

At this moment, faint azure light was flashing over Han Li's body, making it appear as if he were focusing on his own recovery, but in reality, he was pondering his own performance.

These Origin Defying Stone Swords did indeed provide quite a unique challenge, and Han Li was confident that he would've been able to at least control five swords had he gone all out. Perhaps he could've even challenged a sixth sword, but unfortunately, there was no way to find out, and that left him feeling a little forlorn.

However...

A thought suddenly occurred to him, and a barely detectable smile appeared on his face.

All of a sudden, the ground trembled violently as three stone swords came plummeting back down to earth.

Qi Liang's face had turned quite pale, but his eyes were full of elation.

Thanks to Han Li's guidance, he had put up a stellar performance, lifting three stone swords before also moving a fourth stone sword, so he had all but assured himself of one of the 10 available spots.

Han Li gave an undetectable nod of approval upon seeing this.

He had offered Qi Liang this guidance in order to repay him for acting as the guide that integrated him into the Blaze Dragon Dao.

"Three swords," Xiong Shan declared with a slight nod.

It didn't take long before all of the remaining elders had attempted the trial, but no one else was able to control three stone swords after Qi Liang.

Han Li opened his eyes before rising to his feet.

Out of the 40 or so inner sect elders who had taken on this mission, a total of 13 had managed to control three or more swords.

Among them, six were native elders, only one fewer than the non-native elder camp, and Zhu Feng was the only one who had managed to control four swords. However, Han Li and Qi Liang had both been able to budge a fourth sword, so ultimately, the two camps were quite evenly matched.

During the past contests between the two factions, the native elders had always held the upper hand due to the advantages that they enjoyed when it came to many aspects, such as resource allocation, so this outcome was naturally an extremely encouraging one for the non-native elders.

Only then did Xiong Shan slowly make his way toward the center of the room before sweeping his gaze over all of the elders assembled.

Those who had only managed to move one or two swords knew that they had no chance of being selected, so they were quite relaxed, and Zhu Feng's selection was obviously guaranteed. Hence, the only ones that were nervous were the 20 people who had managed to move three swords.

After a brief pause, Xiong Shan declared, "Zhu Feng, Li Feiyu, Qi Liang... Zhen Qi. The 10 of you can stay, the rest can leave."

Out of the 10 chosen, five were native elders, while the other five were non-native elders.

The bearded man with the Nan surname approached Han Li and Qi Liang, then cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "Congratulations, Brother Li, Brother Qi. If it wasn't for the two of you, we'd be looked down on again!"

His sword mastery wasn't of a very high level, and he was only just barely able to lift two stone swords, so he naturally wasn't selected, but he had quite an easygoing personality and wasn't bitter about it.

"I was just lucky," Qi Liang replied with a smile.

The other non-native elders expressed their congratulations to the five who were chosen, then promptly departed, leaving only Xiong Shan and the 10 selected elders in the hall.

A pleased look appeared on Xiong Shan's face at the sight of the 10 people standing before him, and he was just about to say something when a streak of black light suddenly appeared in the distant sky.

It was approaching like a bolt of black lightning, arriving directly above everyone in the blink of an eye amid a deafening thunderclap.

The streak of black light crashed down onto the drill ground, causing the entire area to shudder slightly, following which a purple-robed man was revealed.

The man wasn't exactly hideous in appearance, but his entire body was pitch-black in color, as if he had been smoked. He was over twice as tall as the average person, and his arms were as thick as a normal person's waist, while his fists were the size of washbasins. His entire body was comprised of thick bands of muscle that resembled black steel, causing his purple robe to bulge in many places.

"Brother Mo, this is my cave abode, not your Immortal Origin Palace. Don't you think it's a little inappropriate for you to just barge in like this?" Xiong Shan asked in a cold voice.

"My apologies, Brother Xiong. I heard that you were gathering sword cultivators to activate an array, so I immediately came here," the purple-robed man chortled, and his voice was so loud and penetrative that Han Li and the others could feel their eardrums ringing slightly.

Even though he was extending an apology, there was no hint of apology at all in his expression and the tone of his voice.

Xiong Shan gave a cold harrumph and didn't pursue the matter any further.

"Come to think of it, why didn't you tell me that you were going to use that sword array, Brother Xiong? According to our agreement, I lent you those things under the promise that I would be present when you refine your bonded treasure. Are you planning to go back on our agreement, Brother Xiong?" the purple-robed man asked.

"Is there any need for me to inform you? You know every little thing that goes on on my Heavenly Sword Peak like the back of your hand," Xiong Shan replied in a cold voice.

"Surely you jest, Brother Xiong," the purple-robed man chortled.

"Brother Li, this is Elder Mo Xie of the Immortal Origin Palace. It's said that he ran for the position of deputy dao lord 10,000 years ago, and after failing, he went into seclusion for close to 10,000 years, emerging far more powerful than before. I've heard that he's extremely close to reaching the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage," Qi Liang informed.

Han Li gave a slight nod in response.

After hearing Xiong Shan refer to the purple-robed man as Brother Mo, Han Li had already guessed that this was Elder Mo Xie.

"Looks like these are the sword cultivators that you've gathered to help you. Tsk tsk, they don't look that great. I hope they can pull their weight," Mo Xie said as he took a condescending glance at Han Li and the others.

"That's not something for you to worry about. Let's go!" Xiong Shan harrumphed coldly, then flew into the distance as a streak of golden light.

Han Li and the others quickly followed along, while Mo Xie also sprang up into the air as a streak of black light.

……

Not long after the departure of Xiong Shan and the others, a group of white-robed servants of the Heavenly Sword Peak made their way onto the plaza in an orderly fashion. All of them were at the Core Formation Stage, and they quickly set about carrying the Origin Defying Stone Swords away.

Not only were these stone swords very difficult to control, they were also extremely heavy, and it took around a dozen Core Formation cultivators just to be able to lift a single one of them.

Right as these people were beginning to lift the fourth stone sword, one of them suddenly let loose a cry of surprise, immediately drawing everyone's attention.

"What's going on, Senior Martial Brother Wang?"

"Look at the underside of this sword!"

Chapter 208: Heavenly Sword Tomb

All of the Core Formation cultivators turned to inspect the underside of the fourth Origin Defying Stone Sword upon hearing this, and they were greeted by a peculiar sight.

A small line of text had appeared on the underside of the sword, and it read: "The number one sword cultivator of Heavenly South was here". [1]

It appeared that someone had forcibly engraved this line of text onto the surface of the sword, and every single stroke resembled a sharp sword in itself.

"What happened? I don't think this line of text was there before..."

"Could it be that one of the inner sect elders who just undertook the trial did this?"

"That's impossible! Deputy Dao Lord Xiong once said that these Origin Defying Stone Swords don't have any offensive power, but they're as hard as immortal treasures!"

"Then who could've done this?"

"It doesn't matter, just remember to never speak of this to anyone and pretend as if you saw nothing here. If Deputy Dao Lord Xiong finds out about this, all of us will be in huge trouble!"

"Of course."

"You're right, we have to keep this a secret."

"By the way, what kind of place is Heavenly South?"

"Who knows? Probably some insignificant place in the middle of nowhere..."

The chatter continued as the group of Core Formation cultivators carried the fourth Origin Defying Stone Sword away from the plaza.

……

Meanwhile, Xiong Shan and the others had descended to the foot of the Heavenly Sword Peak, where they were hovering in the air in front of a golden mountain face.

With a rustle of his sleeves, four streaks of golden sword qi were released by Xiong Shan, and they circled around momentarily in the air before vanishing into a certain section of the mountain face up ahead.

Initially, the mountain face remained completely unmoved, and it was as if the two streaks of golden sword qi had simply vanished. However, in the next instant, bright golden light began to radiate from the surface of the mountain face, and countless golden runes sprang forth, intertwining in mid-air to form a strange diagram that resembled a sword array.

The section of the mountain face encompassed within the golden light gradually turned semi-transparent, and Mo Xie chuckled, "So this is the entrance of your vastly renowned Heavenly Sword Tomb. What an eye-opening sight this is."

Xiong Shan wore a solemn expression, and he offered no reply to Mo Xie as he swept his sleeves through the air while chanting an incantation, and more streaks of golden sword 1i flew out of his sleeve before vanishing into the sword array, making it become clearer and clearer.

Han Li was inspecting the sword array before him with an intrigued expression, and through it, he could see a black passageway slowly taking shape on the mountain face.

Meanwhile, a hint of excitement had appeared on Qi Liang's face.

"You seem very excited, Brother Qi," Han Li remarked through voice transmission.

"You've only recently joined our sect, so it's no surprise that you haven't heard of the Heavenly Sword Tomb. Deputy Dao Lord Xiong is a renowned sword collector in our sect, and it's said that he's collected countless powerful swords in this Heavenly Sword Tomb, making it an extremely renowned place.

“However, it's also an extremely mysterious place, and barely anyone in the sect has had a chance to see it. I never thought that he would take us into the Heavenly Sword Tomb today. It looks like he must be intending to refine a treasure in there," Qi Liang explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a contemplative nod, and he was also becoming rather intrigued.

At this point, Xiong Shan had already reached the final stage of his incantation, and the golden light radiating from the mountain face was growing even brighter, gradually forming a thick golden light barrier with countless runes shimmering on its surface.

A string of dull thumps rang out, and seven indentations appeared on the golden light barrier in a circular formation.

Xiong Shan abruptly ceased his chanting as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing seven balls of white light that contained seven golden crescent-shaped talisman-like objects.

The seven golden talismans flew through the air before fitting seamlessly into the indentations on the light barrier at his behest.

Countless runes began to surge out of the golden light barrier, which gradually became thinner as the flow of runes continued, and the light barrier finally completely vanished after a full 15 minutes had passed.

A black passageway was revealed, and it was unclear where it led to. It was also impossible to examine what laid beyond the entrance with one's spiritual sense as some type of sensory restriction present.

"Come in," Xiong Shan said before leading the way into the passageway, followed closely by Mo Xie and everyone else.

Once everyone had entered the passageway, a burst of golden light surged over the mountain face, and the entrance of the passageway was closed again.

The dark passageway was quite long, and everyone only reached the conclusion after walking for a full 15 minutes. At the end of the passageway was a giant azure stone gate that was quite antiquated in appearance with countless runes engraved onto its surface.

Xiong Shan pulled out a badge before gently waving it at the azure stone gate, and a layer of azure light instantly appeared over the surface of the gate, as if it had awakened after a long slumber.

The azure light warped momentarily before forming an array that was even more complex than the one on the mountain face outside.

Immediately thereafter, Xiong Shan swept a sleeve through the air, and nine small azure swords came flying out one after another before plunging themselves into nine different parts of the stone gate.

The array on the surface of the stone gate flashed momentarily before gradually fading, and the gate slowly swung open.

Right at this moment, an incredibly bright burst of light erupted out from within, and the eruption of light had come so abruptly that everyone outside reflexively closed their eyes.

As the burst of dazzling light enveloped everyone, they instantly vanished from within the passageway, and by the time Han Li reopened his eyes, he could hear the sound of howling wind blowing past his ears.

It was as if the entire space were filled with countless bursts of powerful sword intent that were surging toward him from all directions.

After taking a moment to gather himself, he inspected his surroundings to find that he was standing on a vast grassland.

The grassland was riddled with dome-shaped graves, each of which had a flying sword plunged into it, and there were over 1,000 flying swords present.

Dispersed between the countless graves were 10 massive black stone pillars, each of which was separated by hundreds of kilometers, splitting up the entire Heavenly Sword Tomb into 10 sections.

Furthermore, there were three teams of cultivators stationed in each section, with each team consisting of a Grand Ascension Stage leader and nine Body Integration cultivators, amounting to a total of 300 cultivators.

Han Li swept his gaze over the grassland, and there was only a hint of surprise on his face, but in reality, he was astonished by what he was seeing.

Among the flying swords plunged into the graves, some were as slender as willow branches, some were as wide as palace gates, some were giving off glacial qi that had frozen all of the grass in a radius of several hundred feet, and some were burning with scorching flames that scorched the earth around them...

Every single one of the flying swords was swaying slightly from side to side while emitting a faint ringing sound, and astonishing sword qi was surging straight into the heavens, slicing all of the clouds up above into thin ribbons.

There were also some flying swords that would occasionally begin trembling violently while giving off a piercing screech as they attempted to pull themselves out of their graves. Whenever this happened, the cultivators stationed nearby would immediately make a string of hand seals to quell the unrest.

However, there were so many flying swords on the grassland that as soon as one flying sword was restrained, another one would begin struggling, with some even managing to pull themselves out of their graves altogether, so the cultivators present were constantly kept on their toes.

However, these cultivators seemed to have already grown accustomed to this, and they were able to perform their duties in a calm and orderly fashion.

Every single one of these flying swords was an exceptional treasure that a Body Integration or even a Grand Ascension cultivator would've sacrificed all of their belongings to acquire, and some of the premium flying swords in this tomb would've been extremely alluring even to True Immortal cultivators.

Such an astonishing collection of flying swords gathered in a single place would've been enough to shock anyone as this was no longer something that could've been acquired through wealth alone.

All of the True Immortal cultivators present had flying swords as their bonded treasures and were extremely proficient in the art of sword manipulation, so they were even more astonished by this extraordinary sight.

Zhu Feng reluctantly withdrew his gaze from the vast array of flying swords around him as he turned to Xiong Shan with an admiring expression and praised, "I had always heard that Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's Heavenly Sword Tomb was an extraordinary place, but even all of the rumors I've heard fail to do this place justice. I am truly humbled by what I have been shown today..."

There was some element of flattery to his words, but no one else found it to be overly sycophantic as they were thinking the same thing.

"I spent a great deal of time and effort over the past tens of thousands of years to gather these swords, and I must say, it was no easy task collecting the 1,080 flying swords required to form this sword array," Xiong Shan replied as a hint of pride flashed through his eyes.

However, Han Li wasn't listening to this conversation at all as his gaze was focused intently on the northwestern direction of the Heavenly Sword Tomb.

This was because there were 72 graves in that area, plunged into each of which was an azure flying sword. All of the azure flying swords were trembling incessantly as thin arcs of golden lightning flashed over them, as if they were trying to struggle free from their graves.

These 72 azure flying swords were none other than the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that Han Li was searching for!

The flying swords seemed to have detected Han Li's presence, and they began to struggle even more violently, releasing dazzling arcs of lightning as they did so.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and his first instinct was naturally to take back his flying swords.

However, there was no way that he could simply ask for them from Xiong Shan, and attempting to take them by force would've been no different from committing suicide.

With that in mind, he immediately suppressed his burning desire to recover his flying swords as he cut off the spiritual connection between himself and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

[1]. Heavenly South is a continent in the Mortal Realm that Han Li came from. For more information, check out https://a-record-of-a-mortal-is-journey-to-immortality.fandom.com/wiki/Heavenly_South.

[Back]

Chapter 209: Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Array

With the spiritual connection severed, the lightning flashing from the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords immediately faded. However, for some reason, they were still struggling incessantly as if they were attempting to free themselves from their graves.

The three teams of cultivators stationed in that area immediately sprang into action upon seeing this, casting a series of incantation seals onto the graves of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which immediately began to glow with azure light while releasing bursts of tremendous restrictive force.

Even so, they were still unable to completely suppress the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords' resistance, and several of them were still struggling violently, as if they were trying to break free.

"What's going on, Senior Martial Brother Ye Feng? These flying swords have always done this every once in a while, but they've never been this hard to restrain," a purple-haired man mused with a perplexed expression.

Seated beside him was a dark-skinned young man who offered no reply, but he stood up from the ground before making his way over to the flying swords, then made a hand seal before raising his hands up into the air.

Several palm-sized black rocks instantly flew up into the air, then circled around in a series of gentle arcs before landing on the graves that the flying swords were plunged into with unerring accuracy.

The surfaces of these rocks were quite coarse, and they were giving off a faint black glow. They appeared to be quite ordinary, but in reality, these were Sword Restraining Stones, a type of strange material that could temporarily suppress the spiritual nature of flying swords.

As the Sword Restraining Stones descended from above, the graves began to glow brighter and brighter, while the struggles of the flying swords began to subside, and the arcs of lightning surging over them also faded.

Just like the Sword Restraining Stones, there was also more than met the eye to these unremarkable-looking graves. Not only were they able to nurture the flying swords that they held, ensuring that their spiritual nature didn't seep away without their former owners' care, they also restricted the swords and prevented them from flying away.

Once all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had settled down, Ye Feng returned to his original spot before taking a seat again.

The purple-haired man could only heave an internal sigh upon seeing this.

Ye Feng had been one of the brightest rising stars in the sect, but for some reason, on a certain day several years ago, his personality suddenly underwent a massive change. He became extremely quiet, and his rapidly advancing cultivation base also stagnated, much to Elder Mo Xie's displeasure.

As these thoughts were running through the purple-haired man's mind, someone else approached him and said, "This is the final day that we'll be on duty in this Heavenly Sword Tomb. From tomorrow onward, we're going to struggle to find missions that are this safe and easy to complete while still yielding consistent merit points every month."

"Weren't you just complaining last time that this is the most boring mission you've ever been on?" the purple-haired man chuckled.

Meanwhile, at the entrance of the tomb, Han Li had severed his spiritual connection to the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, but his attention was still fixed on them.

Upon noticing that Ye Feng was one of the people looking after the swords here, one of the mysteries that had stumped him this entire time was solved.

Back when he first arrived in the Bell Toll Mountain Range, there was an occasion where Daoist Xie and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords' auras had been cut off at the same time. As a result, he had assumed that they were together, and he was quite disappointed to have recovered Daoist Xie, only for there to still be no trace of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

It had to have been the case that Ye Feng just so happened to have been on duty in the sword tomb on that day, and by activating the restrictive array here, both Daoist Xie and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords' auras had been concealed at the same time, thereby leading to this misconception.

"I'm now going to tell you all about the mission that I gathered you here to complete," Xiong Shan said as he swept his gaze over everyone.

All of the True Immortal Stage elders, including Mo Xie, immediately fell silent to listen to what Xiong Shan had to say.

"The array that you're seeing right now is called the Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array. Through the use of this array, I can erase the marks of the previous owners left in all of the flying swords in the Heavenly Sword Tomb and convert them into pure sword essence. My aim is to infuse all of this sword essence into my bonded flying sword," Xiong Shan declared.

Everyone was quite stunned by this declaration.

If it really were possible to gather all of the sword essence of these exceptional flying swords and infuse them into a single flying sword, then there was a very good chance that the recipient flying sword would become an Acquired Immortal Treasure of unimaginable power.

"As I'm sure you've already figured out, aside from the sword offering platform at the center, this place is split up into 10 areas. I need one of you in each area to control the flying swords there and help me erase the marks in those flying swords and convert them into sword essence," Xiong Shan continued.

Everyone immediately began to scour their surroundings upon hearing this, as if they were deciding which area they wanted.

Han Li was doing the same thing while pondering what Xiong Shan had just said, trying to gather some useful information from his words.

The graves in the sword tomb appeared to have been arranged in a random and haphazard fashion, but in reality, there was a clear order to them. For example, flying swords with similar sword intent or came from the same origins would often be placed in the same area, while flying swords with conflicting sword intents would be split up into different areas.

At the center of each area was a black stone pillar that was over 30 feet thick and in excess of 100 feet tall. These were the array cores of each area, and each stone pillar had around a dozen longan-sized Immortal Origin Stones embedded into them.

Just this impressive collection of Immortal Origin Stones alone was already a stunning sight for all of the True Immortal Stage elders present.

"If you ask me, you should've erased the marks of the original owners of the flying swords in advance. Wouldn't that have made things far more convenient?" Mo Xie asked.

"You don't know anything! Once a mark is erased from a flying sword, it'll lose the majority of its spiritual nature, and what little remains will continue to seep away over time. Only by erasing the marks during the refinement process can I preserve their original spiritual nature and power to the greatest extent," Xiong Shan harrumphed coldly.

"I see, I've been enlightened," Mo Xie replied with a nonchalant smile.

Xiong Shan didn't waste any more time with words as he summoned a shimmering golden flying sword with a flick of his wrist.

The sword was over three feet in length and roughly two inches wide. It was entirely golden in color and was giving off peerlessly sharp sword intent. At the tip of the sword's hilt was a fearsome-looking ancient beast with its mouth wide open, and its eyes were giving off a sharp gleam,a s if it were an actual living creature.

Everyone only took a single glance at the sword before looking away, as if they felt like the light radiating from the sword was too sharp for their eyes to behold without incurring harm.

"As expected of your bonded flying sword, Fellow Daoist Xiong. After the past few years of preparation, it's become even more formidable than before! Once its refinement is complete, I'm sure you'll be able to use it to reach the Golden Immortal Stage after a few more centuries of seclusion," Mo Xie praised as his eyes lit up with amazement.

"Thank you for your kind words, Fellow Daoist Mo."

After summoning his bonded flying sword, Xiong Shan's aura had become even more formidable than before. He let loose a long roar as he rose up into the air alongside his sword, then flashed through the sky several times like lightning before arriving on the sword offering platform at the center of the grassland.

The platform was 360 feet in radius and 720 feet tall. It was entirely constructed from a glittering and translucent jade-like material, and there were all types of complex array patterns engraved upon it, as well as many unknown spirit stones embedded onto its surface, connecting together to form a massive array that encompassed the entire platform.

"I've been preparing for this day for tens of thousands of years. If everything goes well, we'll all be happy, but let me make this clear: if any one of you drops the ball at a critical moment, don't blame me for turning on you after the event," Xiong Shan said to Han Li and the others.

"Rest assured, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong, I'll be sure to do everything in my power to ensure everything goes smoothly," Zhu Feng vowed as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Several other native elders quickly followed suit and made similar promises, while Han Li and the non-native elders nodded in response.

"Get into position!"

With that declaration from Xiong Shan, Han Li and the other elders flew up into the air before racing toward different parts of the grassland.

Han Li immediately flew toward the northwest as a streak of azure light, but midway through his flight, he suddenly drew to an abrupt halt.

In the same instant, Zhu Feng flew past him, giving a derisive harrumph while glancing at Han Li out of the corner of his eye as he did so. He then flew into the area that the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were situated in before drifting down toward the black stone pillar in that area.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, following which he turned and flew toward an area in the southwest.

These areas weren't split up very evenly, and not all of the areas had orderly shapes. Furthermore, the number of flying swords in each area also differed, with some containing only several dozen swords, while others contained over 100. The area where the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were situated was reserved only for the set of 72 swords.

If one had to describe exactly what shape the Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array was, then it could only be likened to a flower bud that was about to bloom. The sword offering platform at the center of the area was like a stamen of the flower, while the 10 areas were like the petals around the stamen.

After everyone had adopted their positions, Xiong Shan brought his palms together in front of him before making a hand seal, and the golden flying sword hovering in front of him instantly began to radiate dazzling golden light.

He then began to chant an incantation, and there seemed to have been some type of strange force in the sword tomb resonating with his incantation, producing a sound that resembled heavenly music ringing out across the entire sky.

At the same time, the sword offering platform beneath him also began to glow brightly, as did the array on the platform.

A burst of loud rumbling rang out from the platform, and a white jade altar with side lengths of around three feet each began to slowly rise up from its center.

The altar was riddled with runes, and at its center was a black hole that perfectly matched the width of the sword.

Chapter 210: Chaotic Swords Dance

Xiong Shan's incantation continued as he grabbed onto the hilt of the golden longsword with both hands, then slowly plunged it into the hole on the white jade altar.

A grating sound rang out, and as soon as the sword was plunged into the altar, the entire sword offering platform instantly shuddered violently, following which a dazzling pillar of white light rose up from its surface and erupted straight into the heavens.

At the same time, the Immortal Origin Stones embedded into the black stone pillars in all of the 10 areas began to glow brightly while releasing bursts of abundant spiritual power, which flowed into the patterns on the stone pillars like water.

The 10 black stone pillars shuddered in unison before releasing pillars of dazzling black light that shot high up into the sky.

The shreds of clouds in the sky were scattered even further by these pillars of light, and a gray light barrier that was visible even to the naked eye appeared up above, encompassing the entire sword tomb like an upside-down bowl.

A hint of excitement appeared in Xiong Shan's eyes upon seeing this, and his quiet chanting suddenly grew significantly louder, ringing out like thunderclaps in the heavens.

All of a sudden, golden light began to flash from the gray light barrier, forming a series of golden threads that connected with one another while swaying incessantly.

At the same time, a buzzing sound that resembled the flapping of wasp wings rang out across the entire sword tomb, and the sound was becoming louder and louder.

Han Li looked around to find that all of the flying swords in the area that he was situated in had begun to sway violently in unison, looking as if they were struggling with all their might to free themselves from their graves.

Due to how rapidly they were swaying from side to side, they were leaving sector-shaped afterimages above their graves.

Through his spiritual connection with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, Han Li could feel a sense of intense fear, one that was shared by all of the other flying swords. It seemed that all of the swords in the sword tomb were terrified and wanted to leave this place.

He couldn't help but think back to how he had nurtured those Golden Lightning Bamboo trees back in the Mortal Realm, and how he had painstakingly refined those 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords. An indescribable feeling welled up in his heart as these thoughts flashed through his mind.

On his long cultivation journey thus far, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were the treasures that had been with him the longest aside from the Heaven Controlling Vial, enduring countless life and death situations alongside him.

At this moment, these flying swords that were connected to his soul were about to have their marks erased and their sword essence extracted, and Han Li was desperate to save them.

He wanted nothing more than to rescue his swords and flee the scene, but that would've been impossible.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords seemed to have sensed his despair, and all of them began ringing even more loudly, as if they were working up the resolve to do something.

Through their spiritual connection, Han Li could sense the decision that they had made. If Han Li were unable to rescue them, then they would rather self-detonate than have their marks erased and be integrated into another sword.

Right at this moment, a faint buzzing sound suddenly rang out in the sky.

Han Li immediately looked up to find that all of the golden lines on the gray light barrier in the sky had fallen still, and they had formed countless golden sword visages.

These swords were all of different shapes and forms, with some as straight as arrows, while others had curved blades, and resembled ancient rulers, while others were shaped like sharp spikes.

Their sizes also varied drastically, with some standing at several thousand feet in size, resembling massive boats, while some were only around an inch in length, bearing a closer resemblance to a needle than a sword.

Thanks to Han Li's exceptional eyesight, he was able to see that even the tiniest of those swords were inscribed with a complete set of runes, and there weren't any visible imperfections.

As the giant sword array appeared, the sword qi within the entire heavenly sword tomb had swelled to several dozen times its original volume, and all of the grass on the ground was instantly torn to shreds, while a sharp aura permeated through the air.

The expressions of Han Li and the other inner sect elders standing on the black stone pillars all changed slightly upon seeing this.

The three teams that were stationed in each area were also looking on with solemn expressions as they remained completely still on the spot, not daring to move even in the slightest for fear of being torn to shreds by the sword qi that was surging around them.

All of a sudden, a hint of befuddlement welled up in Han Li's heart. Somehow, he felt like what he was witnessing right at this moment was rather familiar to him.

Right at this moment, all of the elders who were looking at the sword array up above gave a muffled groan in unison, as if they had been struck by an invisible blow, and all of them were forced to avert their eyes.

Even Mo Xie was only able to look at the sword array for fewer than 20 seconds before he was forced to look away by the sharp, unbearable pain in his consciousness.

Han Li was also experiencing the same thing, but thanks to his enormous spiritual sense, he was able to keep inspecting the array without pain after blinking a couple of times.

Right at this moment, Xiong Shan's voice suddenly rang out in everyone's minds. "The sword qi contained within this Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array is quite harmful to spiritual sense, so I'd advise all of you not to look at it for too long."

Everyone naturally averted their eyes upon hearing this, not daring to try and glean the secrets that the sword array harbored any longer.

In contrast, a hint of enlightenment suddenly appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

Back in that immortal abode in the Vast Glacial Realm, he had once obtained a Myriad Sword Scroll, and the aura and permutations of the sword array on that scroll were very similar to the sword array that he was witnessing at this moment. [1]

There were even some parts of the myriad sword artwork that were even more profound than this array.

He was quite elated upon making this realization, and he hurriedly began to carefully inspect the sword array up above.

A short while later, Xiong Shan suddenly let loose a thunderous roar from the sword offering platform, causing the entire grassland to shudder.

Immediately thereafter, a string of cracks and pops began ringing out incessantly as the graves on the grassland exploded one after another.

As a result, all of the flying swords in the entire sword tomb were released, and they began flying wildly in all directions, trying to escape from the tomb that they had been trapped in for so long.

The 30 teams stationed in the sword tomb immediately sprang into action, unleashing various abilities to control the flying swords.

In the eastern part of the grassland, a flying sword that was completely enveloped in scorching flames was flying straight up toward the heavens, leaving such a scorching trail of heat in its wake that the surrounding air was popping incessantly.

The three teams in that area immediately began to chant an incantation in unison, summoning a massive water dragon under the guidance of the three Grand Ascension cultivators, with which they were able to quickly drag back the fiery sword.

In the southern part of the grassland, a giant yellow sword that was around three feet wide and 18 feet long. The sword was giving off an earthy yellow radiance, and instead of rising up into the heavens like the other flying swords, it aimed its tip at the ground, then began rapidly revolving on the spot, attempting to burrow itself into the earth.

The three teams stationed there were already prepared for this, and under their joint efforts, the ground in that area had already turned a dark azure color and become as solid as rock, so no matter how much the giant sword attempted to drill itself into the ground, it was only able to raise a flurry of sparks in futility.

After Han Li's 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were freed, they immediately gathered together like a swarm of bees with golden lightning flashing around them as they set off rapidly in Han Li's direction.

However, due to the fact that there were swords flying all over the place, it would've been impossible to discern the intentions of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords unless one were paying particular attention to them.

"Stop those swords!" Zhu Feng immediately ordered upon seeing this.

The three teams situated in that area immediately sprang into action, unleashing their abilities as they drew upon the spiritual qi around them to form a massive cage formed by streaks of azure spiritual qi, which began to descend upon the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The swords had only managed to fly for less than 10 kilometers before they were stopped in their tracks by the azure cage.

Lightning flashed through the air as all 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords began to glow with dazzling golden light, releasing countless arcs of golden lightning that tore the azure cage into shreds.

Through their spiritual connection, he could sense that there was a hint of rage in the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords as they unleashed their Divine Devilbane Lightning, but there was nothing that he could do at the moment aside from emulating the other elders and restraining the flying swords in his area.

"Useless idiots!" Zhu Feng spat as he looked on with a disdainful expression.

He then made a grabbing motion, and several massive marks appeared out of thin air, enveloping the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords before forcibly dragging them back.

Xiong Shan seemed to have already anticipated this retaliation from the swords, and he only took a few glances at the unfolding situation before paying it no further heed.

Soon, most of the flying swords were restrained one after another, but there were still some that were unwilling to be controlled, constantly attempting to fly out of the sword tomb, while others were only able to fly in small, restricted areas, crashing into one another over and over again amid a string of incessant clangs.

Han Li was controlling the flying swords in his area while simultaneously recollecting the myriad sword artwork from the past.

Thanks to his experience in studying the myriad sword artwork, he was able to make very fast progress in his examination of the sword array up above, and he was quickly able to make several important observations. However, he was still far away from completely understanding it.

Right at this moment, Xiong Shan suddenly ceased in his chanting, then abruptly sprang up into the air before flying toward the east.

After entering the area that Qi Liang was situated in, he made a grabbing motion with one hand, and a massive golden palm projection appeared in the sky before closing itself around a silver flying sword.

The silver flying sword immediately began to struggle with all its might while bright silver radiance surged out of its blade like flowing water. It then transformed into hundreds of silver sword projections that fled in all directions, attempting to tear through the golden hand projection, but its efforts proved to be completely futile.

Xiong Shan raised his other hand and brought his hand together like a blade, manifesting another golden palm projection in the air before smearing it over the silver flying sword.

The silver sword shuddered violently as a layer of semi-transparent light appeared over its surface before being stripped away inch by inch by the second golden palm projection. As this process unfolded, the silver sword turned into a semi-transparent flying sword, as if it had become a spiritual sword, and it hovered obediently in mid-air, no longer displaying any movement.

[1]. For more information on the Vast Glacial Realm and the Myriad Sword Scroll, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1594: Vast Glacial Realm and Chapter 1710: Golden Sword, respectively.

[Back]

Chapter 211: Reversal

Xiong Shan slowly released the silver flying sword, which had already been completely stripped of its sword essence and spiritual nature at this point, and the sword came plummeting out of the sky before being torn to shreds by the sword qi surging throughout the sword tomb before it even had a chance to land on the ground.

Xiong Shan didn't even bother to take a glance at the destroyed flying sword, and he had already turned his attention to another curved longsword that resembled a snake.

He then extended a hand forward once again to repeat the same process.

Han Li only took a quick glance in that direction before turning his focus back to the sword array up above.

In the past, he had studied the myriad sword artwork in order to cultivate the Sword Observation Art, so he hadn't focused much of his efforts on studying the permutations of sword arrays through the artwork.

However, as he observed the sword array on this occasion, he found that he was filling in many of the gaps in his knowledge in this regard.

At its core, this sword array was constructed through the utilization of sword qi.

All arrays had a core and certain key points, and as long as one could find those key points, there would be a way to destroy or tamper with the array.

Time slowly passed by, and close to a day flew by in the blink of an eye.

Through his observation, Han Li had already found many important points on the array, but it was still impossible for him to disable the array without detection.

If he were to forcibly disable the array, that would be no different from taking his flying swords by force, so he had no choice but to continue to observe and bide his time.

During this time, Xiong Shan had already extracted the sword essence out of several hundred flying swords from several areas in the east and in the south.

At this moment, half of the sky above the grassland was riddled with flying swords that had been converted into a spiritual form.

Right at this moment, Xiong Shan flew toward an area in the western part of the grassland, then reached out and made a grabbing motion toward a giant sword with a wide blade.

At this point, his complexion was looking a little pale, indicating that this refinement process had been quite taxing on him, but his expression was glowing with elation, and there was a look of excitement in his eyes.

Meanwhile, Han Li's gaze was still fixed intently on the array up above as he carefully observed the countless sword visages in the sky.

All of a sudden, he noticed that something seemed to have changed in the sword array compared with its starting point, but he was unable to put his finger on exactly what had changed.

However, he had a feeling that this point of difference was quite possibly the only opportunity that he had to alter the array and recover his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

However, the more he tried to concentrate, the more elusive that point of difference proved to be, and he was starting to feel a little agitated.

It didn't take long before Xiong Shan wiped away the marks of the original owners of all of the flying swords in the area around him.

Up to this point, the majority of the flying swords on the grassland had already been converted into pure sword essence.

After converting all of the flying swords in one area into sword essence, Xiong Shan didn't immediately move onto the next area. Instead, he flipped a hand over to prepare a pair of pills that he promptly devoured before turning in Han Li's direction.

He then shifted his gaze toward the area that Zhu Feng was in, and his gaze alternated between the two areas a couple of times, as if he were deliberating which area to move onto next.

At this point, Han Li was feeling so agitated that sweat was already beginning to bead up on his forehead, but he still hadn't found a way out of this predicament.

He took a deep breath as he came to a decision. Instead of continuing to observe the sword array, he closed his eyes and forcibly infiltrated it with his spiritual sense.

As soon as his spiritual sense entered the array, Han Li instantly felt a burst of sharp pain spearing through his soul, as if there were hundreds of swords piercing into his soul at once, producing a sensation of indescribable agony.

However, he refused to back down, and he gritted his teeth as he forcibly withstood the assault with his immense spiritual sense.

Meanwhile, Xiong Shan's attention was focused entirely on the task at hand, while the other elders didn't dare to release their spiritual sense to examine the sword array for fear of incurring spiritual harm, so no one noticed what Han Li was doing.

After taking a moment to digest the two pills, Xiong Shan's complexion recovered a little, and in the end, his gaze settled on the northwestern area before he set off in that direction.

He reached out with one hand to conjure up a golden palm projection in the air, which grabbed toward one of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The flying sword seemed to have detected the impending peril, and it began to tremble while screeching incessantly, producing a sound much like the sobs of a woman.

To Han Li, it sounded as if the sword were expressing its despair and displeasure at Han Li's inaction in its hour of need.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, while a barely detectable smile appeared on his face.

In the next instant, the flying sword that was caught within the grasp of the golden palm projection abruptly ceased in its trembling and screeching, hovering in mid-air without any further movement.

The other 71 flying swords that were originally flying in all directions also fell still at once, as if they had received some type of instruction. All of them were highly focused soldiers preparing for battle, remaining completely still to conserve their energy.

Zhu Feng was initially quite glad to see that all of these unruly flying swords had suddenly settled down, but for some reason, a hint of foreboding then suddenly welled up in his heart.

Sure enough, his intuition proved to be correct.

Right as the golden palm projection was about to completely close itself around the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, a loud thunderclap suddenly rang out as it released a massive halo of golden lightning that forced the golden palm projection open.

At the same time, the other 71 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords also began to flash with golden lightning as they struggled free from their restraints in unison before flying toward the remaining flying sword.

Bursts of rumbling thunderclaps rang out as the 71 flying sword tore the golden palm projection apart with formidable golden lightning to reunite with the trapped flying sword.

"What are you doing, you idiots? Restrain the other swords!" Xiong Shan roared in a furious voice.

He thought that this was yet another wave of instinctive resistance that the flying swords were putting up, and he began to reprimand Zhu Feng and the others for their incompetence. Unbeknownst to him, it wasn't that Zhu Feng was unwilling to restrain the flying swords. Instead, he was physically unable to.

Right as Xiong Shan's voice trailed off, dazzling arcs of golden lightning erupted out of the 71 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in unison, and they transformed into 72 streaks of golden light that shot forth through the air, escaping Zhu Feng's control before flying toward the eastern region of the sword tomb.

Zhu Feng was greatly alarmed to see this, and he hurriedly tried to make amends, but the flying swords were extremely fast, reaching the eastern part of the grassland before he or Xiong Shan had a chance to react.

After reaching their destination, the 72 flying swords suddenly dispersed in different directions rather than breaking out of the array, and they flew through the air in a series of profound trajectories, forming a small sword array within the Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array.

The newly formed sword array began to radiate dazzling light that illuminating the sword array up above, converting all of the golden lines of the sword array in the sky into sword qi that surged toward the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Almost in the exact same instant, all of the sword qi in the entire sword tomb was stirred up into a frenzy, and the entire Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array also underwent an astonishing change.

It was as if the entire array had suddenly undergone a reversal in this instant.

Xiong Shan immediately flew onto the scene, and he was just about to intervene when he suddenly threw up a mouthful of blood and began to plummet out of the sky. His aura was closely tied to the sword array, so he had suffered backlash from the array's reversal.

By the time he steadied himself, it was already too late.

The other elders were also quite alarmed by this turn of events, and everyone was at a loss for what to do. As for the Grand Ascension and Body Integration Stage disciples, they couldn't have done anything even if they wanted to.

Meanwhile, Mo Xie was observing the unfolding situation from outside the array, and he did notice some abnormalities in advance, but he had only brushed it off as natural changes to be expected within the sword array and didn't plan on doing anything.

Hence, the only person who knew what to expect was Han Li.

Earlier, he had forcibly withstood the resistance from the sword array to inspect the array's internal condition, and he had noticed that the circulation and distribution of sword qi within the array had changed.

He noticed that after Xiong Shan had converted most of the flying swords into sword essence, the concentration of sword qi in the areas that those flying swords were situated in had increased significantly, resultign in some degree of imbalance.

Hence, he had rapidly enhanced this imbalanced state using the sword array created by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, resulting in a complete reversal of the Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array.

The process sounded simple enough, but it was actually extremely difficult to execute.

Firstly, it required an extremely high level of sensitivity toward changes in the existing sword array, thereby allowing one to sense minute changes in sword qi.

Secondly, precise timing was required to reverse the array. Otherwise, the reversal attempt would most likely end in failure.

Finally, the small sword array used to exacerbate the imbalance in sword qi came from the existing sword array, so the two were closely connected and could resonate with one another.

Not even the slightest mistake could be made in this entire process, and only then could the sword array be reversed. Otherwise, the sword array would merely be destroyed instead.

The hundreds of streaks of sword essence that were hanging in the air suddenly seemed to have been summoned by something, and they began to fly through the sky along a series of strange trajectories.

Looking on from afar, a thought suddenly occurred to Mo Xie, and he looked up at the sword array in the sky to find that the trajectories followed by the streaks of sword essence perfectly matched the lines of the array.

At this point, a giant funnel-shaped purple vortex had already taken shape at the sword array formed by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and sword qi was surging incessantly within the vortex alongside flashes of golden lightning.

Hundreds of streaks of pure sword essence were converging toward the azure vortex, accompanied by countless streaks of peerlessly sharp swordlight, presenting a marvelous visual spectacle to behold.

Chapter 212: Escape

This type of pure sword essence that was devoid of the marks of the former owners was like the best type of supplement that existed for flying swords, being both extremely nutritious and very easy to digest.

In the blink of an eye, the majority of the sword essence had been absorbed by the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

All of the flying swords began to vibrate violently while screeching in unison, as if they were crying out in elation.

At this point, the sword array that had been completely reversed by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had also completely spiraled out of control, and the remaining flying swords that were yet to have their marks erased seemed to have been encouraged as they began struggling frantically once again.

Xiong Shan was barely able to contain his fury upon seeing this, and he roared in an enraged voice, "Restrain those flying swords, you fools! What are you all waiting for?"

Aside from the elders that were still overseeing the remaining areas, all of the other elders immediately unleashed their abilities in unison, trying to stop the wave of swords that was surging incessantly toward the vortex.

However, these arrays had only been designed to counteract resistance from a small number of flying swords at a time, yet at this point, virtually all of the flying swords on the grassland had gone on a collective rampage, and it was impossible to stop them all.

"Please assist me, Fellow Daoist Mo Xie. I'll be sure to reward you handsomely after the event!" Xiong Shan yelled, then gritted his teeth as he made a hand seal before raising his palms to the heavens.

A loud clang rang out as the golden longsword that was plunged into the altar rose up from the ground while radiating bright golden light, then immediately sped toward him.

As soon as the sword left the sword offering platform, the entire array ceased to function any longer, and the sword array in the sky also vanished as a result.

After a brief moment of hesitation, Mo Xie reached out with both hands, and a string of buzzing rang out as around a dozen black longswords flew out of his sleeves.

All of the swords had black lightning flashing around them, and they began to fly into the wave of swords.

At this point, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were already lapping up the final bits of sword essence in the air.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as a massive golden pillar of lightning that was over 100 feet thick and in excess of 10,000 feet in height rose up from the azure vortex, piercing straight into the heavens like the spear of a lightning god.

A burst of earth-shattering rumbling rang out up above, and the layers of restrictions encompassing the entire grassland were torn apart one after another to produce an enormous hole in the sky.

Meanwhile, the lightning spear only appeared for an instant before disintegrating into countless specks of golden light.

Lightning continued to flash over the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords as countless arcs of golden lightning connected together, intertwining to form a massive azure sword that was over 100 feet in length.

As soon as the giant sword took shape, it immediately aimed its own tip as the enormous hole in the sky, and azure light flashed over its blade as it prepared to fly toward the hole while a burst of spatial ripples proliferated outward around it.

Right at this moment, an extremely sharp screeching sound suddenly rang out, striking sharp pain into everyone's eardrums, and some of the Body Integration Stage disciples instantly fell unconscious on the spot with blood seeping out of their ears.

"Come back!" Xiong Shan roared, and in the next instant, a massive golden sword projection abruptly appeared out of thin air before slashing down upon the giant azure sword.

A resounding clang rang out as the sword projection clashed against the azure sword, sending powerful shockwaves erupting in all directions.

A golden halo surged through the air from the point where the two swords clashed, spreading in all directions.

Everyone felt a burst of shockwaves sweep through the air overhead, and as they looked up, they were greeted by the sight of a clear chasm in the sky. It wasn't that the space itself had been torn apart. Instead, the shreds of clouds and sword qi in the sky, and even the dust particles in the air, had been sliced apart by the golden halo.

Immediately following Xiong Shan's bonded flying swords were the dozen or so black lightning longswords unleashed by Mo Xie. Unfortunately, they were struck by the expanding golden halo along the way, and all of them were sent flying back with tremendous force.

As the owner of the swords, Mo Xie was naturally dealt a heavy blow as well, and he hurriedly made a beckoning motion to withdraw the flying swords, following he took no further action and began to watch from the sidelines.

Right at this moment, an extremely clear crack rang out in everyone's ears.

The golden sword projection was abruptly split down the middle before shattering into countless pieces, and two halves of a golden flying sword came falling out of the sky, having been completely robbed of its former luster.

At the same time, the giant azure sword plunged straight through the hole in the sky before flying away, vanishing in the blink of an eye.

Xiong Shan threw up a large mouthful of blood as he caught the two halves of his bonded flying swords, and he was livid with fury.

All of the elders and disciples immediately converged around him, but no one dared to say anything, and even Mo Xie remained silent with his brows slightly furrowed.

Han Li was standing slightly back from the crowd, stabilizing his own churning aura in secret. That golden sword projection just now had been an extremely mighty attack, and although most of its force had been nullified by the enormous amount of sword essence absorbed by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, Han Li was still inevitably somewhat impacted by the attack.

"The swords have gone in the northeastern direction! Hurry up and get them back!" Xiong Shan spat through gritted teeth with a furious look on his face.

Having sustained such severe damage to his bonded flying sword, he had to go into seclusion to address his own injuries as soon as possible. Otherwise, there was a very good chance that he would suffer a severe decline in his cultivation base.

Everyone immediately set off to give chase upon hearing this, only for Xiong Shan to stop them. "Hold on, they're in the northwest now... Wait, no, the southwest..."

"What's going on, Fellow Daoist Xiong?" Mo Xie asked, and the other elders were also looking on with perplexed expressions.

"I've lost track of the swords. My final connection with them has been completely severed," Xiong Shan said in a cold voice.

He then turned to look at the severely ravaged sword tomb, as well as the remaining flying swords on the grassland, of which there were fewer than 300, and his eyes were burning with fury.

He raised an arm, and his sleeve was billowing audibly despite the lack of wind as he swung his arm down in a forceful motion.

All of the remaining flying swords were instantly struck by a burst of tremendous force that sent them plunging straight into the ground.

A string of loud thumps rang out as all of the flying swords landed on the ground, plunging so deep into the earth that only their hilts were visible above the surface.

Everyone could clearly sense Xiong Shan's fury, and no one dared to do or say anything without further instructions.

Zhu Feng was the one that had been assigned to oversee the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords,and his face had turned deathly pale, while his body was trembling uncontrollably from fear.

He was nothing more than an inner sect elder, so if Xiong Shan were to turn on him in a fit of rage, then his death would've been sealed. Even if the sect were going to punish Xiong Shan after the event, that would hardly matter to Zhu Feng when he was already dead.

Xiong Shan slowly swept his gaze over everyone's faces, and despite his fury, he still hadn't lost his rationality.

He knew that there was no way that such a reversal would've taken place in the Thousand Edge Spirit Gathering Sword Array for no reason. Someone had to have tampered with it, and there was a very good chance that the culprit was one of the 10 elders standing before him.

As the one overseeing the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, Zhu Feng was the most suspicious one, but he wasn't the one that Xiong Shan viewed as the primary suspect.

Instead, in his eyes, the most suspicious one was Mo Xie, who had requested to be present.

Such a complex sword array was impossible to completely control, even for Xiong Shan himself, and if anyone present had the ability to reverse the array, then it could've only been Mo Xie, whose cultivation base was extremely close to his own.

Mo Xie seemed to have noticed the hint of suspicion in Xiong Shan's eyes, and he immediately protested, "You're not suspecting me, are you, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong? I didn't do a single thing aside from when you asked for my help at the end, and I didn't even release my aura at all. If I had tampered with the array, how is it possible that I managed to do so while completely bypassing your detection?"

"There's no need to get so worked up, Fellow Daoist Mo. I haven't said anything," Xiong Shan harrumphed coldly.

Despite his suspicions, he had no proof, so he couldn't pursue the matter. He wasn't a rash person. Otherwise, he wouldn't have been able to reach his current position.

"It looks like you still have many things to take care of today, so I won't keep you any longer. I'll come back some other time to take back what you borrowed from me. Farewell!" Mo Xie said.

Xiong Shan offered no response as he raised a hand to cast a few incantation seals in a certain direction, and the space there rippled as a ball of white light that was several dozen feet in size appeared.

Mo Xie cupped his fist in a parting salute toward Xiong Shan, then flew into the ball of white light in a flash.

Xiong Shan watched as Mo Xie departed from the sword tomb, then withdrew his gaze and began to inspect the faces of the 10 elders standing before him with a frosty look on his face.

It was as if the atmosphere had completely congealed, and no one dared to utter even a single sound.

Just like everyone else, Han Li's head was slightly lowered to avoid Xiong Shan's gaze.

After a long silence, Xiong Shan's gaze ultimately settled on Zhu Feng. "Do you not have anything to say, Elder Zhu Feng?"

Zhu Feng's heart jolted violently upon hearing this, and he began stuttering in a fearful manner. "No... I... But..."

Xiong Shan scoured the entire sword tomb with his spiritual sense in secret once again, but was still unable to find any clues, and he continued, "I already warned all of you earlier. Anyone who drops the ball will not be granted mercy! You were the one who made this grave error, so I can't just let you get away with this without some form of compensation."

"H, how do you want me to compensate you, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong?" Zhu Feng asked as cold sweat poured profusely down his face.

"Given the massive losses I've incurred, you wouldn't be able to cover everything even if you sold everything in your possession. I'm not a cruel and heartless person, so I'll only ask for 6,000 merit points and 300 Immortal Origin Stones as compensation," Xiong Shan declared in a cold and implacable voice.

Zhu Feng almost slumped down onto the ground upon hearing this.

This was more than everything that he currently owned, and forcing him to fork out such enormous compensation hurt worse than killing him.

However, he had no choice but to accept this outcome.

Everyone else present was grimacing internally, denouncing Xiong Shan for his cruel demands while also celebrating the fact that they weren't in Zhu Feng's shoes.

Chapter 213: Finally Back

"D, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong, I've managed to gather 6,000 merit points during my many years in the sect, but I don't have 300 Immortal Origin Stones in my possession... Would I be able to use top-grade spirit stones instead?" Zhu Feng asked in a careful manner.

"I can give you some time. Gather everything for me in 10 years, and I'll let this matter slide," Xiong Shan said in a cold voice.

"But... Alright," Zhu Feng replied with a sullen expression.

Even after extorting Zhu Feng, Xiong Shan's mood didn't improve much, and he declared, "Do not speak a single word of this to anyone after you leave this place. Otherwise, you'll have to answer directly to me. Piss off now!"

Everyone hurriedly vowed not to speak of this matter to anyone, then sheepishly departed, not daring to say anything despite not receiving any merit points for their efforts.

After emerging from the Heavenly Sword Tomb, Han Li and Qi Liang traveled alongside one another in silence. Upon reaching the teleportation hall, the two of them exchanged farewells with wry smiles before returning to their respective mountains.

After returning to his cave abode on the Crimson Dawn Peak, Han Li immediately examined his own body to ensure that no mark had been planted in him by Xiong Shan, following which he entered his secret chamber to recuperate.

Several days later.

In the northeastern region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, there was a thin elderly man in a white robe with his hair arranged into a Daoist bun. He was standing on a bare rock on the summit of a lone mountain near the edge of the mountain range, looking out toward the sky in the southwest.

There was nothing in the pristine sky in that direction, but the elderly man's eyes were glowing with excitement, while his face was also alight with anticipation.

Moments later, a hint of azure light suddenly appeared in the distant sky.

Over the course of several seconds, the hint of azure light gradually expanded, revealing itself to be a massive azure sword.

"There they are!"

The elderly man's eyes lit up as a faint smile appeared on his face.

In the next instant, the elderly man released his aura without any further concealment, revealing his early-True Immortal Stage cultivation base in its full glory.

He was originally an itinerant cultivator residing on an island outside of the Ancient Cloud Continent, and he had only recently arrived near the Bell Toll Mountain Range. His plan was to rest for a few days on this lone mountain, but while meditating, he detected a peculiar flying sword with an aura comparable to that of an immortal treasure flying rapidly toward him.

As a proficient sword cultivator himself, the elderly man could sense that the flying sword seemed to have no owner, and he was immediately driven by his greed to try and intercept the sword.

As the flying sword continued to approach, the elderly man rose up into the air as a streak of dazzling white light, hurtling directly toward the sword.

Even though the giant sword formed by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords wasn't being controlled by Han Li, it still put up instinctive resistance as lightning began to crackle over its surface.

The elderly man paid no heed to this as he reached out toward the hilt of the giant sword with both hands enveloped in spiritual light.

All of a sudden, a burst of piercing golden light erupted from the giant azure sword alongside a thunderous boom, and countless serpentine arcs of golden lightning sprang forth in a frenzy, encompassing the entire area in a radius of several hundred feet. An airtight ball of golden lightning instantly took shape, and a blood-curdling howl rang out from within.

Immediately thereafter, the ball of golden lightning vanished, and a charred black corpse that was releasing a plume of white smoke fell out of the sky.

Even before it had a chance to land on the ground, it was blown into black dust by the wind and scattered in all directions.

As for the giant azure sword, it split up again into 72 flying swords amid a flash of light before descending into a valley down below, seemingly having overexerted itself.

……

Two months later, an azure-robed young man appeared above an extremely secluded snow-covered valley on the northeastern outskirts of the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

The man slowly descended into the valley, and it was none other than Han Li, who had tracked the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords all the way here thanks to his spiritual connection with them.

He was concerned about Xiong Shan conducting surveillance on him, so he had spent the entire first month after returning to his cave abode cultivating in his secret chamber.

Sure enough, Xiong Shan didn't gloss over any potential suspects, and he had even sent people to Han Li's territory in secret, presumably to conduct surveillance on him.

It was most likely the case that all of the other elders, including Mo Xie, had received the same treatment, and all of them had no choice but to turn a blind eye to this in order to avoid arousing further suspicions.

Only after verifying that he was no longer under Xiong Shan's scrutiny did Han Li leave the Crimson Dawn Peak in secret before arriving here.

Following his descent into the valley, he immediately flew over to a green pond at the end of the valley before drawing to a halt.

He swept his gaze over the pond to find that its surface appeared to have been quite tranquil, but in reality, there were countless tiny streaks of sword qi surging within it. As a result, any rocks, leaves, or pieces of wood that fell into the pond were instantly shredded into countless pieces.

Han Li knew that the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were in this pond, and he immediately summoned them to come out.

A string of splashes rang out as the originally tranquil surface of the pond instantly began to churn like boiling water, following which the 72 flying swords flew out one after another, then circled around in the air momentarily before flying toward Han Li.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

The flying swords were all glowing with azure light as they danced joyfully around him like elated children while ringing incessantly.

"You're all finally back!"

Han Li exhaled as he raised a hand to stroke the flying swords one by one, as if they were the shoulders of old friends, and countless emotions welled up in his heart as he felt their familiar yet also slightly unfamiliar auras.

Due to the fact that the flying swords had absorbed the pure sword essence of several hundred powerful flying swords, their auras had naturally been significantly elevated. However, as a safety precaution, Han Li unleashed a secret technique to conceal their auras rather than testing out their powers right away.

After making sure that no one else would be able to detect the flying swords, he carefully stowed them into his own body one by one.

Back in the Mortal Realm, he only had two flying swords taken from him by an elder devil, and he was already ecstatic upon recovering them, so he was naturally even more elated to have recovered a whole set of 72 lost flying swords.

As for the significant increase in power experienced by the flying swords, that was just an added bonus.

……

Shortly thereafter, Han Li returned to the Crimson Dawn Peak without alerting anyone, and as soon as he returned, he immediately instructed Meng Yungui to gather everyone.

Inside a certain hall in the courtyard, the 10 servants bowed in unison as they greeted, "We pay our respects to Elder Li."

"Over these past years, all of you have kept my cave abode in good order and haven't fallen behind in your cultivation, either, and that's quite commendable. Yungui, take these pills and split them with everyone," Han Li said with his hands clasped behind his back.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a sleeve through the air, and a burst of azure light flew into Meng Yungui's grasp in a flash, containing a small storage bracelet.

Meng Yungui and the others were ecstatic to see this, and they immediately extended another collective bow of gratitude. "Thank you, Elder Li!"

Han Li didn't often appear before them, but whenever he did, he would always bestow upon them some pills that were extremely beneficial for the cultivation of Core Formation cultivators, for which they were extremely grateful.

In particular, Meng Yungui had successfully manifested a nascent soul during this time and became a Nascent Soul cultivator.

"From this day forth, I'm going into seclusion, and the Crimson Dawn Peak will be shut off for some time. I'm going to be activating all of the restrictions, and I won't be seeing any guests," Han Li instructed.

Meng Yungui and the others hurriedly gave affirmative responses upon hearing this.

"Sun Buzheng, you'll be responsible for overseeing matters in the cave abode during my seclusion," Han Li said.

"Rest assured, Elder Li, I'll be sure to perform my duties diligently," Sun Buzheng immediately said.

"Yungui, you possess the highest cultivation base out of everyone, so I'm going to give you a mission. Go out and search for rare and exotic spirit plants and seeds or seedlings for me. The more types you find, the better, and don't worry about the costs too much," Han Li instructed.

Meng Yungui faltered slightly upon hearing this, then immediately accepted the order.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a storage treasure that he handed to Meng Yungui as he continued, "There are some spirit stones in here, as well as two treasures for your protection. If you do a good job, you can keep those two treasures as a reward."

Meng Yungui injected his spiritual sense into the storage treasure, and an elated look immediately appeared in his eyes as he said, "Thank you, Elder Li! I'll be sure to do my best!"

Envious looks appeared in everyone's eyes upon seeing this.

The treasures inside the storage treasure had to have been quite powerful. Otherwise, they wouldn't have gotten such an excited reaction out of Meng Yungui.

In particular, Sun Buzheng was feeling both envious and regretful.

His cultivation base had originally been slightly higher than Meng Yungui's, but during these past years, Meng Yungui had made a series of consecutive breakthroughs, reaching the Nascent Soul Stage before him.

If he had known that this would happen, he would've worked even harder in his cultivation, and perhaps he would've been the one to receive such a reward then.

Meng Qianqian was staring directly at Han Li with an unblinking gaze, and there was a hint of anticipation glowing in her eyes. She had changed into a pristine white dress, giving her a pure and gorgeous appearance.

"Alright, you can all go now," Han Li said to everyone with a smile before turning and making his way back into his cave abode.

Everyone immediately extended a collective bow once again. "Farewell, Elder Li."

However, Meng Qianqian didn't bow with everyone else, and her face was gradually growing paler and paler.

A faint thump rang out as the gate of the cave abode swung shut.

After speaking to Meng Yungui for a moment, Sun Buzheng picked out a few people to accompany him, and before long, they were busy at work.

Meanwhile, Meng Qianqian was staring at the shut stone gate while biting down on her own lower lip with a sense of melancholy in her heart.

Meng Yungui could tell that she was feeling very dejected, and he approached her before asking, "What's wrong, Qianqian?"

"Nothing," Meng Qianqian replied as she lowered her head, and a film of tears had already appeared over her eyes.

That entire time, Han Li hadn't even taken a single glance at her.

Meng Yungui was aware of his sister's thoughts, and he sighed, "Elder Li is not from the same world as us. You should be well aware of this..."

Meng Qianqian shuddered slightly upon hearing this, but she then raised her head with a determined look in her eyes.

Meng Yungui could only shake his head and heave a faint sigh upon seeing this.

On the outside, Meng Qianqian had a very delicate appearance, but she was actually very stubborn and unyielding on the inside, and he was powerless to dissuade her once she had her mind set on something.

In any case, perhaps this wasn't necessarily a bad thing.

Meng Yungui set these thoughts aside with a faint smile and began to ponder how he was going to complete the task assigned to him by Han Li.

Chapter 214: Six Time Dao Runes

A short while later, one restriction after another was activated on the Crimson Dawn Peak, producing a series of light barriers of different colors over the entire mountain.

After doing all of that, Han Li made his way into the secret chamber of his cave abode before taking a seat with his legs crossed.

At this moment, the 72 recovered Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were enveloped by pure immortal spiritual power inside his body, and were being slowly refined by his nascent flame.

They had been separated from him for many years, and even though their power had significantly increased from absorbing so much sword essence in the Heavenly Sword Tomb, their spiritual nature had become quite chaotic, so it would've been unwise to use them right away. Hence, he had to carefully refine them first.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to produce his Heaven Controlling Vial before inspecting it closely right in front of his eyes.

At this point, it had been confirmed to him beyond a reasonable doubt that the Heaven Controlling Vial contained the laws of time.

Back in the Spirit Realm, he had obtained a replica vial from Ma Liang, and by combining the two, he was able to activate the Heaven Controlling Vial to a slight degree to unleash attacks. However, something had to have changed during the 300 years that were missing from his memory, and he found that he was no longer able to use the vial in such a manner.

After a brief pause, Han Li summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis behind him amid a flash of golden light.

With a wave of his hand, the Mantra Treasured Axis flew to his side before beginning to rapidly revolve on the spot.

Golden ripples spread through the air to completely encompass the Heaven Controlling Vial, and there were barely detectable hints of time law powers surging into the vial.

Meanwhile, Han Li continued to scrutinize the Heaven Controlling Vial intently, but the vial displayed no reaction whatsoever.

After some contemplation, Han Li switched to a different hand seal, and the Mantra Treasured Axis began to glow far brighter than before, but it also shrank down into a small golden ball in the blink of an eye before flying into the vial at his behest.

A layer of translucent light flashed over the surface of the Heaven Controlling Vial, and several faint runes appeared on its surface, only to immediately vanish without a trace in the next instant.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he heaved a faint sigh.

Seeing as the Mantra Axis Scripture was a cultivation art that concerned the laws of time and he had already manifested a Mantra Treasured Axis, he had thought that perhaps he would be able to use it to control the vial to some degree or trigger some type of change in the vial.

However, it appeared that this was not the case, or perhaps this was because he simply hadn't yet reached a sufficiently advanced level in the cultivation art.

Han Li shook his head as he abandoned this endeavor, then summoned that giant ape puppet before instructing it to continue to harvest green liquid and water his spirit plants with the liquid while he was in seclusion.

As for the crystals required for his Earthly Deity Avatar's cultivation, he would create those during the breaks in his seclusion to ensure that his avatar could continue to refine heavy water at an enhanced rate.

Another thought then suddenly occurred to him, and he made his way into another stone chamber before setting up a small spirit gathering array. After that, he placed the giant egg that he had obtained from Fang Pan at the center of the array, hoping that the slow and steady nourishment of spiritual qi would be enough to hatch the egg.

After making all of these arrangements, Han Li returned to his secret chamber to meditate once again.

This meditation lasted three days and three nights, and once he had completely settled his mental state and primed himself into the best condition, faint golden light began to radiate from his skin, instantly illuminating the entire secret chamber.

Over three years passed by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, countless dark clouds suddenly appeared in the sky above the Crimson Dawn Peak, and the world's origin qi was churning violently as it converged toward the cave abode.

Inside the cave abode, Han Li's entire body was radiating dazzling golden light, and three incredibly bright specks of golden light had appeared on his lower abdomen, greedily devouring the abundant world's origin qi in the surrounding area.

He had opened up yet another immortal acupoint, and there were currently six Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him.

Powerful time law fluctuations were emanating from the Mantra Treasured Axis, and these fluctuations were far more potent than the ones released by the axis back when it only had four Time Dao Runes.

Han Li's eyes sprang open as an elated look appeared on his face.

He was naturally quite glad that he had opened up another immortal acupoint, but what he was even more ecstatic about was that he had finally manifested six Time Dao Runes.

This was a stage that cultivators of the Mantra Axis Scripture normally only reached after opening 12 immortal acupoints!

According to the cultivation art's description, the Mantra Treasured Axis would receive a significant increase in power with each set of six Time Dao Runes that it manifested, and Han Li couldn't wait to test out the power of this ability.

The Mantra Treasured Axis began to rapidly revolve at his behest, and countless golden ripples spread through the air in all directions, but were only able to reach about 100 feet away from him.

It seems like as long as I'm still on the first level of the cultivation art, no matter how many Time Dao Runes I attain, the effective range of the Mantra Treasured Axis will only be 100 feet. Perhaps the range will only increase once I reach the second level, Han Li thought to himself.

Inside the area encompassed within the golden ripples, everything had slowed down significantly, including the flow of air and the world's origin qi.

A layer of blue light appeared in Han Li's eyes, allowing him to see this slowing effect even more clearly.

The colorful world's origin qi was clashing against itself like waves before dispersing in different directions.

Everything was clearly visible, and it was quite a mystifying experience.

Even though everything around him had slowed down, he remained completely unaffected himself, so in a way, it was as if his speed had increased by twofold.

In the next instant, he appeared several dozen feet away in a flash, and the changes in the surrounding air and the world's origin qi around him triggered by his movement were all clearly visible to him.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to produce a small ball of heavy water.

With a flick of his finger, the heavy water instantly exploded into countless drops that erupted in all directions.

The speed at which these drops of heavy water was traveling had also been halved, making every single one of them clearly visible to Han Li.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li was able to easily intercept all of the drops of heavy water before recombining them into a ball and stowing it away again.

Even though the effects of the Mantra Treasured Axis were very clearly laid out in the Mantra Axis Scripture, he would still have to do a lot more experimentation before he could completely master this ability.

In the next instant, Han Li raised a hand, and countless arcs of silver lightning appeared over the center of his palm.

These arcs of lightning were also completely unaffected by the Mantra Treasured Axis.

He spread his fingers open, and several arcs of silver lightning sprang forth, crashing into a wall of the secret chamber.

A layer of translucent white light instantly appeared on the wall before flashing sluggishly a few times, and the arcs of silver lightning extended in all directions over the wall before vanishing.

The sluggishness of the white light and the rapid movement of the silver lightning presented a stark contrast.

Han Li nodded to himself even upon seeing this. Even after the silver lightning had left his hand, it still remained completely unaffected.

If the Mantra Treasured Axis were to slow down his own attacks as well, then it would've been an entirely pointless ability.

He then experimented with his spiritual sense and attacks from his treasures, only ceasing the experiments once he confirmed that none of those things were adversely affected, either.

Han Li then summoned the giant ape puppet into the secret chamber, and as a result of the Mantra Treasured Axis's influence, the sound of the puppet's footsteps was elongated by twofold, producing a very strange sound.

Before long, the giant puppet had drawn to a halt outside the area encompassed within the golden ripples.

"Attack me," Han Li instructed.

The giant ape puppet immediately opened its mouth to blast forth a thick pillar of blue lightning. At the same time, it raised a hand to send five arcs of blue lightning hurtling toward Han Li from its fingertips.

The attacks were quite weak, but the speed of lightning was still nothing to be scoffed at.

However, as soon as the lightning came into contact with the golden ripples, its speed was instantly halved.

This didn't sound like much, but in reality, it was an enormous difference.

Han Li sidestepped the attacks without using any movement techniques, and the arcs of lightning flew right past him without even brushing his clothes.

Han Li was very excited to see this, and he instructed the giant ape puppet to unleash some other types of attacks, all of which also had their speed halved.

After this string of experiments, he had ascertained most of the properties of the Mantra Treasured Axis. He had also thought of multiple ways to use the Mantra Treasured Axis, and the more he thought about it, the more excited he became.

If he could use this ability appropriately, then he would stand a chance at defeating even late-True Immortal cultivators.

However, he then suddenly noticed something a little disheartening. He hadn't been using his Mantra Treasured Axis for very long at all, yet a large chunk of his immortal spiritual power had already disappeared. It seemed that this ability was extremely taxing to use.

However, given how incredible its effects were, it made sense that it would be so taxing on the user's immortal spiritual power.

The Mantra Treasured Axis vanished in a flash at Han Li's behest, and he sat down with his legs crossed, planning to continue to cultivate.

However, before that, he instructed the giant ape puppet to fetch him his Heaven Controlling Vial, and he attempted to activate it with his Mantra Treasured Axis once again, but the outcome was still the same as last time.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but he quickly emptied his mind before returning to his seclusion.

……

Over 20 years flew by in the blink of an eye.

The Crimson Dawn Peak remained as peaceful as ever, far removed from the lively and bustling scenes one would expect to see on some other peaks in the sect.

The red fire miasma near the mountain had already completely vanished, so the climate had returned to normal, and everywhere that wasn't encompassed under a restriction was covered in a thick layer of snow.

The boundless expanse of pristine snow presented a stunning sight to behold.

Unfortunately, there was no one on the Crimson Dawn Peak to appreciate this beautiful scenery. Everyone was busy at work, either looking after the cave abode or cultivating themselves.

On a plot of empty land at the back of the Crimson Dawn Peak, there was a crimson array that was over 100 feet in size engraved onto the ground. Numerous crimson crystals were embedded into the array, and the crystals were flashing with a fiery glow.

At the center of the array sat Meng Qianqian in a white dress.

Streaks of crimson light were rising up from the crystals before converging around her, making it appear as if she were seated within a crimson flame.

A faint sheen of sweat could be seen on her forehead, and her cheeks were a little red. She seemed to have been cultivating some type of secret technique.

Over the past two decades, her appearance hadn't changed much, but her cultivation base had already reached the late-Core Formation Stage, displaying a rate of progress that was quite extraordinary among the outer sect disciples of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Of course, the pills bestowed upon her by Han Li and the spirit stones left to her by Meng Yungui prior to his departure played extremely important roles in this, but her resolve in her pursuit of the Great Dao was also an integral factor.

Without these mental qualities, there was no way that she wouldn't have been able to bear the loneliness and mind-numbing monotony of cultivation.

Chapter 215: Monkeys Worshiping an Immortal

Right as Meng Qianqian was cultivating, a resounding boom suddenly rang out in the distance over the entire Crimson Dawn Peak.

A thick blanket of dark clouds instantly appeared in the sky above Han Li's cave abode, and the world's origin qi converged in a frenzy, forming a spiritual qi vortex that was visible even to the naked eye.

Meng Qianqian's eyes sprang open as she turned her gaze toward Han Li's cave abode with an elated look on her face.

During the past 30 or so years, phenomena like this would appear every once in a while. At her current cultivation base, she still didn't know exactly what this entailed, but everyone speculated in private that this was a sign that Han Li was making some type of breakthrough in his cultivation.

Everyone was already accustomed to this.

Of course, this type of speculation was something that Meng Yungui expressly forbade, and he also warned everyone not to speak a single word of what they had seen here to anyone.

The interior of the secret chamber was illuminated by dazzling golden radiance, and there were seven specks of golden light shining on Han Li's lower abdomen.

They resembled seven giant mouths that were guzzling down the tremendous amount of world's origin qi nearby before gradually converting it into pure immortal spiritual power.

This rate of world's origin qi absorption was countless times faster than before, and 14 Time Dao Runes had appeared on the Mantra Treasured Axis that was slowly revolving behind Han Li.

A long while later, Han Li slowly opened his eyes, and a hint of elation appeared on his face.

Over the past two decades of arduous cultivation, he had made rapid progress, opening four immortal acupoints in rapid succession.

Over the course of just a few decades, he had opened seven immortal acupoints, and this rate of progress would've shocked even the Golden Immortal Stage dao lords.

He rose to his feet as bright golden light radiated from his body, and the 14 Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him immediately began to release powerful time law fluctuations.

Sensing the immense law powers imbued within the Mantra Treasured Axis, Han Li was once again struck by the urge to test out its power, and he immediately flew out of his secret chamber as a streak of azure light.

As the phenomenon in the sky faded, Meng Qianqian took a deep breath, then closed her eyes as she continued in her cultivation.

Streaks of fiery light surged into her body, and her face took on a bright red complexion again while her brows furrowed slightly in pain.

Right at this moment, Han Li appeared beside her array without any warning, then released a burst of light out of his fingertip, which surged straight into Meng Qianqian's glabella.

Meng Qianqian shuddered as the redness of her face quickly faded, and she opened her eyes.

Upon spotting Han Li, she hurriedly rose to her feet before extending a curtsey. "Elder Li."

"Working hard in your cultivation is a good thing, but you can't be too ambitious. Otherwise, you'll put too much strain on your body. Too much of a good thing becomes a bad thing, understood?"

Not long after he left his cave abode, he noticed that Meng Qianqian was on the verge of qi deviation, so he decided to give her a hand.

A faint blush appeared on Meng Qianqian's face, and she forcibly composed herself as she replied, "Yes. Thank you for your guidance, Elder Li."

"Barring any mishaps, it looks like you'll also be able to manifest a nascent soul in a few years. When that time comes, I'll have other missions to assign to you," Han Li remarked before vanishing on the spot once again.

Meng Qianqian hurriedly raised her head to say something, but Han Li was already nowhere to be seen, leaving her looking around in a daze.

In a certain valley within the territory of the Crimson Dawn Peak, a streak of azure light descended out of the sky before fading to reveal Han Li.

The valley was surrounded by a ring of mountains that kept out the cold wind, so it was quite warm inside. There wasn't any snow in the valley, and instead, it was filled with grass that was interspersed with vibrant flowers.

A waterfall that resembled a white jade belt was crashing down rock that was jutting out of the stone face, sending countless water droplets splashing in all directions and making the area also rather humid.

There were several fruit trees that were laden with yellow peaches growing near the waterfall, and some monkeys chattering incessantly as they swung from tree to tree. There were dozens of these monkeys here, and they weren't afraid of Han Li at all.

Han Li paid no heed to these monkeys as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis amid a flash of golden light, and a layer of golden ripples spread through the air, encompassing an area with a radius of 100 feet around him, within which was half of the waterfall.

Everyone encompassed within the golden ripples instantly became significantly slower, having been reduced to a third of their original speed now that the Mantra Treasured Axis had over 12 Time Dao Runes.

One half of the waterfall continued to tumble down as normal, while the other half had been slowed down significantly, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

The nearby monkeys immediately erupted into a panic upon seeing this, and some of them were screeching in horror, while some others appeared to have been quite excited, dancing around as they yelled in excitement.

Right at this moment, a crimson monkey that was close to twice the size of the other monkeys let loose a long howl, then waved an arm through the air and began springing away.

This seemed to have been the monkey king, and all of the other monkeys immediately followed it, fleeing away into the distance.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he made a beckoning motion with one hand, and one of the monkeys was immediately drawn to him.

A panicked look appeared on the monkey's face as it flew involuntarily toward Han Li while screeching urgently, as if it were asking its companions for help.

All of the other monkeys immediately stopped in their tracks and turned to the monkey king.

There was a bright gleam in the monkey king's eyes, indicating that it was an extremely intelligent creature, and it hesitated momentarily before slowly making its way toward Han Li.

All of the other monkeys also slowly followed along upon seeing this.

The monkey that was drawn to Han Li quickly entered the area encompassed within the golden ripples, and its flailing arms were instantly slowed to a third of their original speed, while its panicked screeches also became elongated, producing an extremely strange sound.

The monkey still had a panicked look on its face, but it was also looking quite shocked as well, clearly alarmed by the slowing of time around it.

Han Li gave a slight nod upon seeing this.

He hadn't captured the monkey for fun. Instead, he simply wanted to observe the Mantra Treasured Axis's effect on living beings.

The monkeys approached Han Li, led by their king, then fell to their knees and kowtowed to him before looking up at him with imploring expressions.

"You're quite an intelligent monkey, I see. Rest assured, I have no intention of harming your brethren," Han Li said as he gave the monkey king a slight nod, and with a sweep of his sleeve, the monkey was returned to the pack, drifting onto the ground completely unharmed.

At the same time, Han Li pointed a finger forward to release a burst of azure light, which split up into several dozen bursts, each of which surged into a monkey's body.

The azure light instantly transformed into a surge of warmth that flowed through the monkeys' bodies, providing a sense of indescribable comfort.

All of a sudden, a layer of crimson light appeared over the monkey king's body, and the light flashed a few times before fading.

A dazed look appeared in the monkey king's eyes, but it then immediately returned to its senses, and its eyes were looking even more intelligent than before as it led all of the monkeys to kowtow to Han Li once again.

It was quite a poetic scene, with the monkeys worshiping an immortal in front of a scenic waterfall.

Han Li paid no heed to the monkeys as he tested out the Mantra Treasured Axis's power for a while longer, and a pleased look appeared on his face.

If he were to face Fang Pan again in his current form, there was no way that he would've struggled anywhere near as much. In fact, he would've been able to easily defeat him.

Now that he had this Mantra Treasured Axis, he finally possessed a powerful self-preservation tool in the Immortal Realm.

After pondering something for a while, he suddenly flew back toward the summit of the Crimson Dawn Peak as a streak of azure light.

The monkey king looked on at Han Li's departing figure with a dazed expression, while the other monkeys were looking around, at a slight loss for what to do.

……

Han Li quickly returned to his cave abode to continue his seclusion, and several more years passed by in the blink of an eye.

Inside the cave abode, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and golden light was surging over his entire body, while the seven immortal acupoints on his abdomen were flashing incessantly as they absorbed the world's origin qi that was constantly flowing into the room.

A long while later, he slowly opened his eyes, and the golden light radiating from his body faded as he furrowed his brows slightly.

Ever since he opened his seventh immortal acupoint, his rate of cultivation progression had declined quite sharply.

He wasn't actually progressing all that slowly. When compared with other True Immortals of the same cultivation base, he was still making far quicker progress, but having gotten used to the rapid progress that he was making before, this was a slightly disheartening turn of events.

Han Li rose to his feet as clasped his hands behind his back and began to pace back and forth in his cave abode, seemingly pondering something.

Moments later, he stopped in his tracks, seemingly having made some type of decision, and he made his way out of the cave abode.

Under normal circumstances, this rate of cultivation wouldn't have been an issue, but the problem was that he was still far from safe.

Fang Pan was dead, but the mysterious figure behind him still existed, and no one knew when he was going to appear.

He had recovered his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and refined them over the course of several years. Furthermore, his cultivation base had progressed significantly, and he now possessed the Mantra Treasured Axis, but he still didn't have much confidence in being able to take on that person.

This wasn't the time to be resting on his laurels. He still had to attain more power as quickly as possible.

The best way to enhance one's rate of cultivation was naturally through consuming pills.

Due to the rapid progression that he had been making thus far, he hadn't put much thought into acquiring pills. However, it was now time to go out and search for some pills that were suitable for him. During these decades of seclusion, he had matured a batch of 10,000-year-old ordinary spirit medicines, and it was also about time that he completed the three missions that he had to complete per 100 years in the sect.

A burst of dull rumbling rang out as the restrictions on the Crimson Dawn Peak slowly receded, producing a vibrant and colorful show of lights.

Sun Buzheng and the others immediately converged in front of the entrance of Han Li's cave abode upon seeing this.

The gate of the cave abode slowly opened, and Han Li emerged from inside.

"Welcome, Elder Li!" the group of nine servants greeted in unison.

"Has Meng Yungui still not returned?" Han Li asked.

Out of the nine servants, both Sun Buzheng and Meng Qianqian had already reached the Nascent Soul Stage, while most of the rest of them had also reached the late-Core Formation Stage.

Three of the 10 servants had successfully manifested nascent souls during the past few decades, and that was quite a remarkable rate of progress, even in the Blaze Dragon Dao. In particular, Meng Qianqian's cultivation aptitude seemed to have been slightly superior even to her brother's.

"Meng Yungui is still yet to return from the mission that you assigned to him, Elder Li," Sun Buzheng informed.

A hint of concern appeared on Meng Qianqian's face at the mention of her brother, and Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Meng Yungui's cultivation base wasn't very advanced, and Han Li could only hope that he hadn't encountered any mishaps.

With the two treasures that Han Li had bestowed upon him for protection and his status as Han Li's servant, he should've been fine as long as he didn't venture out of the Blaze Dragon Dao's territory.

"You've all worked quite hard looking after the cave abode for all these years. Take these pills as a reward."

With a wave of his hand, a pill vial descended in front of each of the nine servants.

"Thank you, Elder Li!"

Sun Buzheng and the others were ecstatic, and they immediately stowed the vials away before extending grateful bows.

Chapter 216: Bell Toll

"Today marks the end of my seclusion. The spirit fields in the territory of the Crimson Dawn Peak have been left uncultivated this entire time. Sun Buzheng, take some people with you to prepare these spirit fields for plantation," Han Li Instructed.

"Yes, Elder Li. May I ask what types of spirit plants you would like us to plant in those fields?" Sun Buzheng asked.

"Just focus on preparing the fields for now, I'll make further arrangements after that," Han Li replied.

Everyone immediately gave affirmative responses before turning to leave.

"Qianqian, come with me," Han Li suddenly instructed, then turned and made his way back toward his cave abode.

Meng Qianqian faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a hint of elation flashed through her eyes as she joyfully followed along behind Han Li, and before long, they had entered a stone chamber in Han Li's cave abode.

At the center of the stone chamber was a small spirit gathering array that was roughly 30 feet in size, filling the entire chamber with abundant spiritual qi, and at the center of the array laid a huge white egg.

As Meng Qianqian entered the stone chamber, she was initially quite excited and curious, but her gaze was then drawn to the giant white egg.

Following the past three decades of nourishment, the vitality contained within the egg was becoming more and more potent, but it still showed no signs of hatching at all.

Meng Qianqian opened her mouth, seemingly to ask something, but she then recalled what her brother had told her, and she hurriedly closed her mouth and stood off to the side in silence, awaiting further instructions from Han Li.

Han Li looked at the egg in silence for a moment, then said, "Qianqian, your mission from now on is to find a way to hatch this egg for me. You're using a fire-attribute cultivation art, and you've manifested a nascent soul, so perhaps you'll be able to assist the egg in its hatching process. During this time, you can freely enter this cave abode and this stone chamber, but make sure you don't mention this to anyone, not even your brother, understood?"

He flipped a hand over to produce a jade badge and a storage bracelet as he spoke, then handed them both to Meng Qianqian.

"Yes, Elder Li! I'll be sure to keep this a secret and do my best to complete this mission!" Meng Qianqian hurriedly replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then departed from the cave abode and made his way down the mountain.

Shortly thereafter, he appeared in the underground cavern where the fire vein was situated.

Compared with several decades ago, the fire-attribute spiritual power in the air was a lot more stable, but it was still extremely hot, as if the very space itself were on fire.

Above the churning lake of lava was a massive fiery red cocoon, which was expanding and shrinking in a rhythmic fashion as it continued to devour the surrounding fire-attribute spiritual power.

Han Li released his spiritual sense to check on the Essence Fire Raven within the cocoon, and an elated look immediately appeared on his face.

Having absorbed so much of the pure fire-attribute spiritual power released by the fire vein, the Essence Fire Raven was well on its way to a full recovery, and it was entirely possible that it could even reach greater heights than its former peak.

The fire raven seemed to have sensed Han Li's presence, and the giant cocoon wobbled slightly as a string of crisp chirps rang out from within.

"Keep focusing on your recovery here, there's no need to come out anytime soon," Han Li said with a faint smile.

His words of reassurance seemed to have worked, and the giant cocoon settled down again.

Han Li watched the cocoon for a moment longer, yet right as he was about to depart, the entire underground cavern suddenly shuddered violently.

A burst of indescribably enormous power erupted forth from underground like a ferocious wave, and the roof of the cavern trembled as countless crimson rock fragments came raining down from above.

Even with Han Li's current cultivation base, he was still quite alarmed by this burst of tremendous power.

In the next instant, a deafening sound that resembled the toll of a giant bell rang out from deep under the earth.

The underground cavern quaked violently once again, and a giant wave that was several hundred feet tall rose up from the lake of lava, sending molten lava splattering in all directions.

The giant cocoon hovering in mid-air also wobbled a few times before setting down again.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly as a rumor pertaining to the Bell Toll Mountain Range sprang into his mind.

It was said that this place had been given its name due to the strange bell-toll-like sound that would ring out from underground in the region every once in a while.

In all of his years at the Blaze Dragon Dao, Han Li had never heard this so-called bell toll, and he was only hearing it for the first time now.

However, the burst of power that had erupted forth from underground didn't seem to have come from tectonic plate movement.

Han Li pondered this for a moment before shaking his head to rid himself of that train of thought.

Regardless of what the underlying reason was, this didn't have anything to do with him, and he had plenty of other things to worry about.

He took another glance at the giant cocoon before turning to depart, but all of a sudden, he abruptly turned back around like lightning as a hint of blue light flashed through his eyes.

He had turned around so quickly that a loud snap had rung out in the air, and he was staring intently at the surface of the lake of lava.

It was only for an instant, but out of the corner of his eye, he had spotted a massive red shadow flashing past at the bottom of the lake of lava.

The red shadow resembled a creature's tail, and it had flashed past at an extraordinary speed.

As soon as Han Li noticed this, he had already released his spiritual sense, but he was unable to track down the red shadow.

There were all types of chaotic auras underground that were severely limiting his spiritual sensory range.

What was that thing?

Han Li remained standing on the spot in silence for a long while, then raised his head to inspect his surroundings with a faint smile on his face.

It seemed that this Bell Toll Mountain Range was far more complex than he had imagined. However, even if there were some type of mysterious creature lurking in here, it most likely didn't pose a threat to the Essence Fire Raven.

With that in mind, Han Li turned and made his way out of the underground cavern.

Several hours later, in the High Profound Palace of the Cloud Piercing Peak.

There were many elders and disciples gathered in front of the white and azure stone walls in the palace, and all of them were scouring the walls for missions that were suitable for them.

As for the golden stone wall at the rear of the hall, that was nowhere near as lively abd bustling. There were only a few True Immortal cultivators standing in front of it, sighing incessantly with tightly furrowed brows.

"Why is it so hard to find a mission that pays well, but doesn't require much work?" a white-haried elder sighed before departing.

Right as he was exiting the hall, he passed by Han Li, who strode directly to the golden stone wall.

He raised his head to look up at the stone wall, looking at the missions from the top, and as his gaze roamed downward, his brows also began to furrow.

The missions on the stone wall were either ones where the reward didn't match the difficulty, or required an extremely long time to complete, so it was no wonder that all of the other elders were feeling so dismayed.

The most eye-catching mission on the stone wall was naturally still the one that required one to cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture to the second level.

Right at this moment, a voice rang out from behind Han Li.

"Is that you, Brother Li?"

Han Li turned around to discover a pair of familiar figures, and the one who had spoken was a man with a coarse beard. He was none other than the inner sect elder with the Nan surname who had participated in the mission released by Xiong Shan alongside Han Li.

"Long time no see, Brother Nan, Brother Lu," Han Li greeted as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Indeed. I heard from Brother Qi some time ago that you were in seclusion, and I didn't think you would come out so soon," Elder Nan chuckled as he returned Han Li's salute.

"Aren't you a little too conscientious, Brother Li? You've only just come out of seclusion, and you're already here checking out the missions," Elder Lu jibed as he also cupped his fist in a salute.

"The deadline for the sect's regular elder mission completion is about to arrive soon, so I thought I'd take on some missions to get the job done as soon as possible," Han Li explained.

The two elders exchanged a glance upon hearing this, and peculiar looks appeared on both of their faces.

Elder Nan cleared his throat, then asked, "Brother Li, are you really going to complete three regular elder missions to fulfill your obligations?"

Their reactions naturally didn't evade Han Li's notice, and he replied, "I am. This was the option that I chose when I first entered the sect. Is there something wrong?"

"Well... The regular elder missions released by the sect have always offered great rewards, but they've also always been quite difficult to complete, either requiring extensive investment of time and effort, or requiring one to take great risks," Elder Nan explained.

"Indeed. In contrast, it's far easier to serve at a palace for 100 out of every 1,000 years. There's always been an element of luck in the regular elder missions as those missions are assigned to you, and you don't have the option of picking and choosing missions as you please. If you ask me, it would be a better idea to take on a few missions here and earn sufficient merit points to fulfill your obligations," Elder Lu added.

"I see. Thank you for your advice. At the moment, I can't see any suitable missions on this wall, so I'll go and see what regular elder missions are assigned to me before making a decision. Where do I go to receive those missions?" Han Li asked.

"In that case, we won't try to dissuade you any further. To the left of the High Profound Palace's rear hall is a side hall, and you'll be assigned your missions there," Elder Nan replied.

"Thank you, Brother Nan. I'll be going now."

Han Li cupped his fist in a salute toward the two elders before departing.

He made his way around the golden stone wall, then made his way into the rear hall of the High Profound Palace, and sure enough, there was an entrance to a side hall on the left.

The entrance was slightly ajar, and he made his way toward it before pushing it open and entering the side hall, which wasn't very large, only around the same size as Han Li's guest room.

On the ceiling was a skylight, through which a beam of sunlight was shining directly down upon a potted plant sitting on the upper right corner of a redwood table in the room.

The plant was only around half a foot tall, and it resembled an ancient pine tree. It had a glittering and translucent appearance under the light of the sun, and a series of faint golden veins were extending all the way from its roots to every single branch, giving off specks of starry light.

Han Li was immediately able to tell from the abundant spiritual qi contained within the plant that it was a precious spirit medicine.

However, he didn't recognize this spirit medicine, nor had he ever seen this type of planting method, and he found himself unable to look away.

Chapter 217: Sloppy Old Man

"You like it?"

Right as Han Li was growing rather transfixed by what he was seeing, a rather enigmatic voice rang out from behind the redwood table.

Han Li hurriedly turned in that direction to find an elderly man reclining lazily in a large taishi chair behind the table.

He wore a lotus crown and an old gray daoist robe. His gray hair was quite disheveled, while the tip of his nose was slightly red, giving him a very sloppy appearance.

Furthermore, there was a gourd strapped to his belt on either side of his waist.

One gourd was silver, while the other was red, and there were complex runes engraved on both of them, indicating that they were clearly no ordinary gourds.

"I do," Han Li replied.

"You like it more than those women with big tits and arses?" the elderly man asked as he sat up a little straighter.

Han Li was completely taken aback by this question and didn't know how to respond.

The elderly man sitting on the chair seemed to have been a very enigmatic person.

The fact that he was sitting here indicated that he was the attendant elder overseeing this, but not only was he not wearing an inner sect elder robe, the potted spirit plant on the table and the two gourds strapped to his waist didn't appear to have been things that the average person could've owned.

What was most perplexing to him was that the elderly man's aura was extremely strange, and even with his spiritual sense, he was unable to ascertain the man's cultivation base.

"Please don't fool around with me any longer, Senior. I've come here to accept my regular elder missions," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Seeing as he was unable to glean the man's cultivation base, it was best to play it safe and refer to him as senior.

The elderly man seemed to have not heard Han Li at all as he grumbled to himself, "What a terrible job this is! I'm about to get bored to death! It's much more fun tending to my plants..."

He then leaned forward slightly and removed the silver gourd from his belt before pulling out the stopper with a quiet "pop", and the entire side hall was instantly filled with the sweet and fragrant aroma of honey.

As soon as Han Li caught a whiff of this aroma, his eyes immediately lit up. It seemed that the silver gourd contained some type of mixed spirit liquid.

A slightly smug smile appeared on the elderly man's face at the sight of Han Li's reaction.

He raised the gourd before slowly tipping it forward, gently pouring a drop of golden liquid out from within onto the soil at the foot of the potted plant on the table.

The potted plant immediately began to glow with golden radiance, which slowly flowed up along the plant like water until it reached all the way to the very tips of its branches and pine-needle-like leaves.

Only after this process had repeated itself several times did the golden light gradually fade away.

The elderly man gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then strapped the silver gourd back to his belt before pulling out the red gourd on the other side.

Han Li thought that this gourd contained another type of spirit liquid that he was going to pour onto the plant, but to his surprise, the elderly man removed the stopper before chugging down the contents of the gourd.

An even stronger aroma instantly permeated throughout the entire hall, completely overriding the aroma of the spirit liquid from before.

It was clear that this gourd contained an extremely fragrant wine, rather than another type of spirit liquid.

Han Li was rendered speechless upon seeing this, and he turned to examine the potted plant once again.

After having his fill of wine, the elderly man wiped his lips with the back of his hand, and the tip of his nose had turned an even brighter shade of red.

He took a glance at Han Li, and was very pleased to see Han Li displaying such keen interest in his potted plant.

Unbeknownst to him, Han Li was pondering how to learn this type of planting method so that he could use it for himself. If he could do that, then he would be able to plant precious spirit medicines directly in his secret chamber, rather than in the medicine fields.

"Looking at the sequence of missions, the mission that you have to take on is to go to an island by the Cloud Lake Island in the eastern sea of the Ancient Cloud Continent. There, you have to find the lair of an Origin Mirage Beast and bring back one of its spirit husks."

The elderly man had pulled out a thick azure book from somewhere, and he had flipped to a certain page before assigning Han Li his mission.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this. "The mission only requires me to bring back a spirit husk?"

"Don't underestimate this Origin Mirage Beast. According to my knowledge, it's already reached the mid-True Immortal Stage, and it's not an easy task to sneak into its lair to steal its spirit husk," the elderly man cautioned.

"That's a very valid piece of advice, Senior. I was too quick to jump to conclusions. Would you happen to have any other information on this beast, Senior?" Han Li asked.

"I can tell you've got decent taste, and you've been quite polite to me, so I'll give you this piece of information. The Origin Mirage Beast is constantly in seclusion, but for seven days out of every decade, it'll leave its lair to wreak havoc wherever it pleases, and that gives you a window of opportunity to steal its spirit husk. If you're not in luck, then you'll just have to wait for a few years. Don't go rushing in recklessly and losing your life," the elderly man said.

"Thank you for this information, Senior," Han Li replied.

"This mission can be both difficult or easy, depending on how you approach it. As long as you're patient, there's not much risk involved, and the reward is 200 merit points, which you can come back here to collect after you've completed the mission," the elderly man continued.

Han Li gave an affirmative response, then handed over his elder badge to the elderly man.

After accepting the mission and securing the relevant map and information, Han Li bade farewell to the elderly man before departing.

In the air above the High Profound Palace, Han Li contemplated his options for a moment before deciding to head straight to Cloud Lake Island.

This wasn't because he was confident that he would be able to slay the Origin Mirage Beast, or because he was in a hurry to complete the mission. Instead, it was because he had no idea when the Origin Mirage Beast was going to leave its lair, and if he were to delay for too long, only to just so happen to miss that seven-day window, then he would have to wait a decade before he could complete the mission.

Hence, the safest course of action was to get there as early as possible.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately made his way to the teleportation hall on the plaza, then teleported to the Seaview Peak, which was situated in the eastern part of the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

This mountain was near the eastern border of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, and it was currently the furthest area that Han Li could reach through teleportation array.

Standing on the mountain summit and casting his gaze toward the east, even with his exceptional eyesight, he was only able to see a black line as thin as a strand of hair in the distance, and that was the eastern sea next to the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

Han Li's destination, Cloud Lake Island, was one of the countless islands in that region of the sea.

He pulled out a map of that region of the sea that he had obtained from the sloppy old man, and after carefully inspecting it for a long while, he rose up into the air before flying in a certain direction as a streak of azure light.

……

Several months later.

In the region of the sea to the east of the Bell Toll Mountain Range was a massive island shaped like a lotus leaf.

There was a lake on the island that took up around a tenth of the island's entire area, and it sat at the center of the island like a bright green jewel. The bodies of water branching off from the lake spread in all directions over the island, much like the veins of the figurative lotus leaf.

This lake was called the Cloud Cover Lake, and it was the source of all of the freshwater on this island. The name of the island was also derived from this lake, and bodies of water that split off from the lake nurtured all of the tens of millions of living beings on the island. There were numerous cities, towns, and villages dotted along the shores of the bodies of water, and to the west of the Cloud Cover Lake was a main branch by the name of Heavy Sand River.

To the left of the river hundreds of thousands of kilometers away from the Cloud Cover Lake was a massive city that was over 1,000 feet tall, aptly named Heavy Sand City.

The city was constructed from the unique black heavy sand that was gathered from the Heavy Sand River, and at this point, the city had already stood for close to 100,000 years. Not only were there millions of mortals living in the city, there was even a cultivation sect that was as old as the city itself.

That night, the sky was gradually beginning to darken, and the sun hadn't yet completely set.

The setting sun was only just peeking over the horizon, and its dying light had illuminated a vast section of the sea and the tall city walls of Heavy Sand City a blood-red color.

All of a sudden, a streak of azure light flew rapidly over the sky before landing atop the city to reveal none other than Han Li, who had arrived here after a long journey.

He swept his gaze across the buildings in the city down below, and a grim look appeared on his face.

Most of what should've been an impregnable city wall beneath his feet had already collapsed, leaving an enormous hole, and even the embrasured watchtowers on the city walls had been completely destroyed and reduced to an unrecognizable state.

Both the inner and outer sides of what remained of the city walls were smeared with blood, some of which had already begun to turn black and coagulate, giving off a nauseating odor.

The city was riddled with destroyed and collapsed buildings, and many sets of human and animal remains could be seen interspersed throughout the rubble, all of which were severely ravaged and in horrific condition.

As the sun gradually set below the horizon, the entire city was engulfed by a giant shadow, plunging it into complete darkness. There was no other sound aside from the howling of the wind blowing through the completely lifeless city.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly spotted a burst of yellow light, which had appeared in the central area of the city, and it seemed that someone had lit a fire there.

He immediately released his spiritual sense in that direction, and moments later, he shot forth from the top of the city wall like an arrow, hurtling directly toward the spot where the fire had been lit.

A resounding boom rang out as Han Li plummeted down into the center of a spacious courtyard, causing the entire courtyard to shudder violently. The houses that were already on the verge of collapse instantly toppled over one after another to produce a loud commotion.

The fire that had been lit at the center of the courtyard was also scattered into countless sparks by the force of the impact of Han Li's landing.

The three people gathered around the fire were so horrified that they instantly fell to their knees.

Among them, a brown-robed young man and a middle-aged woman were trembling uncontrollably as cold sweat poured down their faces, while the dark-skinned man that rounded out the trio was kowtowing repeated to the ground, not even daring to look at Han Li as he implored, "Please spare us, Senior! We'll leave this place right away..."

Chapter 218: A Coincidence

As the dark-skinned man was speaking, he was frantically crawling backwards on his hands and knees.

The three of them were only late-Foundation Establishment cultivators, and even though they couldn't ascertain Han Li's cultivation base, just the force of his landing alone made it clear to them that he was a powerful cultivator who could crush them like ants, so they naturally didn't dare to linger here any longer.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he said in a cold voice, "Hold on a second. Who are you?"

The trio immediately stiffened up in the face of Han Li's interrogation, and in the end, it was the brown-robed young man who mustered up some courage before replying, "We are just a group of itinerant cultivators from Floral Sun City. We didn't know that you were here, Senior. Otherwise, there's no way we would've dared to come here."

"Do you know what happened here to reduce this city to such a state?" Han Li asked.

The brown-robed young man faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to Han Li with a perplexed expression as he asked, "You're unaware of what's happened here, Senior? Could it be that you're foreign cultivator?"

Han Li was initially rather perplexed to hear this, but he then quickly understood what the young man was referring to. Indeed, for these low-grade cultivators who had most likely lived their entire lives in a small area on the island, they were naturally of the opinion that the island they were on was an entire continent, which made all cultivators from outside the island foreign cultivators to them.

"Cut the chit-chat! Tell me what happened here!" Han Li said in a cold voice.

"From what we've heard, the creature that resides in the Cloud Cover Lake came out to feed again, and it slaughtered everyone in the city," the brown-robed young man hurriedly replied.

"What does this creature look like? Have you seen it for yourself?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I certainly haven't seen the creature, Senior. Otherwise, there's no way I would've lived to tell the tale. However, it's said that this creature has already been cultivating for countless years, and its enormous in stature, almost comparable in size to the hill outside the city. Its tongue is several thousand feet in length, and the venom in its belly..."

The brown-robed young man hurriedly told Han Li everything that he had heard about the beast.

"That's right! The creature comes out to wreak havoc every once in a while, and each time, it'll only be satisfied after slaughtering an entire city of people!" the dark-skinned man added.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "Does this creature only come out for seven days once every 10 years, only to disappear again for the next 10 years?"

The dark-skinned man was rather taken aback to hear this, and he asked in a careful voice, "Have you already heard the rumors, Senior?"

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon hearing this.

The creature that these people were referring to was most likely that mid-True Immortal Stage Origin Mirage Beast. It seemed that even though he had gotten here as quickly as he could, he was still one step too late.

In fact, he had felt rather perplexed on the entire way here.

Under normal circumstances, if an island had a freshwater lake at its center, then there should've been more settlements and higher population density closer to the lake, yet the situation on Cloud Cover Island was the exact opposite.

The coastal regions of the island were riddled with cities that virtually formed a ring around the entire island, but the closer one drew to the center of the island, the more sparse and well-concealed the human settlements became.

Even though Heavy Sand City was still hundreds of kilometers away from the Cloud Cover Cover Lake, it was already the closest city to the lake in the western region of Cloud Lake Island.

Given the information that Han Li had just received, this situation was most likely a result of the threat posed by the Origin Mirage Beast in the Cloud Cover Lake at the center of the island.

"Has there been no one to stand up to the creature and deliver it the retribution that it deserves for its heinous actions?" Han Li asked.

"Apparently, an immortal came to the island under the request of several nearby sects a very long time ago with the objective of slaying the creature. In the end, he fought the creature for three days and three nights before being defeated and retreating with severe injuries. After that battle, all of the sects involved were wiped out by the creature in a matter of days, and ever since then, no one has dared to stand up to it," the brown-robed young man explained.

"Come to think of it, what are the three of you doing here?" Han Li asked.

The three people had been kneeling on the ground the entire time, and they exchanged a few hesitant glances, not willing to reveal their motivations.

"Is there something you can't tell me?" Han Li asked as his expression darkened slightly.

The brown-robed young man shuddered, then hurriedly explained, "Where we are right now is the former site of the Falling Sand Sect, the largest sect in a radius of tens of thousand of kilometers. We were hoping to get here before everyone else and..."

The brown-robed young man's voice trailed off here, and Han Li finished his sentence for him. "And dig up some treasures from the ruins, right?"

"We've only just gotten here and haven't had a chance to find anything yet, Senior! if you don't believe me, you can check my storage pouch."

The brown-robed young man immediately pulled out his storage pouch before offering it to Han Li as he spoke, and the other two cultivators hurriedly did the same thing.

All it took was a brief flash of Han Li's spiritual sense for him to verify that they weren't lying to him. Everything in their three storage pouches combined didn't even have a collective value of five mid-grade spirit stones.

Han Li didn't despise them for their actions at all. As bottom-dwelling cultivators, particularly itinerant ones with no sects to rely on, cultivation was particularly arduous, and he was more aware of this than anyone.

He then carefully scoured the ruins of the Falling Sand Sect with his spiritual sense, and his brows quickly furrowed slightly.

This was a sect of a decent size, but for some reason, there were only a pitiful number of treasures left behind, and they were all of an extremely low caliber for Han Li's standards.

"There are still some things under the ruins to the east over there. Dig those things up yourselves, then leave this place right away."

As soon as his voice trailed off, Han Li rose up into the air as a streak of azure light before flying toward the eastern part of Heavy Sand City.

The treasures left behind in the sect were completely unappealing to him, so he decided to leave them to this trio instead as compensation for the information that they had provided him. Perhaps those treasures would be able to assist them greatly on their path of cultivation.

The trio of cultivators were instantly rooted to the spot upon hearing this, and they were so bewildered that Han Li was willing to help them rather than condemn them that they were at a loss for words. By the time they returned to their senses, Han Li was already nowhere to be seen.

All three of them turned in the direction that Han Li had departed in, then extended earnest bows of respect and gratitude before scrambling to their feet and rushing over to the ruins to the east to uncover the treasures there.

As for Han Li, he didn't immediately depart after reaching the eastern part of the city. Instead, he picked out a relatively intact courtyard in the area before descending into it.

The courtyard was quite a spacious one, indicating that it had previously been inhabited by quite a wealthy mortal clan, but those mortals were obviously no longer of this world.

After arriving in the courtyard, Han Li set up some simple restrictions, then made his way into the main hall.

He lit up one of the oil lamps in the room, then sat down onto a chair beside it.

After that, he flipped a hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask, which he promptly put on, and after chanting an incantation, a massive azure array plate projection appeared before him.

Prior to coming here, he hadn't done much research into the Origin Mirage Beast as he had been focused on traveling to Cloud Lake Island as quickly as possible. He had originally planned to enquire some larger sects in Heavy Sand City for information pertaining to the beast, but that plan had clearly fallen through.

While it was true that he had missed this seven-day window, he wasn't planning to return to the sect right away. Instead, he wanted to see if there were any other ways through which he could complete this mission.

However, the information provided by the sect was far from detailed, and his knowledge of the Origin Mirage Beast was also very limited. As for the information provided by the trio of cultivators from earlier, those were mostly just rumors, so they weren't to be relied upon.

Hence, he decided to turn to the Transient Guild to see if he could uncover more information on this beast.

The identification mission for the giant egg and those feathers that he had released earlier was still active, but hadn't received any responses.

After searching for some time, his eyes suddenly lit up slightly.

There really was a mission concerning the Origin Mirage Beast, and it seemed to have been posted over 1,000 years ago.

"Slay a True Immortal Stage Origin Mirage Beast. Reward: 30 Immortal Origin Stones."

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, and this felt like too much of a coincidence.

Origin Mirage Beasts weren't extremely rare, but those who had reached the True Immortal Stage had to have been exceedingly rare. Could it be that the target for this mission was none other than the one in the Cloud Cover Lake?

A contemplative look appeared on his face as he pointed at the mission to contact the one who had released it through his mask.

Around 15 minutes later, a burst of ripples surged over the array plate projection, immediately following which a projection of an azure figure wearing a deer mask took shape in front of Han Li.

"Are you interested in the mission I released, Fellow Daoist?" the figure asked.

"Indeed, I am interested in the mission that you released concerning the Origin Mirage Beast. Do you know where it resides or have any further information on the beast?" Han Li asked.

A hint of elation flashed through the azure figure's eyes, and he hurriedly replied, "I'll be sure to tell you everything I know, Fellow Daoist. The beast in question resides on an island by the name of Cloud Lake Island to the east of the Ancient Cloud Continent, and it possesses the bloodline of the ancient true spirit, the Mirage Dragon. As a result, it can take on countless different forms and is particularly adept at adopting human forms."

"I'm assuming it must be quite difficult to deal with, right? Otherwise, there's no way your mission would've been left hanging for so long," Han Li mused.

"Truth be told, even as far back as several tens of thousands of years ago, the beast had already reached the mid-True Immortal Stage, and it's extremely cunning, so it is indeed rather troublesome to deal with," the azure figure replied in a truthful manner.

"In that case, 30 Immortal Origin Stones isn't much compensation," Han Li remarked.

A hint of urgency crept into the azure figure's voice as he said, "Truth be told, that's already all of the Immortal Origin Stones in my possession at the moment. However, the spirit husk of the beast is an exceptional spirit material for refining armor, and you can keep it if you can kill that beast."

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li nodded as he said, "Alright."

"Does that mean... you're accepting this mission, Fellow Daoist?" the azure figure asked with a hint of disbelief in his voice.

"I can't guarantee that I'll be able to complete the mission, but I'll certainly give it a try," Han Li replied.

"This is fantastic! In that case, I wish you the best of luck, Fellow Daoist!" the azure figure said in an ecstatic voice.

Chapter 219: Small Test of Abilities

Two days later.

The morning sun was rising up from the surface of the sea, basking the cold Cloud Lake Island in a warm glow.

There was a murky layer of mist above the surface of the Cloud Cover Lake at the center of the island, and the mist showed no signs of dissipating even under the light of the rising sun.

At this moment, Han Li was hovering high up in the sky, surveying the lake down below.

Blue light flashing within his eyes, while his spiritual sense was scouring over the lake, but he discovered that he was unable to see or detect anything through the mist.

With a flick of his wrist, the long black saber that he had obtained from Fang Pan appeared in his grasp.

Layers of golden scales that emerged over his body, and his arm instantly thickened significantly while a layer of piercing black light appeared over the surface of the black saber, drawing in the world's origin qi in the surrounding area.

Countless inky-black runes appeared on the blade of the saber, releasing waves of black light that were imbued with potent law power fluctuations, causing the surrounding space to tremble and ripple.

He raised the saber high above his head, then brought it down in a forceful slashing motion toward the surface of the lake down below.

The sound of howling wind rang out as the entire saber glowed with radiant black light, and a massive saber projection that was over 1,000 feet in length was unleashed before crashing down upon the lake with devastating force.

Even before the saber projection arrived, the sheer force and pressure that it released caused the surface of the lake to part down the center.

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out as massive waves swept over the surface of the Cloud Cover Lake, and two enormous walls of water erupted in opposite directions before sweeping toward the shore with tremendous force.

The waves were so powerful that they swept all the way beyond the shore of the lake before crashing into the nearby forest.

"Who's there?!"

A thunderous roar of fury rang out from the bottom of the lake, immediately following which a streak of golden light erupted forth from beneath the waves, hurtling directly toward Han Li.

Han Li focused his gaze on the streak of golden light to find that it contained a square-faced middle-aged man in a golden robe with a pair of dark purple eyes. The man was holding a golden longsword that it was piercing directly at Han Li.

The man wasn't giving off any demon beast aura, but Han Li's intuition told him that this was the Origin Mirage Beast that he was searching for.

The golden longsword had radiant runes shimmering on its surface, and it was giving off a peerlessly sharp aura.

A loud clang rang out as Han Li parried the sword with his black blade, and the tremendous impact of the clash sent the golden-robed man flying back, while Han Li only wobbled slightly before immediately steadying himself.

"To think that a pitiful little itinerant immortal like yourself would dare to challenge me! You must truly have a death wish! I just so happen to require the blood essence of a human True Immortal to help me break through my bottleneck, so you've come at just the right time!" the golden-robed man chuckled coldly as he steadied himself several thousand feet away.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he suddenly hurled his golden longsword forward, and it split up into thousands of golden longswords amid a flash of light, arranging themselves into layers to resemble an enormous golden lotus flower blooming in the sky.

In the next instant, a string of loud clangs rang out as the golden longswords flew through the air one after another, hurtling directly toward Han Li like a flight golden sword dragon.

Initially, Han Li was of the opinion that these golden longswords were nothing more than sword projections, but only as the golden sword dragon flew toward him and attempted to sink its fangs into his body did he discover that it possessed a substantial form.

He immediately raised his saber to ward off the sword dragon, jamming it into the sword dragon's mouth to prevent it from being able to bite down onto him.

At the same time, the golden sword dragon lashed out with its claws from down below, striking him on the chest to tear his robes apart, leaving several alarming white marks on his golden scales.

Han Li immediately retaliated with a slash of his saber, which raised a huge flurry of sparks as he pulled it out of the sword dragon's mouth, then stomped both feet heavily down onto the dragon's head to send it flying back through the air.

However, before he had a chance to steady himself, the sound of howling wind rang out from behind him, and a strange beast that resembled a True Dragon suddenly appeared behind him before biting down toward his head.

The beast had the head of a dragon, but no dragon horn, and it also had the body of a dragon, but no dragon claws.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and azure light flashed over his entire body as he ducked to the side, allowing him to just barely evade the beast's attack.

However, in the next instant, he felt a burst of excruciating pain spear through his shoulder.

As it turned out, the dragon-like beast had sunk its fangs into his shoulder, and even with his astonishingly powerful physical constitution, the creature was able to bite straight through his shoulder, causing him to bleed profusely.

Han Li was very much alarmed by this. He had clearly evaded that attack, yet somehow, the creature had still managed to sink its fangs into him.

He raised his saber-wielding hand up high, and right as he was about to bring the saber down upon the head of the dragon that was biting into his shoulder, a strong sense of peril immediately welled up in his heart, causing him to stop cold in his tracks.

In the next instant, Han Li felt a sharp pain in his mind, not because he had been struck by some other attack. Instead, he had unleashed a spiritual attack upon himself in order to snap himself back to his senses.

Sure enough, following that burst of sharp pain in his mind, he turned to his shoulder to find that it was completely fine, with no dragon's head attached to it.

If he had brought his saber down just now, he would've unwittingly chopped off his own arm.

"What?! There's no way a mid-True Immortal cultivator could've seen through my illusions!" the golden robed man exclaimed in disbelief as he hovered in the air several thousand feet away.

Even though Han Li had broken himself out of his opponent's illusion, he was still feeling extremely apprehensive.

He abruptly shot forward as he slashed his black saber through the air in an arc, lashing out at his opponent with tremendous force.

"Insolence!"

A furious look appeared in the golden-robed man's eyes upon seeing this, and he made a rapid series of hand seals, following which a ball of five-colored light instantly erupted out from between his fingers.

The five-colored light had a dreamy quality to it, and Han Li was struck by a rush of dizziness at the mere sight of it.

At the same time, a metallic grating sound rang out, and the golden sword dragon pounced at him from behind before attempting to sink its fangs into his back.

Han Li reflexively raised a hand to shield his eyes while slashing his saber through the air behind him.

A crescent-shaped saber projection was sent sweeping through the air before crashing heavily into the sword dragon, causing the latter to rock back amid a resounding clang.

Right at this moment, a giant translucent five-colored hand suddenly reached out from the illusory five-colored light ahead of Han Li before closing itself around his entire body.

Han Li instantly felt a burst of tremendous force compressing around his chest, striking him with a sense of asphyxiation.

In addition to that, the five-colored illusory light was still flashing incessantly, and its dizzying effect was slowing down his reactions ever so slightly.

"Die!"

An explosive roar rang out from behind the five-colored light, while the sword dragon that had just been repelled by Han Li pounced at him once again.

Two of the golden swords on its head abruptly elongated to resemble a pair of horns, which were aimed directly at the back of Han Li's chest.

Blue light was flashing urgently in Han Li's eyes, yet he was still unable to see through the illusory light up ahead, and his consciousness was beginning to become rather murky.

In this dire situation, he let loose a thunderous roar, and golden light flashed over his body as all of his muscles rapidly bulged, transforming him into a giant golden ape that was over 1,000 feet tall in the blink of an eye.

The giant hand around him was unable to contain him any longer and exploded violently.

As soon as he was freed from the giant hand, Han Li grabbed onto his black saber with both hands. The black saber had also extended to several hundred feet in length to match his new stature, and he slashed it viciously toward the illusory five-colored light and the golden-robed man behind it.

The sound of howling wind rang out as the five-colored illusory light was instantly scattered by the astral winds unleashed by the almighty slash, while the golden-robed man hurriedly flew in retreat with an alarmed and fearful look on his face.

However, the attack encompassed an enormous area, and he was unable to evade it in a short time.

Right as the blade was about to reach him, a peculiar grin suddenly appeared on the golden-robed man's face, and he didn't retreat any further as he merely allowed the blade to slice him into two.

The two halves of the golden-robed man's body warped momentarily before abruptly vanishing into thin air.

At the same time, the giant sword dragon that was pouncing at Han Li from behind suddenly began to speak. "Let's see how you dodge this attack!"

Its speed abruptly doubled as it spoke, and it was piercing directly toward the back of Han Li's chest.

With his back facing the sword dragon, Han Li was only able to take a step forward, and he didn't have enough time to dodge the attack or turn around.

Right as the sword dragon was about to plunge into his back, a burst of azure light suddenly appeared in the air between him and the sword dragon before abruptly vanishing from the spot.

In the next instant, the oncoming golden sword dragon suddenly lost all momentum, and it plunged straight down toward the lake below in a limp and lifeless fashion.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he reverted back to his human form, then descended in pursuit of the golden sword dragon.

A string of clangs rang out in succession as the golden swords around the sword dragon's body fell away one after another, revealing the body of the golden-robed man within.

However, a gruesome hole had been punched through his glabella, and his strange purple eyes had also lost all of its luster and vibrance, having turned a lifeless gray color.

The nascent soul that was residing in its head had also already been destroyed.

Han Li extended a hand before making a grabbing motion, and all of the golden longswords that had split off from the sword dragon's body vanished amid a flash of golden light, leaving behind only a single sword that fell into his grasp.

He inspected the golden longsword briefly before stowing it away into his storage bracelet.

Meanwhile, a burst of azure light suddenly flashed within the bloody hole in the golden-robed man's glabella, and a tiny azure sword that was only around an inch in length flew out from within before quickly expanding and reverting back to its original form.

This was none other than Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and all 72 of them had been combined into one on this occasion.

After nurturing the flying swords in his body for the past few decades, they had already completely absorbed the immense amount of sword essence that they had devoured all those years ago. At the moment, each sword had just about reached the level of an Acquired Immortal Treasure, and when combined into a single sword, they were well and truly comparable to a true Acquired Immortal Treasure.

Back in the Blaze Dragon Dao, he had never used the swords as he was concerned that Xiong Shan would notice, so this was the first opportunity that he had had to test out the swords, and they had given him a massively pleasant surprise.

Chapter 220: Along the Way

It seemed that Han Li was able to slay the Origin Mirage Beast in just an instant, but in reality, it had taken a bit of preparation.

Back when he had almost chopped off his own arm after falling prey to the golden-robed man's illusion the first time, he had already activated his Spirit Refinement Technique to discover that its true body was concealed within the sword dragon, so the golden-robed man was nothing more than a deeper illusion.

After acquiring this piece of knowledge, Han Li decided to play along, combining the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in his body into one in advance before lashing out to deal the killing blow right as his opponents thought that he had won the battle.

With a wave of his hand, all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew back to Han Li, then circled around in the air for a moment before vanishing into his body.

Han Li took a glance at the body of the golden-robed man on the surface of the lake, then rose up into the air before descending onto the lake as well, sending slight ripples surging over its surface.

He bent down and examined the golden-robed man's body with his spiritual sense for a moment, then raised his right hand before bringing it down like a blade, plunging it straight into the golden-robed man's lower abdomen to pull out a walnut-sized dark purple demon core.

After losing its demon core, the body of the golden-robed man suddenly began to expand.

A layer of fine cold scales appeared over the body's skin, and the golden dragon robe that it was wearing was quickly torn apart. The body gradually elongated before ultimately transforming into a dragon-like beast with no horns and no claws, then slowly sank into the lake.

After a moment of hesitation, Han Li cast a water repulsion restriction on himself before descending into the lake as well.

Inside the lake, he quickly spotted the body of the Origin Mirage Beast, which was sinking toward a palace on the lakebed.

The Cloud Cover Lake was over 1,000 feet deep, and the light on the lakebed was extremely dim, but the palace was giving off radiant white light, resembling a glittering and translucent crystalline palace.

Upon arriving in front of the palace, Han Li discovered that it was encompassed within a near-transparent light membrane that was keeping out all of the water in the lake.

Instead of immediately entering the palace, Han Li drifted over to the body of the Origin Mirage Beast, then plunged his fingers into the body to pull out a tendon.

The deer-masked figure from the Transient Guild had told him that this demon beast potentially possessed the bloodline of the Mirage Dragon, so he wanted to see if he could extract the blood essence. However, after toiling away for quite some time, he was unable to extract even a single drop of blood essence, and he could only give up in the end.

After harvesting all of the useful parts of the demon beast's body, he returned to the palace and bypassed the light membrane with ease, arriving in front of the palace gates.

The crystalline palace before him was extremely beautiful to behold, with all types of intricate engravings on its surface, making it resemble an immortal abode far more so than the lair of a demon beast.

Han Li laid his palm against the palace gates before pushing forward, and the two white jade gates, each of which was around 30 feet tall and a foot thick, began to slowly open inward.

Han Li made his way into the palace through the entrance, and he discovered that the furnishings inside were rather bare.

There were only two rows of cylindrical pillars standing on either side of the palace, but several small mountains of items of all types of different descriptions had been piled up around the pillars, presenting an astonishing sight to behold.

As it turned out, these mountainous piles of items consisted of all types of spirit stones and treasures of different grades and calibers, all of which were mixed together and strewn about in a haphazard fashion.

Several days ago, he had wondered to himself why there were so few treasures left in the ruins of the Falling Sand Sect, but it had now become apparent to him that the vast majority if the treasures in the sect had to have been brought here by the Origin Mirage Beast.

It was clear that this beast was a hoarder, and this vast collection had most likely come from all of the cities and sects that it had razed to the ground over the years. With its demise, all of these things now fell into Han Li's hands.

After carefully examining the mountainous piles of treasures for some time, Han Li suddenly spotted a semi-transparent object peeking out from behind a golden dragon throne deep inside the palace.

He immediately made his way over to the throne before stepping around it to discover a snake-slough-like object, which appeared as if it were made from some type of crystalline material, but it wasn't hard or cold to the touch in the slightest. Instead, it was as soft as if it had been woven from silk.

This was undoubtedly the Origin Mirage Beast's spirit husk.

Han Li immediately stowed the spirit husk away in his storage bracelet, then pulled out several storage rings to collect the mountains of treasures in the palace.

After close to half a day, all of his storage rings and the storage bracelet on his wrist had been completely filled.

The majority of the collected treasures consisted of spirit stones, and most of them were low or mid-grade ones. Among them, top-grade spirit stone proved to be exceedingly rare, with only around 600 to 700 in total.

If he were to convert the rest of the spirit stones, he estimated that he would be able to exchange them for another 300 to 400 top-grade spirit stones.

It seemed that none of the nearby sects were all that powerful. Then again, this only made sense. If there were any powerful sects nearby, then this Origin Mirage Beast wouldn't have been able to wreak havoc as it pleased for all these years.

Aside from the spirit stones, there were also over 100 treasures and several hundred artifacts, as well as some strange and exotic spirit materials, but not even a single spirit plant or pill.

The artifacts weren't noteworthy in any way, but there were some decent treasures. Of course, they weren't going to be useful to Han Li, but they would've certainly made for great additions to the collections of Meng Yungui and the others.

As for the golden longsword that the Origin Mirage Beast was using, Han Li was able to determine that it was a metal-attribute Divine Spirit Treasure, making it a treasure comparable to Han Li's former Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

There weren't many spirit materials in the Origin Mirage Beast's collection, but some of them were giving off very peculiar auras, and even though Han Li couldn't identify them, it was clear to him that they were no ordinary materials.

In particular, there were several head-sized chunks of dark golden metal that had clearly been formed naturally, but there were countless flower-petal-like patterns all over its surface. Furthermore, it was slightly warm to the touch.

For the next few days, Han Li didn't immediately depart from the palace. Instead, he took advantage of this time away from the Blaze Dragon Dao to unleash all of the sword arrays in his Azure Essence Sword Arts a few times with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Unsurprisingly, the sword arrays had become significantly more powerful, and Han Li was very pleased to see this.

Right before he departed from the Cloud Cover Lake, he put on his Transient Guild mask to contact the deer-masked figure, who was astonished that Han Li had managed to complete his mission so quickly.

Han Li naturally wasn't going to explain anything to him, and he offered the demon core of the Origin Mirage Beast for the deer-masked figure to examine. The deer-masked figure was ecstatic, and he immediately issued the 30 Immortal Origin Stones to Han Li.

The only reason Han Li had taken on this mission was because it was one that he could complete along the way while he was carrying out his regular elder mission for the Blaze Dragon Dao. Furthermore, he didn't want to have to wait a whole decade for the Origin Mirage Beast's next outing.

……

Several months later.

As soon as Han Li returned to the Blaze Dragon Dao, he immediately went to the side hall of the High Profound Palace without delay.

Just like last time, the hall was completely empty, and the gray-robed elderly man seated behind the redwood table was on the verge of falling asleep. Only after hearing the sound of Han Li's footsteps did he open his eyes ever so slightly.

The elderly man sat up straighter as he yawned and asked in a lazy voice, "Oh? Why are you back so soon? Could it be that the mission is too difficult for you to complete, so you're planning to submit merit points instead?"

Han Li offered no reply as he pulled out a storage pouch before setting it down onto the redwood table.

The elderly man faltered slightly upon seeing this, then briefly inspected the contents of the storage pouch with his spiritual sense, and all of the drowsiness in his eyes instantly vanished.

"I had high hopes for you, and you lived up to them, kid! I didn't think you'd be able to complete the mission so quickly."

"I was very fortunate. By the time I got there, the Origin Mirage Beast just so happened to have been absent, so I was able to complete the mission very quickly," Han Li lied.

"You're a lucky kid, but sometimes, luck is also a part of one's power," the elderly man chuckled in response, and it was unclear whether he believed Han Li's claims or not.

He stowed the spirit husk of the Origin Mirage Beast away, then pulled out that azure book and a jade brush. After scribbling something down into the book with the brush, he took Han Li's elder badge from him, and after a flash of white light, 200 merit points had been added to the badge.

"Alright, you've completed the first mission. Go back and take a rest, but don't forget to come back soon for your next mission," the elderly man said as he returned Han Li's badge to him.

"Please assign me the next mission right now, Senior," Han Li requested.

"Well, aren't you hard-working? You're completely different from those sly old foxes who try to delay their missions as much as possible," the elderly man chuckled.

Han Li offered no response to this.

Time was of the essence for him, so he naturally had to be more diligent.

The elderly man flipped open the azure book as he spoke, and after flipping through its pages for a while, he stopped on a certain page as he said, "There's a slightly urgent mission here, so I'll assign it to you."

"What is it, Senior?" Han Li asked.

"Our sect has a large Fire Origin Crystal mine in the Fire Cloud Peak to the southwest of the Ancient Cloud Continent. For some reason, many of the miners in there have recently gone missing, so the sect had to temporarily close down the mine. A Grand Ascension Stage elder that was stationed there ventured into the mine to examine the cause of the disappearances, but he went missing as well.

“Hence, a request has been submitted for the sect to send an inner sect elder to examine the situation and transport all of the Fire Origin Crystals that were excavated in the past 10 years back to the sect. This shouldn't be a very difficult mission, but the reward of 180 merit points is quite decent," the elderly man said.

Han Li nodded in response upon hearing this. "I see. Seeing as it's an urgent mission, I'll set off right away."

He immediately handed over his badge to accept the mission as he spoke, then departed without any delay.

"What an interesting lad," the elderly man mused to himself as he looked on at Han Li's departing figure.

Chapter 221: Wine and Conversation

Over a year later, in a vast mountain range to the southwest of the Ancient Cloud Continent.

The entire mountain range was of an extremely vibrant crimson color, and the ground was riddled with countless volcanoes that were occasionally spewing forth pillars of molten lava.

One fiery pillar after another was erupting into the heavens, presenting a stunning marvel to behold. Bursts of thunderous rumbling were ringing out incessantly, and the sky was filled with fiery clouds, while a strong sulfurous odor was wafting through the air.

Deep inside the mountain range was a mountain that was riddled with holes, giving it the appearance of a honeycomb, and this was none other than the Fire Cloud Peak.

A streak of azure light arrived on the scene in a flash before fading to reveal Han Li, and he took a glance at his surroundings, then immediately flew toward one of the mine caves down below.

Around half a month later.

Two figures, one large and one small, were locked in a fierce battle inside a massive mine cave deep under the Fire Cloud Peak.

Each clash that took place between them resulted in a thunderous commotion that caused the entire mountain to tremble violently, while countless rocks came tumbling down like rain from above.

The smaller of the two figures was none other than Han Li, and there was azure light surging all over his body as he unleashed a flurry of fist projections.

The larger figure was a giant crimson lizard that was 70 to 80 feet in length, and it appeared to be extremely agile. Furthermore, it was blasting pillars of scorching fire out of its mouth, but none of them were able to strike Han Li even once.

In contrast, Han Li was frequently landing his punches, and with each punch that struck its target, a crack would be smashed into the crimson lizard's thick scales.

Before long, the lizard's entire body was already riddled with wounds, and its scales were broken over many parts of its body.

It had been attempting to flee the battle for quite some time now, but Han Li refused to allow it to get away.

Right at this moment, Han Li threw yet another punch at the lizard, yet for some reason, the lizard didn't bother to dodge at all this time, allowing itself to be sent flying before crashing into the rock face behind it.

A large section of the scales on its back were completely shattered by the punch, and it was bleeding profusely.

Right as it was approaching the rock face, the lizard abruptly opened its mouth to blast forth a pillar of crimson flames, which instantly melted the rock face into molten lava.

The crimson lizard was just about to scurry into the molten passageway that it had created for itself when a massive black saber projection swept toward it from behind.

The saber projection was imbued with a tremendous burst of law powers as it descended upon the lizard, and without the protection of its scales, the lizard's body was instantly sliced in half by the saber projection.

Immediately thereafter, the saber projection erupted into around a dozen smaller saber projections that flew in all directions, destroying the lizard's nascent soul before it had a chance to escape.

Han Li made a beckoning motion with one hand, and the black saber flew back into his grasp.

This giant crimson lizard was the culprit responsible for all of the miner disappearances. It wasn't all that powerful, but its scales were extremely resolute, and it was able to easily melt through rock faces to traverse through the belly of the mountain, allowing it to flee from battles or unleash effective surprise attacks.

Hence, even for Han Li, it had taken half a month to finally trap and slay the beast.

A series of crimson crystals, each of which was around the size of a human head, spilled out onto the ground from the beast's disemboweled belly.

The crystals were semi-transparent with a fiery red glow within them, and they were giving off scorching heat like red-hot pieces of charcoal, except countless times hotter.

"So these are Fire Origin Crystals," Han Li remarked to himself as he descended onto the ground and picked up one of the crystals, completely unaffected by the scorching heat that the crystal was releasing.

After examining the crystal briefly, he gathered all of the Fire Origin Crystals on the ground with a sweep of his sleeve.

He then turned his gaze to the crimson lizard, and he chopped off its four claws with a few casual slashes of his black saber and stowed them away before flying in another direction as a streak of azure light.

……

Over a year later.

A figure strode quickly toward the entrance of the High Profound Palace's side hall, and it was none other than Han Li, who had only just returned to the sect.

He heaved a faint sigh of relief as he caught sight of the building up ahead. Having already completed two missions, he only had one more left to complete, and after that, he would be free to do whatever he wanted for the next century.

With that in mind, he strode into the hall and was just about to say something, only to discover that the gray-robed elderly man wasn't there.

Thus, he made his way out of the room, then stopped a young servant who just so happened to have been passing by.

"I pay my respects to the esteemed elder," the young man hurriedly said at the sight of Han Li's elder robes, and he extended a respectful bow toward Han Li as he spoke.

"Do you know where the elder in the side hall went?" Han Li asked.

"Elder Hu Yan should be in the Hundred Wine Cottage on the Hundred Wine Peak at the moment," the young man replied as he pointed to a nearby mountain.

From where they were standing, Han Li was able to see a cluster of buildings on the summit of that mountain.

A peculiar look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he waved a hand to dismiss the young servant, then immediately flew toward the Hundred Wine Peak.

It didn't take long for him to arrive on the mountain, and he took a glance at the large estate up ahead, which had white walls and a red gate. Above the gate were inscribed the words "Hundred Wine Cottage" in extremely free-flowing text that was bordering on sloppiness, as if someone had made the inscription while drunk.

After a moment of hesitation, Han Li released his spiritual sense, and sure enough, the gray--robed elderly man was in the cottage.

He took a moment to adjust his robes, then made his way into the cottage through the gate.

Inside the cottage was a large open-air area, on either side of which were rows of potted plants much like the one in the side hall. The plants were quite varied and diverse, and not only were they all looking extremely vibrant and healthy, they were all giving off their own unique aromas.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this.

In a nearby pot was a green spirit plant that was taller than a grown man, and the plant was laden with yellow beans, which were very similar to that Warrior Bean that Han Li had taken from the two Grand Ascension cultivators of the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

Only after examining the plant for a long while did he withdraw his gaze, then made his way over to a hall in the courtyard before knocking on the door.

"Elder Hu Yan, Junior Li Feiyu has come to see you."

After that, he stood outside the door and began to wait.

Moments later, the door swung open, and the rich aroma of wine poured forth from within. Elder Hu Yan's face was red with intoxication, and he was holding a bright green cup in one hand.

"Oh, it's you. I didn't think you'd be back so quickly," Elder Hu Yan said in a casual voice, then downed the contents of his cup in one go before smacking his lips with pleasure.

He then stumbled back into the hall before laying down onto a reclining chair, where he picked up a nearby flagon to fill his cup with before downing the contents of the cup in one go again.

"This is truly an exceptional wine..." Elder Hu Yan sighed in contentment.

Han Li made his way into the room, and his brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the drunk old man, but he then composed himself as he said, "Elder Hu Yan, I've completed the second mission assigned to me. A lizard beast that was about to break through to the True Immortal Stage had snuck into the Fire Cloud Peak, and it's been slain by me."

"Ah yes, I already received a message informing me of this. You did quite well, kid," Elder Hu Yan replied without even looking at Han Li, and during this time, he had drunk two more cups of wine.

"Thank you for your kind praise, Elder Hu Yan. I would like my next mission now," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Why the hurry? You've already attained immortality, so why are you still scurrying around as if there were a limit to your lifespan? Do you desire more power, or do you wish to be revered by heaven and earth themselves? If you ask me, all of that is superficial, and it's nowhere near as appealing as this cup of wine in my hand. Come and have a drink with me, and we'll set everything else aside for later," Elder Hu Yan said as he pulled out another cup and filled it, then patted a chair next to his as an invitation.

Han Li didn't want to waste any time here, but a thought then occurred to him, and he sat down before picking up the cup.

"In that case, please pardon my intrusion."

"That's the spirit! Drink all the fine wine you can, and enjoy every moment of life to its fullest! That's my mantra! Cheers!" Elder Hu Yan tapped his cup against Han Li's before downing his drink in one go, and Han Li also followed suit.

The wine was very sweet and fragrant, and as it slid down his throat, it was initially quite cold, but transformed into a surge of warmth as it flowed into his dantian. That surge of warmth then spread through his entire body, striking him with an incredibly relaxing sensation.

He felt as if he had suddenly risen up into the clouds with immortal music playing beside his ears, and it was a truly blissful state.

"This is an exceptional wine!" Han Li exclaimed.

"I like you, kid! People always say that wine confounds the senses, but they neglect to mention that only when drunk can one cast aside all inhibitions and be true to oneself. The 3,000 Great Dao laws and the meaning of life can perhaps only be gleaned while in a drunken state! You and I may be immortals, but this is something we can't obtain from anything else! Here, have some more!"

Elder Hu Yan chortled with mirth as he filled Han Li's and his own cup again.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

It seemed that Elder Hu Yan was only making drunken ramblings, but there was some deeper meaning to his words.

Following Han Li's return to the Immortal Realm, there had been danger at every turn, and he had constantly been on his guard, making him unable to cast aside his inhibitions and be true to himself. This was completely different from the carefree life of an immortal that he had previously envisioned.

However, after drinking this cup of wine and hearing these words from Elder Hu Yan, he felt as if all of his worries and frustration had faded away, and he couldn't help but want to agree.

He had once been just a boy in a village, and up to this point in his cultivation journey, he had constantly been under immense pressure. Was this how he was supposed to live out the rest of his existence?

He had already attained immortality, and he now owned a vast territory in a powerful sect, so it seemed that it was time that he also enjoyed life to its fullest.

On top of that, perhaps only by setting aside some of his shackles and inhibitions could he get closer to the Great Dao...

No, this isn't right!

All of a sudden, he shook his head forcefully to rid himself of these thoughts.

Back when he first entered the Immortal Realm, it was perhaps precisely because he had gotten complacent that he had ended up losing his memories and his treasures. Otherwise, given his cautious and steadfast nature, there should've been no way that he had fallen into such a terrible state.

He had only just re-established himself in the Immortal Realm, and if he were to let down his guard again, there was a very good chance that he would suffer the same fate.

It appeared that all was safe and well in the Immortal Realm, but in reality, there was danger lurking at every turn, and he had to be even more cautious if he wanted to survive in this hostile environment.

All of these thoughts passed through his mind in a flash, and in that instant, his determination and resolve toward pursuing the Great Dao was reaffirmed.

"This is Green Pear Wine, right? As expected, it truly is an outstanding wine," Han Li praised as he tipped his cup back, but his eyes had become extremely clear, and the complacent sensation that had clouded his heart had completely faded.

Chapter 222: Soul Mates in Wine

"Oh? You're a wine expert as well?" Elder Hu Yan asked as a hint of surprise appeared in his eyes.

"I wouldn't dare to call myself an expert in front of you, Elder Hu Yan," Han Li replied with a smile.

Indeed, he was far from a wine expert. He had only learned some things about this subject as he was often dragged along by Sun Ke to drink with him while crossing the Thunderstorm Sea, and it just so happened to have been the case that this was one of the wines that he had drunk with Sun Ke.

However, drinking the wine back then hadn't inspired any of these revelations in his heart.

"This is fantastic! I took a liking to you as soon as I saw you, but I didn't think you would be an avid wine enthusiast as well! Come, let's have a few more drinks!"

Elder Hu Yan was ecstatic, and he stood up from his reclining chair before returning to the room.

By the time he re-emerged, he was holding seven or eight different flagons, which he set down onto the table one by one.

The styles of the flagons were all quite varied, as was the case with the accompanying cups.

There was a copper goblet, as well as cups made from jade, wood, stone, gold, and various other types of materials. Furthermore, each cup had some peculiar designs engraved upon them, and these designs appeared to have been runes, rather than purely for decoration.

Han Li was immediately able to tell that every single one of these cups and flagons was a treasure, but he had no idea what effects they had.

A hint of intrigue welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he smiled as he asked, "Why have you brought out so many cups, Elder Hu Yan? Could it be that each type of wine has to be served in its own cup?"

Elder Hu Yan was looking extremely excited, and he eagerly replied, "Of course! A fine steed requires a good saddle, and the same applies to wine. If you don't have the right cup, even the finest wine won't taste as good as it's meant to. For example, this Green Pear Wine must be served in Heavenly Azure Jade cups. Another example is this Red Mulberry Immortal Wine, which must be served using 10,000-year-old green vine cups to maximize its aroma..."

Han Li nodded in response and picked up the cup of Red Mulberry Immortal Wine, which was another type of wine that he had drunk with Sun Ke while crossing the Thunderstorm Sea.

After just a small sip, his eyes instantly lit up.

The Red Mulberry Immortal Wine that he had drunk with Sun Ke had been one of the most precious wines in Sun Ke's collection, so it was definitely of no lesser a quality than this one, but this cup of wine was far more fragrant in comparison.

Han Li took another, and after carefully savoring it for a moment, he quickly realized why this was the case.

As it turned out, the green vine cup was giving off an ancient vine aura that significantly enhanced the aroma of the wine.

"This Red Mulberry Immortal Wine is brewed from 1,000-year-old Red Mulberry Fruit, which is a fire-attribute spirit ingredient, while this green vine cup contains wood-attribute spiritual qi. Wood gives rise to fire, so it naturally enhances the aroma of the wine!" Han Li mused as a hint of admiration appeared in his eyes.

Initially, he had been rather skeptical about Elder Hu Yan's claims, but he now knew that iot really was necessary to pair certain wines with the right cups.

"That's correct. You really do have a knack for wine. Here, have a taste of this Flowing Light Immortal Wine," Elder Hu Yan praised as he picked up a white flagon, then poured out a cup of shimmering amber-colored wine.

Han Li was treated to several types of wine in a row, and all of them were rare and exquisite wines.

He knew very little about wine, but he was a great listener, and his willingness to listen and learn presented a very pleasing sight for Elder Hu Yan.

These wines weren't like ordinary wines in that they were immortal wines that were extremely beneficial for cultivation. Han Li was only at the early-True Immortal Stage, and after drinking so much, his dantian was already filled to the brim with chaotic energies, so it was most likely going to take him a long time to completely digest everything.

With that in mind, he immediately stopped drinking.

Meanwhile, Elder Hu Yan continued to down one cup of wine after another, and it was clear that his cultivation base was significantly superior to Han Li's.

Han Li waited for a short while, but he could see that Elder Hu Yan had no intention of stopping anytime soon, so he interjected, "Could we take a little break, Elder Hu Yan? I have something I would like to report to you."

"You're a real spoilsport, you know that? Fine, spit it out then!" Elder Hu Yan harrumphed in a disgruntled voice as he sat up in his chair.

Han Li gave an apologetic smile as he pulled out a storage treasure before offering it to Elder Hu Yan.

"All of the Fire Origin Crystals excavated from the Fire Cloud Peak over the past decade are in there."

Elder Hu Yan accepted the storage treasure, then examined its contents briefly with his spiritual sense before tossing it aside, following which he pulled out that azure book and scribbled something down onto it.

"It seems like the sect holds these Fire Origin Crystals in very high regard, Elder Hu Yan. May I ask what these crystals are used for? I can tell that they contained immense fire-attribute spiritual qi, but they're very brittle, and I'd say they're more like spirit stones than other types of fire-attribute ore," Han Li said.

"They're a type of fuel used for refining Immortal Origin Stones," Elder Hu Yan replied without even raising his head.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, and he asked, "How are these Fire Origin Crystals used in the refinement of Immortal Origin Stones?"

Elder Hu Yan raised his head to take a puzzled glance at Han Li, then asked, "Are you not aware of the Nine Turns Immortal Origin Array?"

"I haven't heard of it before this," Han Li replied in a truthful manner.

"I see. You must've only recently joined the sect, right? Where do you come from?" Elder Hu Yan asked.

"You are correct, Elder Hu Yan. I've only been in the sect for less than a century, and I came from a secluded island on the Primordial Wave Continent," Han Li replied.

"That makes sense. The Primordial Wave Continent is a very secluded place, so it's no wonder you don't know about these things. The Nine Turns Immortal Origin Array is an extremely renowned array in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and it's capable of fusing 100 top-grade spirit stones into one in a short time to form a single Immortal Origin Stone," Elder Hu Yan explained.

"I see. It's no wonder that Immortal Origin Stones are so rare on the Primordial Wave Continent, yet they seem to be a lot more common in the sect," Han Li mused with an enlightened expression.

"Of course. The Primordial Wave Continent can't even begin to compare with our sect," Elder Hu Yan said in a proud manner.

He flipped a hand over to stow the azure book away as he spoke, then took Han Li's elder badge from him before adding 180 merit points to it.

"Thank you, Elder Hu Yan. Please spare me a bit more of your time and assign me my next mission. It'll only take a short while, and we can get back to drinking after that," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"I finally get some time to slack off, yet here you are, nagging me to no end!"

Elder Hu Yan glared at Han Li with a displeased expression as he spoke, then flipped through a few pages of the mission book before raising his head to look back at Han Li.

"Seeing as you're in such a hurry to complete your three missions, I presume you want to get them done as quickly as possible so you can return to cultivation, right? In that case, I have just the right mission for you. In total, it'll only take several months to complete."

Han Li was very happy to hear this, and he asked, "What's the mission?"

"In order for inner sect disciples to be promoted to direct disciples, they have to pass a trial, and your mission is very simple: you are required to protect some of the inner sect disciples in secret as they undertake the trial," Elder Hu Yan explained.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this. "Protect them in secret?"

"That's right. Those inner sect disciples must pass the trial through their own power, and under normal circumstances, they are to receive no assistance. However, many unforeseen mishaps have taken place during past trials, so it's become a convention to have one or two True Immortal Stage elders accompanying the trial-takers in secret for their safety," Elder Hu Yan explained.

"I see. When does this mission start?" Han Li asked.

"You're in luck, the mission starts in three days. When the time comes, go to the Rising Sun Palace, and someone will notify you of the specific details," Elder Hu Yan replied.

"Thank you, Elder Hu Yan," Han Li said with a grateful look on his face.

Elder Hu Yan had a rather sharp tongue, but he had been quite good to Han Li, and the three missions he had assigned to him had all been relatively easy to complete.

"No need to thank me, just make sure to come over and have a few drinks with me whenever you get some spare time," Elder Hu Yan said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

"I'll be sure to do so," Han Li replied with a smile, then stood up to depart.

As he left the room, he passed by that spirit plant that was laden with yellow beans again, and he couldn't help but stop in his tracks to examine it again.

"Are you familiar with Dao Warriors as well?"

Elder Hu Yan's voice had rung out directly behind Han Li, and Han Li was quite startled by the fact that Elder Hu Yan had gotten so close to him without his detection.

However, he had already composed himself by the time he turned around, and he said, "I only heard about these things by chance in the past. It looks like you're quite an expert in Dao Warriors."

"Of course! If I rank myself as second in terms of Dao Warrior mastery, no one in the Blaze Dragon Dao would dare to claim the top spot!" Elder Hu Yan declared with a hint of pride in his voice.

Han Li was ecstatic to hear this, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "I've always been very interested in Dao Warriors, but it's something that very few people are familiar with, so I've never been able to find someone to teach me. Would it be possible for you to..."

"You want to learn the art of Dao Warriors from me? No, absolutely not! There's no way I'll teach this to you, so don't even think about it," Elder Hu Yan interjected as he shook his head vigorously before Han Li even had a chance to finish his sentence.

"Is there really no room for discussion on this subject, Elder Hu Yan?" Han Li asked.

Elder Hu Yan was just about to turn Han Li down once and for all, but it was clear that he had taken a liking to Han Li after drinking with him, and he said in a meaningful voice, "It's not entirely out of the question. I have two vices in life, one of which is wine, while the other is the art of Dao Warriors. If you can find an immortal wine recipe better than the ones I currently possess, then I could perhaps teach you."

He had scoured the land for countless years for delectable wines and recipes, so he was confident that even in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, there weren't many people who could exceed him in this area.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh at the sight of Elder Hu Yan's confident expression.

He didn't know much about wine, but even he could still tell that Elder Hu Yan was an expert in this area. All of the immortal wines that he had presented to Han Li just now had been extremely rare and delectable, and he had no idea where he was supposed to find better ones.

It seemed that Elder Hu Yan really didn't want to instruct Han Li in the art of Dao Warriors.

"Alright, I'll be sure to do my best, and if I do find something that fits your criteria, I hope you won't go back on your word, Elder Hu Yan," Han Li said.

Even though the chances were extremely slim, he still didn't want to give up. If worse came to worst, he would just have to release a mission in the Transient Guild, and he was sure that he would be able to find something as long as he was willing to pay the price.

"I never go back on my word, so there's no need to try and goad me. If you really can find such an exceptional wine recipe, then I'd be more than willing to impart my knowledge in the art of Dao Warriors upon you," Elder Hu Yan harrumphed.

"In that case, I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said with a faint smile, then cupped his fist in a parting salute before departing.

Chapter 223: Mark

After leaving the Hundred Wine Cottage, Han Li returned straight to the secret chamber of his cave abode, and after activating all of the restrictions inside, he sat down on the spot with his legs crossed.

Having completed two regular elder missions in a row, he was feeling quite weary from his rigorous travels, even though neither mission had been particularly difficult to complete. Now that he had three days to rest, he could digest the immortal wines that had just consumed and also recuperate somewhat.

However, not long after he closed his eyes, he abruptly reopened them again as his expression changed ever so slightly.

The storage bracelet on his wrist had suddenly begun vibrating without any warning.

Before he had a chance to do anything, a streak of black light flashed past, and the black saber flew out on its own, then shot forth into the distance at an incredible speed like a bolt of black lightning.

Due to how abruptly all of this had unfolded, Han Li was unable to immediately stop the saber, but he was able to quickly react before making a hand seal, and layers of azure light instantly appeared within the secret chamber to prevent the saber's escape.

Dazzling black light erupted from the saber, accompanied by what sounded like an animalistic roar, and the black saber was able to slice through the layers of azure light with ease, but it was also slowed down slightly as a result.

Right at this moment, Han Li conjured up his Mantra Treasured Axis amid a flash of golden light, and golden ripples spread through the surrounding area in a radius of 100 feet, encompassing the black saber within.

As a result, the saber was slowed down once again, this time to only a third of its previous speed, immediately following which it was drawn back into Han Li's grasp by a burst of invisible suction force.

The black saber began to vibrate incessantly as it struggled to break free, but it was completely ensnared within Han Li's vice-like grip.

What's going on?

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed upon seeing this.

Fang Pan was already dead, and during all these years in which the black saber had been in his possession, he had already carefully refined it once, so why was this happening?

With that in mind, he injected his enormous spiritual sense into the black saber, and what he saw was not a very pleasing sight.

As it turned out, the black saber had already completely escaped from his control, and there were bursts of invisible force inside that kept out his spiritual sense.

Han Li harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and translucent light flashed from his glabella as a burst of even more tremendous spiritual sense erupted forth in a frenzy, forming a semi-transparent sword projection that was around a foot in length before piercing into the black saber.

The saber projection had been conjured up by Han Li using his Sword Observation Art, and it was able to slice through the bursts of invisible force with ease.

Thus, Han Li was able to force his spiritual sense through the layers of restrictions within the black saber, and his spiritual sense quickly reached a black space that was nestled within the saber's deepest part.

The space was riddled with countless black patterns that varied in thickness, resembling countless cobwebs that formed an enormous and complex array, while a black altar stood at the center of the array.

A ball of warped black light was hovering within the altar, flashing incessantly, and the array patterns around it were also constantly flashing, as if they were resonating with the ball of black light.

Han Li was quite stunned by what he was seeing.

He had meticulously refined the black saber in the past, and his spiritual sense had reached this place before, but at the time, the array patterns here hadn't been anywhere near this complex.

This was most likely the true form of the core restriction within the black saber.

He cast his gaze toward the ball of black light, and it seemed to have detected his gaze as a rather indistinct face appeared within it before looking back at Han Li.

The features of the face were quite blurry, but its eyes were quite clear, and they were thin and long, resembling sharp blades, while giving off an enraged and arrogant gleam.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this.

The face wasn't very clear, but it definitely didn't belong to Fang Pan.

With that in mind, it immediately dawned on him that the owner of the saber wasn't Fang Pan. Instead, he had most likely borrowed it from someone else.

Even though he had meticulously refined the saber, there was no way that he could've detected these concealed restrictions planted within the saber by its original owner.

All of a sudden, Han Li realized the peril that he was in.

The owner of the saber had activated the mark within it most likely to sense its exact location so that he could recover it, and if that person were to track him down, then he would be in a world of trouble.

As soon as these thoughts sprang into Han Li's mind, he immediately conjured up a massive semi-transparent sword projection that lashed out viciously at the ball of black light.

The blurry face let loose an infuriated roar, and it transformed into a length of translucent black chain that was rather similar in appearance to an Origin Separation Law Chain before whipping itself at the sword projection.

A ferocious clash took place, and the black chain was sliced into two by the sword projection before disintegrating into countless specks of black light.

All of the array patterns inside the black space instantly fell dark, and at the same time, the black saber also ceased its struggles, while the light radiating from it faded.

It had become completely still and obedient, and only now did it appear to have been completely refined.

However, Han Li wasn't particularly elated to see this. Instead, he turned his gaze toward the black altar, within which was something that resembled a cross between a rune and a mark, and it was giving off faint spiritual light.

That's a bonded mark!

Han Li immediately conjured up another semi-transparent sword projection above the altar before sending it crashing down onto the mark.

A loud thump rang out, and the sword projection was repelled, while the bonded mark only shuddered slightly before reverting back to its original form, seemingly completely indestructible.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and instead of continuing to unleash more attacks, he withdrew all of his spiritual sense.

Back in the secret chamber, he looked down at the black saber in his hand with an indecisive expression.

Right as Han Li forced his spiritual sense into the black saber and attempted to erase the mark within it, there was a massive black crane that was several thousand feet in size flying through the sky countless kilometers away on the Ancient Cloud Continent.

The crane's entire body was covered in metallic black plumage, but the feathers on the top of its head were golden in color, resembling a crown. Faint black flames could be seen on the surface of its feathers, and these flames were particularly pronounced on its wings, forming two even larger fiery black wings around its actual wings.

The crane was flapping its wings rapidly as it flew at an extraordinary pace, covering a distance of several hundred kilometers with every single flap.

A burly yellow-robed man that was close to 10 feet in height was seated on the black crane's back with his legs crossed.

There were over 100 yellow array flags hovering in the air around him, and they were all giving off bursts of yellow light to form an array that was several hundred feet in size, which was fluctuating in brightness as it slowly revolved on the spot.

He made a hand seal, and countless yellow runes surged out of hands, then circled around momentarily in the air before flowing into the surrounding array, and it seemed that he was unleashing some type of secret technique.

All of a sudden, the yellow array shuddered violently before exploding, and all of the array flags were sent flying in all directions.

The yellow-robed man's face paled slightly, and he opened his eyes as he cursed, "Damn it!"

With a sweep of his sleeve, all of the scattered array flags converged back together before flying into his head, vanishing without a trace.

"Were you able to track him down, Master?" the giant black crane asked in a sharp and piercing voice.

"I almost managed to do it. Having said that, I've determined the rough direction that he's in. What a useless piece of trash that Fang Pan was. Not only did he end up dead, he lost my Black Emperor Immortal Slaying Blade as well!" the yellow-robed man grumbled.

"Fang Pan was nothing more than a fool with mediocre aptitude, how could he possibly compare with you?" the giant crane remarked with a hint of derision in its voice.

"In any case, the Black Emperor Immortal Slaying Blade is my bonded immortal treasure, and I can't afford to lose it. If I had known this would happen, I would've never lent it to Fang Pan," the yellow-robed man grumbled with a frustrated expression.

"Speaking of which, that Han Li sure is a lucky fellow. Not only did he not die 300 years ago, he's managed to kill Fang Pan now. Having said that, now that you're going after him, it seems like his good fortune has come to an end," the black crane said in a sycophantic manner.

"I don't know what secret this Han Li is harboring that made Fang Pan so determined to hunt him down. I have to say, I'm extremely curious! I have to make sure that old fart doesn't find out. Otherwise, I won't get to claim his secrets for myself," the yellow-robed man said in a cold voice, and an enormous aura began to emanate from his body, causing his robes to bulge around him.

The nearby air began to buzz and tremble as a string of loud cracks and pops rang out.

The giant black crane couldn't help but shudder slightly in the face of the yellow-robed man's terrifying aura, and it lowered its head as it sped up a little more.

……

After staring at the black saber in his hand for a while, Han Li suddenly set it down before making a rapid string of hand seals.

Dazzling azure light instantly erupted from his hands, forming a series of large azure runes that descended onto the black saber.

A series of azure runes instantly appeared on the surface of the saber, and these runes were only increasing in number, spreading over the entire saber in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, the black saber had transformed into an azure saber that wasn't giving off even the slightest aura.

This was a treasure sealing technique that Han Li had learned in the past, and after unleashing the technique, he pulled out a long black box, which was clearly a treasure as well.

The surface of the box was flashing with spiritual light, and it was giving off a peculiar aura.

He placed the black saber into the box, then flipped a hand over to produce several talismans, all of which he also plastered onto the box.

His brows were slightly furrowed as he looked down at the black box in his hand.

Even after casting so many seals onto the saber, he still wasn't confident that its former owner would be completely unable to sense it.

Hence, as long as this saber remained by his side, there was always the risk that its former owner could track him down.

He didn't know what type of relationship Fang Pan shared with the saber's former owner, but they were both definitely enemies to him.

It seemed that the owner of the saber had to have used some type of special refinement method to have planted such a resolute seal within the saber.

By Han Li's own estimates, given his current level of power, if he wanted to completely erase the seal, then the only way to do so would be to slowly refine it using his nascent flame, and that would take him at least a century.

This was far too much time to waste on a single weapon, and he was at a slight loss for what to do.

Chapter 224: Passing the Trouble Onto Someone Else

After pondering the issue for a long time, Han Li finally arrived at a decision.

This saber is nothing but trouble, so as opposed to wasting the time it would take to refine it, it would be better for me to sell it.

The saber was indeed quite powerful, but his own safety was naturally far more important in comparison.

After making up his mind, Han Li didn't waste any time as he flipped his hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask, which he promptly put on.

A massive azure array projection soon appeared, and Han Li turned his gaze to the trade section before releasing a trade mission.

There were two ways to sell things in the Transient Guild, one of which was to only display images of the item being sold in a mission and setting out one's intentions. If someone were interested in the item, then the two parties could negotiate a price.

The second method was to list a set price that was non-negotiable.

Han Li chose the second option without any hesitation, listing the saber at a price of 50 Immortal Origin Stones.

Given the power and caliber of the saber, this was definitely a favorable price for prospective buyers.

In this current situation, all he wanted was to sell the saber as soon as possible to rid himself of this trouble, and he didn't conceal the fact that the bonded mark of the saber's previous owner still remained within it.

There were many pieces of stolen goods being sold in the Transient Guild, so this wasn't something that was frowned upon. In the world of cultivation, people were constantly stealing treasures from others, so the buyers in the Transient Guild didn't care where the items that they purchased had come from.

This was most likely why so many people were willing to pay a heavy price to join the Transient Guild.

Han Li placed the wooden box onto the teleportation array at the center of the array projection, and it instantly vanished amid a flash of light.

Han Li naturally didn't want to give up such a powerful treasure, but at the same time, it was a relief to do so.

He was just about to remove his mask when a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he released another mission searching for recipes for immortal wines.

Elder Hu Yan had countless fine wines in his Hundred Wine Cottage, so it wasn't going to be an easy task finding one that wasn't in his extensive collection, but Han Li was still eager to try his luck.

After that, he removed his mask and heaved a faint sight of relief.

He was feeling a little weary after that rather tense sequence of events, and he closed his eyes as a layer of faint azure light appeared over his body.

Two days flew by in a flash, and by the time Han Li reopened his eyes, he was completely reinvigorated.

He immediately pulled out his Transient Guild mask before putting it on, and sure enough, the black saber had already been sold.

"Thank heavens for that," Han Li murmured to himself as he counted the 50 Immortal Origin Stones in his hands.

As for whether the buyer of the saber was going to be pursued by its original owner, that wasn't something for Han Li to be worried about.

After all, clinching such a powerful Acquired Immortal Treasure for only 50 Immortal Origin Stones was a massive steal, so they had to pay an additional price elsewhere.

Even though the saber had been sold, the mission that he had released requesting wine recipes hadn't received any responses.

Han Li didn't have very high hopes for the mission anyway, so he immediately stowed the mask away before leaving his secret chamber.

It was only first light, and the sun had just begun to rise in the east, basking the earth in a warm golden glow.

A layer of golden radiance had appeared over the snow-covered Bell Toll Mountain Range, giving a far more dazzling and beautiful appearance than usual.

Han Li took a deep breath, feeling further reinvigorated by the cold air.

This was already the third day, and it was time that he went to the Rising Sun Palace.

Even though there wasn't supposed to have been any danger associated with this mission, given his careful and cautious nature, he still made sure to sort through all of his pills and belongings, making sure that he had everything that he might need before departing from the Crimson Dawn Peak.

Close to half a day later, Han Li emerged from a teleportation hall, then flew away in a certain direction as a streak of azure light, arriving at a golden palace shortly thereafter.

The palace was over 100 feet tall and extremely majestic to behold. On either side of the palace gates was a sun diagram, and a plaque was hanging above the gate with the words "Rising Sun Palace" inscribed upon it.

At this point, there were already quite a few people in the palace. Judging from their attire, they seemed to have all been inner court disciples, and all of them appeared to have been waiting for something.

Right as Han Li was hesitating about whether to go in, a square-faced young man in an attendant's robe approached Han Li from one side of the gate, then cupped his fist in a salute as he asked, "You must be Elder Li, right?"

Han Li nodded in response.

"My name is Fang Yu, and I'm an attendant here at the Rising Sun Palace. Please come with me, Elder Li," the square-faced young man said with a smile, then made his way toward a side door in the Rising Sun Palace.

Han Li followed along, and the two of them made their way into a side hall with only nothing more than a set of tables and chairs inside.

A middle-aged man in a scholarly robe was seated in the room, and his head was lowered as he savored the cup of spirit tea in his hand.

The man raised his head upon hearing the sound of footsteps, and Han Li faltered slightly at the sight of him, then cupped his fist in a salute as he greeted, "Long time no see, Brother Su."

The scholarly-robed man was one of the non-native elders that had undertaken Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's sword refinement mission alongside Han Li, and the two of them were on friendly terms.

"Indeed, Brother Li. I heard that you've been cultivating in seclusion this entire time. When did you come out of seclusion?" Su Tongxiao asked with a wide smile as he set down his teacup before leading Han Li to his chair in a hospitable manner.

Meanwhile, the square-faced young man had already prepared a cup of spirit tea for Han Li as well.

"I've been out of seclusion for a while now," Han Li replied with a smile. "Have you also taken on the mission to protect the inner court disciples during their promotion trial?"

"I have. I'm very short on funds at the moment, so I have to do more missions to earn some merit points," Su Tongxiao replied with a wry smile.

Han Li nodded in response, following which he seemed to have made an unexpected observation, and a hint of surprise appeared in his eyes as he cupped his fist in a salute and said, "It appears that you've already opened 12 immortal acupoints! This is truly worthy of celebration, Brother Su!"

There were quite a few True Immortal cultivators in the sect, but the majority of them were at the early-True Immortal Stage. Mid-True Immortal cultivators were quite rare, and as for late-True Immortal cultivators, there were barely any aside from the deputy dao lords.

"I was stuck at the early-True Immortal Stage for many years, and it was only just over 10 years ago that I finally managed to make a breakthrough. However, in order to do so, I had to spend virtually all of my merit points, and that's why I had to take on this mission," Su Tongxiao replied, and he was trying to put on a calm facade, but there was an undeniable hint of excitement in his eyes.

"If I can make the same breakthrough, I'd be willing to give up everything in my possession, let alone just some merit points. I must say, I'm extremely envious, Brother Su," Han Li chuckled.

The flattery in Han Li's words was inflating Su Tongxiao's ego, and he couldn't help but burst into laughter as he replied, "Surely you jest, Brother Li. I see that you've also made quite some progress in your cultivation base during these past few decades of seclusion."

The square-faced young man had been standing off to the side this entire time, and he interjected, "Please wait here for a moment, esteemed elders. The trial mission won't commence for some time, and when that time comes, someone will inform you of the specific details of the mission."

"I see. I'm sure you're quite busy, so you can go now," Su Tongxiao said with a wave of his hand.

The square-faced young man extended a salute toward the two elders before departing.

"Do you know him, Brother Su?" Han Li asked as he picked up his teacup before taking a sip.

The tea was very rich and fragrant, and its aroma lingered in the mouth for a long time even after it had already been swallowed, indicating that it was an exceptional tea.

"I've taken on this mission several times in the past, so I've met him a few times," Su Tongxiao explained.

"I see. In that case, I'll have to learn from you, Brother Su. This mission doesn't seem like much, but I can't shake the feeling that it's not as simple as it appears on the surface," Han Li said as he set down his teacup.

"That's well-observed of you, Brother Li. Indeed, there's more to this mission than meets the eye. Take a look at the inner court disciples in the main hall."

Su Tongxiao flicked a finger through the air as he spoke, releasing a streak of blue light that landed on one of the walls of the side hall.

A layer of gentle blue light instantly appeared over the wall, which gradually turned transparent.

On the other side of the wall was the main hall, and they were able to see everything inside, but what was quite interesting was that no one in the main hall seemed to have noticed the change in the wall.

"Your control over your water-attribute abilities is still as immaculate as ever, Brother Su," Han Li praised as he raised an eyebrow.

"You're far too kind, Brother Li," Su Tongxiao replied with a pleased smile.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the inner court disciples in the main hall, and they all appeared to have been quite young.

It was clear that they possessed exceptional aptitude, and all of them had reached the Spatial Tempering Stage.

Even though the age of a cultivator couldn't be determined solely based on their physical appearance, Han Li was able to tell at a glance that none of the cultivators in the hall were over 1,000 years of age.

Even in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, it was extremely rare for someone to reach the Spatial Tempering Stage at such a young age, and it was apparent from this that these disciples most likely had enormous support in terms of resources to complement their outstanding aptitudes.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed a beautiful young woman in a white dress. The woman was none other than Bai Suyuan, and he had only taken a rough glance at the disciples earlier, so he had failed to notice her.

Her appearance hadn't changed much at all, but she had already reached the mid-Spatial Tempering Stage. It seemed that she had only recently made the breakthrough, but that was still an astonishing rate of progress.

Then again, it wasn't all that remarkable once one considered that she possessed the Moonlight Immortal Physique with seven innately awakened immortal acupoints, in addition to the guidance of a Golden Immortal Stage master and an endless supply of pills from the sect.

"As I'm sure you can tell, all of these disciples possess outstanding aptitude. Furthermore, most of them are the descendants of various elders and even deputy dao lords of the sect," Su Tongxiao said in a meaningful voice.

Han Li merely nodded in response, and it was impossible to tell what he was thinking.

All of the inner court disciples in the main hall carried an air of superiority, and they were all quite relaxed, even though they were standing in the prestigious Rising Sun Palace. Furthermore, their bodies were all glowing faintly with spiritual light, clearly indicating that they were carrying exceptional protective spirit treasures.

However, this wasn't the case for all of the disciples. Instead, there were four or five of them standing near the edge of the hall in silence, and their bodies weren't radiating spiritual light, either, making them appear rather shabby in comparison.

"Direct disciples will either become disciples to the 13 Golden Immortal Stage Dao Lords, or to the deputy dao lords. Not only do they have to be at least at the Spatial Tempering Stage, they must complete this final trial to be officially granted such a status.

“These disciples are considered to be the cream of the crop, and they'll receive unreserved support from the sect in all areas, including cultivation arts, pills, resources, and territories. The benefits that direct disciples receive far exceed those of the average inner court disciples.

“Otherwise, there's no way those elders and deputy dao lords would allow their precious descendants to undertake this trial," Su Tongxiao continued, and there was a hint of mockery in his voice.

"What is the purpose of this trial, Brother Su?" Han Li asked.

"You see, all of these disciples possess exceptional aptitude, and they've been cultivating arduously for centuries, but they're lacking experience in true life-and-death situations, and that's where this trial comes in," Su Tongxiao explained.

Han Li nodded in response, then turned his gaze back to Bai Suyuan as a hint of befuddlement flashed through his eyes.

Su Tongxiao quickly noticed the object of Han Li's attention, and he asked, "That woman is Bai Suyuan. Do you know her, Brother Li?"

Chapter 225: Meeting Sun Ke Again

"She's an acquaintance of mine. She and I joined the Blaze Dragon Dao at the same time. It sounds like you know of her as well, Brother Su," Han Li replied with a nod.

Bai Suyuan's exceptional aptitude had seen her catch the eye of the dao lord with the Yun surname as soon as she joined the sect, but ever since then, she had kept quite a low profile, so there shouldn't have been that many people who knew of her.

"I took on a mission released by Dao Lord Yun some years ago, and I just so happened to meet her then. Apparently, she possesses the Moonlight Immortal Physique, and she's reached her current cultivation base after no more than a century of cultivation. I'm sure it won't be long before she forges a resounding reputation for herself in the entire sect," Su Tongxiao remarked.

"Bai Suyuan has been accepted as Dao Lord Yun's disciple, so that already makes her a direct disciple, right? In that case, why is she participating in this trial?" Han Li asked with a befuddled expression.

"She may already be a direct disciple, but the rules of the sect have to be followed. Prior to this, she's been in seclusion this entire time, but now that she's reached the Spatial Tempering Stage, she must also pass this trial in order to officially become a direct disciple," Su Tongxiao explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a contemplative expression.

Right at this moment, a slightly portly young man strode into the Rising Sun Palace. He was wearing an inner court disciple robe, and he also seemed to have been one of the trial-takers.

Han Li took a casual glance at this newcomer, and a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

The newcomer was none other than Sun Ke, together with whom Han Li had traveled to the Ancient Cloud Continent. Somehow, he had managed to join the Blaze Dragon Dao and earned the right to participate in this trial during the few decades since then.

As soon as he stepped into the hall, all of the other disciples instantly turned to him as well.

He seemed to have been rather uncomfortable from all the scrutiny, and he paused momentarily in his footsteps before flashing everyone a smile.

All of the inner court disciples gazed upon Sun Ke with hints of derision in their eyes for a moment before quickly returning to their conversations, and Bai Suyuan was the only one who returned his smile.

Sun Ke didn't seem to have been surprised by this rather frosty reception, and he made his way over to a corner of the main hall on his own, where he began to inspect his surroundings and all of the other disciples.

The disciples in the hall had split themselves up into three distinct circles, with the largest one containing eight or nine people, which was close to half of all of the disciples present. At the center of the circle was a handsome brocade-robed young man with a purple mark on his glabella that was giving off a purple glow, and his cultivation base was at the late-Spatial Tempering Stage.

Standing nearby was a group of five or six people, gathered around another handsome young man with a slightly dark complexion.

However, his eyes were rather long and thin, and he was giving off a rather effeminate aura.

The dark-skinned young man was also at the late-Spatial Tempering Stage, and these two circles of disciples were the most relaxed of the bunch, chatting amicably with one another, seemingly without a care in the world.

The final circle was the one that Bai Suyuan was in. She was surrounded by several female cultivators who were also quite gorgeous, but paled in comparison to her stunning beauty.

Bai Suyuan's eyes were slightly downcast as she remained silent, and her entire body was giving off a faint white glow, giving her the appearance of a silently blooming snow lotus flower.

In contrast with her silence, the female cultivators around her were chatting quietly among themselves as they inspected their surroundings.

While conversing with those around them, both the brocade-robed young man and the dark-skinned young man were shooting occasional glances at Bai Suyuan with a hint of lust and desire in their eyes.

As for the rest of the disciples, they were all standing in silence around the hall like Sun Ke.

A short while later, the brocade-robed young man took one more glance at Bai Suyuan, then cleared his throat before approaching her.

"You must be Junior Martial Sister Bai Suyuan, right? My name is Qi Huanyu. It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance. I've heard a lot about you, including the fact that you're a secret disciple of Dao Lord Yun's, but unfortunately, I never had the chance to meet you before this," Qi Huanyu said with a polite smile.

"You're far too kind, Senior Martial Brother Qi. As a descendant to Deputy Dao Lord Qi, your outstanding aptitude is known to everyone in the sect, and I've heard that you're the leading figure among all inner court disciples," Bai Suyuan replied with a faint smile.

Qi Huanyu faltered slightly upon hearing this. He was indeed quite a renowned figure, but no one had ever referred to him as the leading figure among all inner court disciples before. Could it be that this title had been bestowed upon him without his knowledge?

In any case, he was certainly more than happy to play along, and he made no effort to deny the title as he chuckled, "You're far too kind, Junior Martial Sister Bai. Such an arbitrary title is not one to be taken seriously. Given your exceptional aptitude, I'm sure it won't be long before you surpass me."

Right at this moment, the dark-skinned young man approached them with a cold sneer on his face as he scoffed, "Leading figure? When did you receive such a title, Qi Huanyu? How come I've never heard anyone mention it? Could it be that you gave yourself that title?"

A cold look appeared on Qi Huanyu's face as he glared at the dark-skinned young man, then turned back to Bai Suyuan as he introduced, "You've probably never heard of him, but his name is Tang Chuan, and he's also an inner court disciple."

The dark-skinned young man's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, yet before he could issue a retort, Bai Suyuan said, "How could I possibly not have heard of Senior Martial Brother Tang? Senior Martial Brother Tang is the only son to Elder Jing Ming of the Heavenly Pill Palace, and your mastery of the Profound Spirit Walking Arts is unmatched. Please teach me some time, Senior Martial Brother Tang."

There was a hint of seduction in Bai Suyuan's smile as she spoke, and the anger in Tang Chuan's heart at Qi Huanyu's snide remarks instantly faded as he hurriedly replied, "You're far too kind, Junior Martial Sister Bai. Truth be told, I've only just begun to make my initial forays into the Profound Spirit Walking Arts, and..."

Qi Huanyu was very displeased to have been suddenly shut out of the conversation, and he sneered, "It would be an extremely unwise use of your time to learn a cultivation art as mediocre as the Profound Spirit Walking Arts, Junior Martial Sister Bai."

"How dare you look down on the Profound Spirit Walking Arts! I'm going to make you eat your words!"

Tang Chuan immediately flared up with rage as wisps of black mist rose up from his body alongside a layer of faint black light.

Qi Huanyu was completely unfazed, and the mark on his glabella began to glow with purple radiance.

The disciples around them also began to glower at one another, and all of a sudden, the atmosphere in the hall had become extremely tense.

A faint smile appeared on Bai Suyuan's face, and she took a couple of steps backward in a subtle manner, opening up some space for Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan.

All of a sudden, an authoritative voice rang out within the hall. "Insolence! You're here to participate in a trial, not to fight among yourselves!"

At the same time, a burst of invisible pressure descended upon the entire palace, and everyone in the two opposing groups, including Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan, were instantly rooted to the spot. Even Bai Suyuan was somewhat affected, and a faint unnatural flush had appeared on her face.

The burst of pressure only encompassed the palace for an instant before fading, and everyone was able to move as normal again.

However, the tense atmosphere in the hall had completely faded due to this intervention.

The square-faced young man by the name of Fang Yu appeared amid a flash of white light, and he was making no effort to disguise his Grand Ascension Stage aura, causing the surrounding air to buzz and tremble incessantly.

He swept his gaze over Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan, then gave Bai Suyuan a meaningful look before withdrawing his gaze.

Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan exchanged a final cold glare, then turned and went their separate ways.

Bai Suyuan had also backed away to the side with her head slightly lowered.

"Alright, now that everyone's here, we can commence the trial. Before we begin, I'm going to tell you what you need to do during the trial. I'm only going to say this once, so listen carefully. I am not exaggerating when I say that successful completion of the trial is a matter of life or death for all of you!" Fang Yu declared, administering no further punishment to Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan.

Sun Ke and everyone else who was standing around the hall also gathered around Fang Yu to hear what he had to say.

"You will be undertaking your trial in the Profound Ice Mountain Range. I'll take you to the outskirts of the mountain range, and in order to complete the trial, you're required to venture into the mountain range and slay a Body Integration Stage Dark Snow Bear. You can choose to work with others or slay the bear yourself..."

……

Meanwhile, in the side hall, Han Li was watching everything unfolding in the main hall with a hint of exasperation in his eyes.

Even after so many years, Bai Suyuan was still just as mischievous as ever.

He also noticed that she seemed to have begun using the same cultivation art as Dao Lord Yun. The seductive techniques that she had just displayed were extremely advanced, and the two young men had completely fallen prey to them without their detection.

Thinking back, even with his enormous spiritual sense, he had almost fallen for Dao Lord Yun's seduction, so it was no surprise that those two prodigies had fallen prey to Bai Suyuan's allure.

Just like the inner court disciples, he was also listening carefully as Fang Yu introduced the content of the trial.

"The Profound Ice Mountain Range, eh? That's not far away," Su Tongxiao murmured to himself.

Han Li nodded in response.

At this point, he had already somewhat familiarized himself with the geography of the Ancient Cloud Continent, and indeed, the Profound Ice Mountain Range wasn't very far away, situated northward of the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

Furthermore, the Profound Ice Mountain Range wasn't particularly large. There were supposed to have been many demon beasts lurking within it, but even so, it shouldn't have been very difficult for a pair of True Immortals like them to protect these inner sect disciples.

All of a sudden, Han Li raised his head and cast his gaze toward the entrance of the side hall.

Almost at the exact same moment, two figures appeared there amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

One of them was a purple-robed middle-aged man with a square face and a pair of bright eyes under a set of thin eyebrows. He had an elegant and refined demeanor, but still cut an authoritative figure.

Beside him was an incredibly seductive young woman in a white robe, and it was none other than Dao Lord Yun, Bai Suyuan's mistress.

The two of them were giving off enormous auras, with the purple-robed middle-aged man's aura slightly superior to that of Dao Lord Yun.

"Dao Lord Ouyang! Dao Lord Yun!" Su Tongxiao hurriedly rose to his feet before cupping hi fist in a salute.

Han Li also hurriedly stood up before extending a salute of his own.

"You two are the ones assigned with protecting the trial-takers in secret, is that correct?" Dao Lord Ouyang asked.

"That's right," Han Li and Su Tongxiao replied in unison.

"I'm sure you've already been made aware of the contents of the trial. During this trial, your mission will be to deal with any unforeseen mishaps that may arise. Aside from that, these disciples are to take on the perils that arise under normal circumstances on their own, and if they're unable to do so, then it's fine to allow them to perish during the trial.

“The sect has no need for incompetent disciples, so if they can't even survive a trial like this, then it would be better for them to die within the sect than elsewhere," Dao Lord Ouyang said in an implacable voice.

Su Tongxiao hesitated for a moment, then asked, "Dao Lord Ouyang, would you be able to elaborate on what you mean by perils that arise under normal circumstances?"

Chapter 226: Immortals and Mortals

"The two of you can exercise your own discretion in this regard. As long as you think it's something that they can handle, then do not intervene. There's no need to go into this with any psychological burdens.

“Disciples have always had to put their lives on the line during these trials, so even if some of them end up dead, no one would dare to blame the two of you. You two act as both their guardian and their examination overseers, so you have to ensure fairness above all else, understood?"

"Yes," Su Tongxiao and Han Li hurriedly replied.

Dao Lord Ouyang gave Han Li's duo a nod, then turned his gaze to Dao Lord Yun, who looked directly back at him.

Dao Lord Ouyang didn't say anything further before turning around and flying away as a streak of light, while Dao Lord Yun swept her gaze over Han Li and Su Tongxiao.

In the end, her gaze lingered on Han Li for a moment, but in the next instant, she also flew away into the distance.

In the instant that Dao Lord Yun turned around, a peculiar look appeared in Han Li's eyes, only to instantly fade a moment later.

Only after the two dao lords had vanished into the distance did Han Li and Su Tongxiao raise their heads before exchanging a glance.

"Brother Su, was that the ninth-ranked dao lord, Ouyang Kuishan just now?" Han Li asked.

"Precisely. The 13 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords are on a rotating roster, with each dao lord serving as the sect master for 100,000 years before the next dao lord takes over, and Dao Lord Ouyang is the incumbent sect master at the moment. I just didn't think that Dao Lord Yun would accompany him and depart without saying anything. It seems like she's quite concerned for that precious disciple of hers," Su Tongxiao replied with a nod.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the main hall as he said, "Looks like they're about to set off. We should prepare for departure as well."

Sure enough, the inner court disciples there were already departing from the palace, led by Fang Yu.

"There's no need to hurry, Brother Li. Let them go on their own for now, and we'll catch up a bit later," Su Tongxiao replied with a wave of his hand.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a gray-haired elderly man suddenly appeared in the side hall without any warning, and judging from his attire, he was also an inner sect elder.

The elderly man took a glance at Han Li and Su Tongxiao, then quickly settled his gaze on the latter before approaching him with a warm smile.

"Long time no see, Elder Su."

"It's always a pleasure, Elder Wang," Su Tongxiao replied with a warm smile of his own.

A thought occurred to Han Li upon seeing this, and he immediately closed his eyes, pretending to meditate.

The gray-haired elderly man didn't stay for very long, only making some brief small talk before departing, and Su Tongxiao accompanied him to the entrance of the side hall.

Right as he was about to depart, the gray-haired elderly man stuffed a storage pouch into Su Tongxiao's hands in a subtle manner, and Su Tongxiao stowed the storage pouch away without even looking at him.

As soon as the elderly man departed, a middle-aged man who also appeared to have been an inner sect elder made his way into the side hall.

The middle-aged man swept his spiritual sense over the pair of elders in the room, then automatically ignored Han Li as he cupped his fist toward Su Tongxiao with a wide smile. "I knew you'd be the one taking on this mission, Elder Su!"

"Welcome, Elder Fan," Su Tongxiao replied with a smile.

The middle-aged man didn't waste time with small talk at all before handing a storage pouch straight to Su Tongxiao.

As it turned out, this was far from the end of the visitors. It didn't take long before seven or eight groups of people had visited the side hall, and all of them had come to bribe Su Tongxiao before quickly departing.

It was clear to Han Li that these were all seniors of the disciples undertaking the trials, and these gifts had been bestowed upon Su Tongxiao so that he would look at the disciples that were connected to them.

However, Han Li was a completely unfamiliar figure to them, and he was only at the early-True Immortal Stage, so these gifts were naturally all presented to Su Tongxiao, who accepted them without any discretion.

Meanwhile, Han Li sat off to the side in silence this entire time, but internally, he was pondering what Dao Lord Yun had said to him through voice transmission right before her departure.

Dao Lord Yun had asked him to protect Bai Suyuan at all costs, and it seemed that she hadn't made the same request to Su Tongxiao, despite the fact that his cultivation base was superior, and that was rather peculiar in Han Li's eyes.

After waiting for a while without any more visitors, Su Tongxiao called out to Han Li, "It's about time, Brother Li. Let's set off."

Han Li opened his eyes and nodded in response. "Sure."

……

Atop a massive mountain in the northern region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range was a huge bluestone hall.

This was the northernmost teleportation hall of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Frosty winds that were carrying countless snowflakes were howling through the air outside the hall, and the temperature was much lower than it was elsewhere.

After emerging from the hall, Han Li and Su Tongxiao immediately flew toward the north without any delay.

After flying for close to an hour, the two of them began to slow down.

Tens of thousands of kilometers away, a giant flying boat was racing through the clouds.

"From here, all we have to do is follow along at a leisurely pace. By the way, if you and Bai Suyuan joined the sect at the same time, then it's only been less than a century since you came to our sect, right? What do you think of it?" Su Tongxiao asked as he turned to Han Li with a smile.

"The sect certainly has a vast wealth of cultivation arts and resources, but they're not exactly the most accessible to people like us," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Indeed, Brother Li. For itinerant elders like us with no powerful connections or backers in the sect, it's difficult to advance in our cultivation. The funds that we receive upon joining the sect are extremely meager, and we have to rely on ourselves for everything else.

“At this level, even mountains of gold and silver can be easily exhausted to make any progress. Otherwise, I wouldn't have only made this breakthrough after more than 100,000 years in the sect," Su Tongxiao said with a self-deprecating smile.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this. "We're supposed to have received funds upon joining the sect?"

"Yes, you were supposed to have received 500 top-grade spirit stones and three Immortal Origin Stones. May I ask who your guide was when you first joined the sect?" Su Tongxiao asked.

"It was Qi Liang," Han Li replied.

Su Tongxiao gave Han Li a meaningful look upon hearing this, but didn't say anything.

However, it was already very apparent what he was implying. Essentially, he was telling Han Li that this initial care package had been taken by Qi Liang.

Han Li feigned an enraged expression upon hearing this, but internally, he wasn't actually all that bothered by this.

This was most likely standard practice in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and he had always been a little wary about why Qi Liang had been so friendly to him, so he was actually rather relieved to have finally found an explanation.

Thinking back to all the bribes that Su Tongxiao had just accepted, Han Li was left feeling a little speechless.

It seemed that the rules were largely the same regardless of whether it was in the Mortal Realm, the Spirit Realm, or the Immortal Realm, and in many ways, these True Immortals were just like mortals.

All of a sudden, a thought seemed to have occurred to Su Tongxiao, and he asked, "By the way, do you still recall Deputy Dao Lord Xiong's failed sword refinement from some years ago?"

"Didn't Deputy Dao Lord Xiong warn us not to speak of this to anyone? I think it's best that we don't discuss this," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"It's fine! The two of us are the only ones here anyway. Besides, even if we don't speak of this to anyone else, which elder in the inner sect doesn't know about what happened? It's already as open as an open secret can be," Su Tongxiao replied with a nonchalant smile.

Han Li merely smiled in response and didn't say anything.

"Apparently, in order to set up the sword array, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong borrowed a large sum of Immortal Origin Stones from Elder Mo Xie of the Immortal Origin Palace. He still hasn't repaid Elder Mo Xie, and a few days ago, Elder Mo Xie visited Deputy Dao Lord Xiong, demanding that he repaid his debt. The two of them almost got into a physical altercation over this, and it turned into quite an embarrassing spectacle..."

Su Tongxiao seemed to have been quite interested in the latest gossip in the sect, and he told Han Li about a bunch of different things.

Han Li didn't have much interest in engaging in the gossip, but there was nothing better to do anyway, so he intentionally guided the conversation to subjects that he was interested in hearing about. He had only joined the sect not long ago, and he had no intention of being swept up in any conflicts.

As a result, the two were chatting non-stop like a pair of good friends that hadn't met in many years.

As the giant flying boat continued to progress northward, the temperature was dropping further and further. Along the way, they even encountered several snowstorms. Han Li had been busy cultivating in seclusion all this time, so this was the first time that he had had an opportunity to appreciate the scenery of the snow-covered forest.

Close to a month passed by in the blink of an eye, and the flying boat that was carrying Bai Suyuan and the other inner court disciples finally drew to a halt in front of a mountain range that was situated northward of the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

This was the trial venue, the Profound Ice Mountain Range.

This was the third-largest branch of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, and it extended over a vast distance from south to north.

The trees here were extremely tall with dense canopies, and their leaves were all in needle form. These trees were extremely resistant to the cold and were one of the few types of plants that could grow in this mountain range, resembling a series of pointy white spires under the blankets of white snow.

At this point, Bai Suyuan and the other inner sect disciples had already gotten down from their flying boat on a spacious plot of land in the southern part of the mountain range.

Fang Yu stowed the flying boat away, then declared, "Alright, this is as far as I'll be taking you. All of you have a map of this place, and there are three paths that you can take into the mountain range. That will be up to your own discretion, all you have to do is complete your mission. I'll be waiting here in a month for your return."

After that, he flew onto the peak of a small mountain, then sat down with his legs crossed and his eyes closed, leaving the inner sect disciples to their own devices.

Before long, the two dozen or so disciples had gathered together in small groups.

There were several people gathered around each of Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan, and it seemed that they had already made plans to travel together.

Meanwhile, Bai Suyuan and the other female cultivators had already split up to join their groups, and it was clear that they had also decided on this in advance.

That left Sun Ke and the other itinerant cultivators to gather together to form a third group.

Qi Huanyu took a glance at Bai Suyuan, who was inspecting the map on her own, and he immediately detached himself from the group to approach her.

"We've already selected the Snow Camel Mountain Route, Junior Martial Sister Bai. It's a relatively dangerous route, but it's closest to the center of the mountain range, where Dark Snow Bears are most active.

“On top of that, we should be reaping some additional rewards along the way. Why don't you come with us so we can all look after one another during the trial?" Qi Huanyu offered with a hopeful look in his eyes.

Chapter 227: Three Routes

"I've also considered the Snow Camel Mountain route, and even though it's quite short, it's several times more likely to encounter powerful demon beasts on this route than the other two routes, so it really is quite dangerous," Bai Suyuan said as her brows furrowed slightly.

"Rest assured, Junior Martial Sister Bai. With me by your side, you won't be in any danger!" Qi Huanyu hurriedly guaranteed as he gave himself a pat on the chest.

Before Bai Suyuan had a chance to reply, they were approached by Tang Chuan, who scoffed with a disdainful expression, "You sure like to make bold promises that you can't keep, Young Master Qi! You think you have what it takes to ensure Junior Martial Sister Bai's safety?"

"Don't say that, Senior Martial Brother Tang. Senior Martial Brother Qi is only looking out for me," Bai Suyuan said with a smile.

A hint of warmth instantly welled up in Qi Huanyu's heart upon hearing this, and he turned to Tang Chuan with a cold expression as he retorted, "What does this have to do with you? Leave us alone!"

Tang Chuan paid no heed to Qi Huanyu as he said, "Junior Martial Sister Bai, Junior Martial Brother Chen and I are planning to take the White Fox Valley route. The rewards reaped along the way won't be any lesser than the Snow Camel Mountain route, and it'll be a bit safer. Our ultimate goal is to hunt down Dark Snow Bears, so there's no need to take any unnecessary risks along the way. Why don't you come with us, Junior Martial Sister Bai?"

A hesitant look appeared on Bai Suyuan's face upon hearing this.

Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan were just about to say something further when she suddenly decided, "I'll take the Pine Fruit Mountain route with Senior Martial Brother Sun Ke and the others."

Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan both faltered slightly upon hearing this, and Sun Ke and the others were also quite taken aback by this decision.

The itinerant immortals accompanying Sun Ke were very pleased to see this. There weren't many female cultivators on this trip, and the vast majority of them had chosen to join Qi Huanyu or Tang Chuan's group on the flying boat, so it was naturally a massively pleasant surprise for them that the most beautiful female cultivator of the bunch had chosen to accompany them.

However, Sun Ke was not so pleased.

All he wanted was to be able to safely complete this trial, and he didn't want to get involved in these conflicts at all. However, seeing as Bai Suyuan had expressly chosen him, he couldn't just ignore her, so he had no choice but to turn in her direction.

At the same time, Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan were also looking back at him with fiery contempt in their eyes, and both of them were considering whether they should change the route that they were taking so that they could accompany Bai Suyuan.

"With my lackluster abilities, I'll only be dragging you two down, so it's best for me to take the safest route. You are among the cream of the crop of all inner sect disciples, and I admire both of you greatly. I can't accompany either of you on this mission, but I'll be cheering for both of you. I'm sure one of you will be able to claim the top spot for this trial," Bai Suyuan said.

The egos of Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan were greatly inflated by Bai Suyuan's glowing praise, and both of them gave up on the idea of changing routes.

Neither of them were looking at Sun Ke anymore, and they exchanged a vicious glare instead, then bade farewell to Bai Suyuan before leading their groups down the two most perilous paths.

Following their departure, Bai Suyuan approached Sun Ke with a bright smile and asked, "You're not opposed to me accompanying you, are you, Senior Martial Brother Sun?"

"Not at all!" Sun Ke replied with a polite smile, and all of the itinerant disciples eagerly welcomed her with open arms as they began to introduce themselves.

Meanwhile, Han Li and Su Tongxiao were hovering in mid-air above a snowy mountain close to 100 kilometers away. Both of them had concealed their auras, and in front of them was a thin screen of water that was depicting Bai Suyuan and the others.

"That Bai Suyuan really is something. The trial has barely started, and she's already managed to goad her two fiercest competitors into going down the most dangerous routes. Her strategy and manipulation are both top-notch," Su Tongxiao praised.

Han Li was already accustomed to Bai Suyuan's wiles, so he wasn't surprised by this at all, and he smiled as he replied, "I would say the foolishness of those two have played a bigger role in this."

"I agree, Brother Li. With such high expectations set on them by Bai Suyuan, those two will be sure to fight tooth and nail over the top spot for the trial," Su Tongxiao chuckled.

Han Li didn't want to dwell on this topic any longer, so he changed the subject. "By the way, I heard that Bai Suyuan has an ancestor who seemed to have been quite an important inner sect elder of our Blaze Dragon Dao. Do you know him, Brother Su?"

"The elder that you're referring to is Elder Bai Fengyi, who disappeared several thousand years ago. He's more familiar with Elder Qi Liang. I don't know him very well, but I did meet him a few times before his disappearance," Su Tongxiao replied with a nod.

"Do you know what happened to Elder Bai?" Han Li asked as an intrigued look appeared on his face.

"There are all types of theories about what happened to him going around in the sect. Some say that he perished while carrying out a mission for the sect, others say that he was killed by certain sworn enemies of his.

“If you ask me, I think he went somewhere to go into seclusion in order to make a breakthrough to the Golden Immortal Stage. Also, according to some obscure sources in the sect, the Origin Soul Lamp left behind by Elder Bai in the sect has never been snuffed out," Su Tongxiao replied.

It seemed to Han Li that there was more to this matter than met the eye, but he didn't ponder the subject any further.

Meanwhile, Bai Suyuan and the others were gradually vanishing out of sight on the screen of water, and Su Tongxiao erased the screen with a sweep of his sleeve as he said, "Let's go, Brother Li. We have to catch up."

Han Li nodded in response, and as opposed to flying beyond this point, they descended into the forest and began to follow Bai Suyuan and the others on foot while keeping tabs on the three groups with their spiritual sense.

After following the disciples for a while, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as if he had detected something, but his expression then quickly returned to normal.

……

Sun Ke's group consisted of six disciples, and they were flying at a low altitude deeper into the Profound Ice Mountain Range over a mountain path with a rather gentle slope.

The area appeared to have been quite peaceful, but there were many demon beasts in the mountain range that were very proficient at concealing themselves in the snow. Hence, anyone who dared to fly along recklessly at a high altitude could easily end up falling prey to those lurking demon beasts.

It seemed that everyone had already been assigned roles in advance, and Sun Ke had been tasked with leading the way.

At this moment, there was a jade bowl treasure hovering above his head, and rays of white light were shining down from the bowl, enveloping his entire body. At the same time, there were four glittering and translucent azure flying daggers slowly revolving around him.

This still didn't seem to have put him at ease, and he was also holding a small yellow shield with a surface that was as smooth as a mirror in his hand.

Behind him, the other four male cultivators had all adopted protective measures as well and were scouring their surroundings with wary expressions.

Bai Suyuan was bringing up the rear with a white jade bracelet in her hand, forming a white halo around her. At the same time, she had also put on a white veil garment that was giving off specks of silver light.

The group was flying ahead in a slow and cautious manner, and they didn't encounter any danger aside from some sneak attacks from a few reckless demon beasts, all of which were easily dealt with.

As they ventured deeper and deeper into the mountain range, the air temperature also plummeted further and further.

A bone-chilling aura was rising up from beneath the earth, and gusts of frosty wind were also sweeping through the air. Even with the Spatial Tempering Stage cultivation bases of Sun Ke and the others, they were beginning to shiver from the cold. Bai Suyuan was still able to ward off the cold relatively well, but everyone else was clearly beginning to struggle.

All of them activated their cultivation arts to keep themselves insulated, but the temperature continued to plummet, and they were beginning to sorely regret not preparing any treasures that enhanced their resistance to cold conditions.

After all, constantly using their cultivation arts to ward off the cold was very taxing on their magic power, which was detrimental to the battles to come, but they had no choice in the matter.

Right at this moment, Sun Ke suddenly stopped in his tracks, then turned around and produced an intricate red wine flagon as he said, "I have some spirit wine here that's brewed using fire-attribute spirit ingredients and can help ward off the cold. Please have some if you'd like."

Everyone exchanged a few hesitant glances upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, Sun Ke flipped a hand over to produce a cup, which he filled with the spirit wine from the flagon.

The wine had a bright red hue, and it was giving off a fiery red glow. It was as if the wine were burning, and the surrounding air temperature was significantly elevated in its presence.

At the same time, a peculiar fragrance was spreading through the air, and even Bai Suyuan's eyes lit up slightly as she was struck by the urge to give the wine a taste.

One of the young men in the group seemed to have been an avid wine enthusiast as well, and he immediately praised, "This is certainly a fine wine!"

"Do you drink as well, Brother Lin? Please give this a taste if you don't mind. It'll be very helpful for warding off the cold," Sun Ke said as he offered the young man his cup.

"Don't mind if I do!" The young man eagerly accepted the cup before downing its contents in one go.

The wine flowed down into his belly, leaving a scorching trail in its wake, then transformed into a burst of fiery heat that enveloped all of his internal organs.

The burst of heat then split up into several bursts that flowed to all parts of his body as if they had a mind of their own, and he was left feeling extremely light and airy, as if he were about to drift away with the wind.

His entire body stiffened as if he had been struck by lightning, following which an intoxicated look appeared on his face, and it took a long while before he returned to his senses, upon which he praised once again, "This wine is exceptional! May I ask its name, Brother Sun?"

"This wine is called Fire Drop Wine," Sun Ke replied with a smile.

"A fitting name for an exceptional wine! I was fortunate enough to have tasted one of the top 10 immortal brews, the Green Pear Immortal Wine, and I'd say its flavor is slightly lacking compared with this Fire Drop Wine," the young man said in an excited manner.

Not only was this wine extremely delectable, just as Sun Ke said, it was very effective in warding off the cold.

At this moment, his entire body felt as if it were being basked under the warm glow of the sun, and a hint of redness had appeared on his cheeks, while all of the biting chill in his body had been expelled.

The other three male cultivators had no further reservations upon seeing this, and each of them had a cup of the spirit wine as well, following which elated looks appeared on their faces.

They weren't avid drinkers, so they didn't care about the taste of the wine, but they were very pleased with its effects.

Furthermore, the warmth released by the Fire Drop Wine was lingering in their bodies and didn't appear as if it were going to dissipate anytime soon. Hence, they wouldn't have to continue to use their cultivation arts to keep themselves insulated.

"The warmth released by the Fire Drop Wine will linger for around half a day before slowly fading. You should have a cup as well, Junior Martial Sister Bai," Sun Ke said with a smile.

"Thank you, Senior Martial Brother Sun," Bai Suyuan replied with a nod.

Chapter 228: Disparity

"How much more of this Fire Drop Wine do you have, Junior Martial Brother Sun?" the first young man to have drunk the wine asked, and everyone turned to Sun Ke upon hearing this question.

One cup of wine could keep them warm for half a day, and there were six people in the group. They were going to have to stay in the Profound Ice Mountain Range for close to a month, so this one flagon of wine most likely wasn't going to be enough.

"Rest assured, everyone, I still have a few jars left, so we'll definitely have enough to weather this trial," Sun Ke replied with a smile, and everyone was quite relieved to hear this.

"You have my thanks, Senior Martial Brother Sun. If you need help with anything in the future, feel free to call on me," a tall young man in the group said in an earnest manner, and everyone else nodded in agreement.

"You're all far too kind. All of us come from the same sect, so it's only right that we help out one another," Sun Ke replied in a calm manner, but internally, he was quite pleased with this reaction.

He had only been in the Blaze Dragon Dao for a short time, so he was eager to make connections, and some spirit wine was certainly a fine price to pay for this purpose.

Meanwhile, several thousand kilometers away, a hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes, but it was then quickly replaced by a contemplative expression.

At some point, Su Tongxiao had already vanished without a trace.

Sun Ke and the others continued onward without any delay, and shortly thereafter, they encountered their first real battle since entering the mountain range.

It was a group of snow foxes with powers that ranged between the Nascent Soul Stage and the Deity Transformation Stage, and there were around 40 to 50 of them. They had come rushing out from either side of the mountain range while howling in unison, presenting an intimidating sight to behold.

Everyone in Sun Ke's group was quite powerful in their own right, and thanks to Sun Ke's wine, they had all developed a sense of camaraderie, so they were able to quickly get into a battle formation.

The three cultivators in the group with the highest cultivation bases, namely Bai Suyuan, Sun Ke, and another young man were situated at the very forefront, and the three of them summoned a a crescent-shaped flying sword, four flying daggers, and a purplish-golden staff, respectively.

The flying sword transformed into a streak of silver swordlight that was over 1,000 feet in length in a flash, then came slashing down from above.

Meanwhile, the purplish-golden staff released several hundred purple staff projections amid a flash of bright light, all of which hurtled through the air with astonishing power.

As for the four azure flying daggers, they were glowing bright in unison as they expanded to dozens of times their original size, swooping downward as a set of giant azure blades, each of which was several hundred feet in length.

The skulk of snow foxes were instantly sent flying back by the barrage of attacks, and the dozen or so Deity Transformation Stage snow foxes were killed on the spot, instantly halting the momentum of their charge.

In the next instant, the three disciples behind Sun Ke's trio sprang into action as well, and a flurry of attacks were sent raining down upon the snow foxes

Bursts of dull rumbling rang out alongside flashes of light of different colors.

A few moments later, all of the light subsided, and the skulk of snow foxes had already been reduced to sets of dismembered bodies, while a large area had been stained red with their blood.

Han Li gave a slight nod as he observed the group in action from afar.

These disciples had decent reactions. In particular, Bai Suyuan and Sun Ke had endured some life-and-death situations outside of the sect, so they were naturally more capable in situations like these than the other disciples who had grown up their entire lives in the sect.

As a major sect in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, the Blaze Dragon Dao possessed a cultivation environment that was unimaginable to those in the outside world. It had all of the resources and treasures that these disciples could ever want for, thereby allowing them to progress rapidly in their cultivation, but there were downsides to this as well.

For the sake of the development of these core disciples, the higher-ups of the sect had spared no effort.

Sun Ke and the others only took a short while to regroup before they continued onward.

Meanwhile, the other two groups had also been attacked by demon beasts.

On the Snow Camel Mountain route, Qi Huanyu and the others encountered a flock of vicious snow birds with vulture-like heads, but excessively large beaks, out of which they were able to shoot a relentless barrage of white ice arrows.

There were over 100 of these birds in total, and around half of them possessed Deity Transformation Stage power.

A volley of white ice arrows descended out of the sky, interspersed with a bone-chilling aura, and the occasional bird came swooping down from above as well.

Qi Huanyu's group was quite large, and all of them were carrying extremely powerful treasures, but none of them had any experience when it came to life-and-death battles.

Hence, the violent killing intent displayed by the flock of birds and the relentless storm of attacks caught them completely off guard, and they were looking a little panicked.

All of them were standing in a circle with their backs facing one another to form a ring-shaped protective barrier that warded off the oncoming attacks.

Qi Huanyu's face was slightly pale, and he yelled, "Don't panic! These are just some Deity Transformation Stage demon beasts! Everyone, listen to me. Half of you continue to support the barrier, while the other half retaliates!"

He was the leader of the group, and his instructions instilled within everyone a sense of confidence as they immediately began to carry out his orders.

Before long, bursts of dazzling light were erupting into the air to strike at the white birds in the sky.

The disciples were feeling very intimidated, so their attacks were quite feeble, but thanks to the massive cultivation base advantage they had, they were able to strike down the birds one after another.

Around 15 minutes later, the battle finally drew to a conclusion.

Most of the birds had been slain, while the rest had fled the battle.

Qi Huanyu and the others were uninjured. They looked at the bird carcasses around them as they inhaled the bloody scent in the air, and even though their faces were quite pale, they were gradually regaining their composure.

"I can't believe a bunch of mere Deity Transformation Stage demon beasts had all of you in such a panic! You should be ashamed of yourselves! You saw what happened just now. As long as we maintain our composure, these demon beasts are no match for us!" Qi Huanyu yelled in an attempt to raise morale.

Everyone immediately nodded in response.

Qi Huanyu was just about to say something further when a more experienced individual in the group stepped forward and cautioned, "Young Master Qi, the scent of blood here is too strong, so we should leave this place as soon as possible."

Qi Huanyu faltered slightly upon hearing this, then immediately understood the reasoning behind the advice, and he instructed everyone to continue onward.

Meanwhile, Su Tongxiao appeared in the air above amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, then shook his head in dismay before vanishing from the spot.

The situation was much the same over on the White Fox Valley route. Tang Chuan's group didn't have much practical battle experience, either, and they also erupted into a blind panic in the face of the ferocious demon beasts that they were attacked by.

However, thanks to their cultivation base advantage and powerful treasures, they were able to weather the storm, then composed themselves before defeating the enemy without suffering any casualties.

The three groups of disciples continued onward, and seven or eight days passed by in the blink of an eye as all of the disciples ventured deeper into the Profound Ice Mountain Range.

The demon beasts that they encountered along the way were becoming more and more powerful, and some Spatial Tempering Stage demon beasts had begun to appear.

After several battles, Qi Huanyu and the others had become far more proficient in battle than before, but they were still struggling in the face of demon beasts of a similar level of power to themselves.

On the Snow Camel Mountain Route, Qi Huanyu and his group had been surrounded by around a dozen giant ice praying mantises.

These praying mantises were entirely white in color with frosty patterns all over their bodies, and their mouths were split up into four mandibles. Their eyes were large and protruded outward, giving them a fearsome appearance, and their thick and strong front limbs resembled a pair of giant blades that were giving off bone-chilling auras.

Every single one of these demon beasts possessed early-Spatial Tempering Stage power, and they were extremely fast, dashing around Qi Huanyu's group while unleashing a ferocious barrage of attacks, leaving trails of afterimages in their wake.

Just like before, Qi Huanyu and the others had formed a circle, conjuring up a ring-shaped protective barrier that encompassed everyone within it.

However, these praying mantises were far more powerful than the birds from before, and they were able to unleash powerful projections with their blade-like front limbs.

These projections were imbued with ferocious power, causing the ring-shaped light barrier to tremble incessantly.

Qi Huanyu and the others were forced to inject all of their magic power into their protective treasures to maintain the light barrier, so they were completely unable to retaliate.

The praying mantises were letting loose bloodthirsty screeches as they swung their front limbs through their air relentlessly, seemingly only growing more vigorous and powerful as time went on.

The ring-shaped light barrier wasn't just a single cohesive barrier. Instead, it was jointly formed by everyone's protective treasures, and some of the more fragile parts of the barrier were close to giving out.

A tall and thin young man turned to Qi Huanyu with a panicked expression as he asked, "What do we do, Young Master Qi? These things are all at the Spatial Tempering Stage, and there are too many of them for us to deal with!"

The young man was a direct descendant to a True Immortal Stage elder of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and he had been cultivating his entire life in the sect, progressing smoothly to the Spatial Tempering Stage thanks to an endless supply of pills. As a result, he had next to no battle experience.

He had made some improvements in this regard over the course of the trial thus far, but his heart was still shuddering with fear at the sight of these terrifying praying mantises.

Everyone else in the group was in much the same mental state as the young man, and they couldn't help but wonder if they were going to die here, a thought that only made them even more panicked and fearful.

All of a sudden, a loud crack rang out, and a light barrier conjured up by a white handkerchief treasure was destroyed, creating an opening in the overall light barrier.

A bright projection flew straight through the opening, and an agonized howl rang out as blood splattered through the air.

A disciple near the opening had been sent flying with a large gash sliced into his arm, but thankfully, he was wearing a suit of armor of quite a high caliber, so he had managed to escape severe injury.

Bright purple light erupted from Qi Huanyu's glabella as he swept an arm through the air, releasing a purple wheel treasure that conjured up a purple vortex to fill the opening.

"There's no need to fear! There are True Immortal cultivators protecting us in secret during the trial, and they'll take care of all unforeseen mishaps for us. These praying mantises are beyond what we can deal with, so I'm sure one of them will intervene soon!" Qi Huanyu yelled.

Everyone else was ecstatic to hear this.

"I've heard about this before, and I was rather skeptical, but it must be true if Young Master Qi says so!"

"There are only 10 of us, yet we're facing close to 20 of these praying mantises. This is definitely beyond the scope of the trial, so why has there still not been an intervention?"

Su Tongxiao was hovering high up in the sky as a blurry shadow, and he shook his head with a forlorn sigh while flicking a finger through the air.

Streaks of invisible sword qi instantly came hurtling down from above, piercing through the bodies of most of the praying mantises.

All of the praying mantises that were struck instantly exploded silently into piles of dust that were scattered by the wind.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Su Tongxiao vanished once again immediately thereafter.

It didn't take long before Qi Huanyu and the others noticed that most of the praying mantises had disappeared, thereby significantly alleviating the pressure on them.

"How come there are suddenly so much fewer praying mantises?" someone asked with a puzzled expression.

"They were obviously killed by someone! There really is someone protecting us in secret!" someone else exclaimed with an ecstatic expression.

Qi Huanyu was also quite relieved to see this, and a triumphant smile appeared on his face as he yelled, "These filthy beasts must pay the price for attacking us! Don't let any of them get away!"

Everyone else immediately answered his call, then began retaliating against the remaining praying mantises with renewed vigor.

A short while later, all of the praying mantises were slain with the exception of two of them, which had managed to get away.

The front limbs of these praying mantises were filled with abundant spiritual power and were outstanding tool refinement materials even for Spatial Tempering cultivators, so these front limbs were immediately severed before being stowed away by several of the disciples.

"Let's go!"

Qi Huanyu flew up into the air and led the way forward.

Now that it was confirmed that there was indeed someone protecting them in secret, he was instilled with a great deal of confidence and began to continue onward at a faster pace than before.

Chapter 229: Trapped

Not long after Qi Huanyu and his group defeated the praying mantises, Tang Chuan's group found themselves locked in battle against a nest of white ice scorpions deep in the White Fox Valley.

There were around 20 to 30 of these scorpions, and all of them were quite powerful. Tang Chuan and the others were already in a dire situation, but all of a sudden, the few Spatial Tempering Stage scorpions in the nest somehow vanished without a trace.

Tang Chuan and the others were ecstatic, and they immediately retaliated, quickly slaying all of the ice scorpions before continuing onward.

Meanwhile, Su Tongxiao lingered for a moment in the air above them before vanishing yet again.

……

Several thin silver threads came flying down, whistling through the air before plunging into a white ice python's body to inflict a massive wound.

The Spatial Tempering Stage ice python let loose an agonized cry before plummeting to the ground. Blood was gushing out of its body as it spasmed a few times before falling completely still.

The thin silver threads came flying back before coming together to form a silver flying sword that returned to Bai Suyuan's side.

Sun Ke and the others were standing around Bai Suyuan in a circle to form a protective barrier, and outside the barrier were around a dozen more Spatial Tempering Stage giant pythons that were attacking them relentlessly.

Each of Sun Ke and the others had to deal with more than two of these giant pythons on their own on average, and they were definitely on the back foot, but they were still able to hold their own for now.

After slaying that python, Bai Suyuan didn't stop for even a single moment as she pointed a finger forward, and the silver flying sword shot forth through the air once again, split up into dozens of silver sword threads that formed a lotus flower shape as it hurtled toward one of the pythons that Sun Ke was locked in battle against.

Sun Ke was ecstatic to see this, and he hurriedly assisted her with his four azure flying daggers.

At this point, 10 days had already passed in the trial, and they were well and truly deep in the Profound Ice Mountain Range. The demon beasts that they were encountering were becoming more and more powerful, and on this day, they had been surrounded by around a dozen of these mid-Spatial Tempering Stage python beasts.

The six of them had immediately formed a circular defensive array, and as the most powerful one among them, Bai Suyuan was protected at the center of the array so she could retaliate against the enemy.

She certainly didn't disappoint, unleashing secret techniques one after another, displaying immense combat prowess in the face of the giant pythons.

Time slowly passed by, and the tide of the battle was beginning to turn in their favor.

The dozens of sword threads pierced through a giant python's body, and they hadn't struck a vital region, but they did temporarily stop it cold in its tracks.

Immediately thereafter, a massive purplish-golden staff projection came crashing down viciously onto its head, splitting its head into multiple chunks as blood and intracranial fluids splattered in all directions.

All of a sudden, a white python let loose a strange roar before fleeing into the distance, and the remaining python beasts immediately followed along, vanishing into the distant sky in the blink of an eye.

Bai Suyuan and the others didn't set off in pursuit. All of them had expended a great deal of magic power during the course of the battle, and they immediately pulled out some pills and spirit stones to aid in their recovery.

Meanwhile, Han Li was concealed high up in the sky as a blurry shadow within a cloud, and he gave a slight nod of approval.

He hadn't had to intervene even once during this entire trial.

Bai Suyuan and the others were all quite commendable in their tactical acumen and mental fortitude. The strategy that they had employed in the battle just now was a little unrefined, but considering their cultivation bases, they had already done extremely well.

After resting for a short while, Bai Suyuan and the others continued onward, and Han Li followed along.

However, in the next instant, his expression changed slightly as he turned to a certain direction, and Su Tongxiao appeared there amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

"Weren't you busy protecting the other two groups, Brother Su?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"I've already mostly cleared out the other two routes. This is turning out to be a lot more exhausting than I bargained for! The two groups of disciples have improved quite a bit, so I'm sure they'll be fine on their own now. These disciples all possess exceptional aptitude, but they're sorely lacking in practical battle experience," Su Tongxiao sighed.

"They've grown up their entire lives in the sect under the protection of the elders, so it's no surprise that they don't have much experience in battle," Han Li said.

In his eyes, someone who hadn't experienced life-and-death battles wouldn't be of much use at all in perilous situations, even if they possessed a lofty cultivation base.

"It's not that difficult for them to accumulate battle experience. There's an Illusory Nightmare Pagoda in the sect that's available exclusively to direct disciples to help them improve in this regard," Su Tongxiao said.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this. "I didn't know there was such a place in the sect."

"There are many interesting places in the sect. You'll learn about all of them in due time, Brother Li," Su Tongxiao said with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response, then suddenly raised his head, and Su Tongxiao's brows also furrowed slightly at the exact same moment.

A Body Integration Stage demon beast was quickly approaching Qi Huanyu's group.

"I didn't think that a Body Integration Stage demon beast would appear so soon," Su Tongxiao mused.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as the corners of his lips curved upward by a minute degree as he said, "It must've been attracted by the blood and carcasses of all of the demon beasts that you slew to clear out the two routes."

"Perhaps," Su Tongxiao replied before preparing to depart.

Qi Huanyu's group couldn't even deal with a bunch of Spatial Tempering Stage demon beasts, so they certainly didn't stand any chance against a Body Integration Stage foe. Hence, he had to keep a close eye on them as a safety precaution.

Right at this moment, his expression changed slightly as he cast his gaze toward Tang Chuan's direction.

As it turned out, another Body Integration Stage demon beasts had appeared there. It was a giant bird that was flying extremely fast, and it was rapidly closing in on Tang Chuan's group.

"There are two Body Integration Stage demon beasts at once!" Su Tongxiao exclaimed with a hint of urgency in his eyes.

The three routes were quite far away from one another, so if he were to go to one route, then he wouldn't be in time to go to the other.

"Brother Li, can I trouble you to take care of the demon beast on Tang Chuan's route? I would be extremely grateful to you if you could do so," Su Tongxiao said as he turned to Han Li.

A reluctant look appeared on Han Li's face as he cast his gaze forward, and after a brief hesitation, he replied, "Alright, I suppose I could do that."

"You have my thanks, Brother Li," Su Tongxiao said, then immediately flew away into the distance.

Han Li took a glance at Su Tongxiao's departing figure, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he also vanished from the spot.

……

Meanwhile, Tang Chuan's group of eight was continuing onward, and according to the map, they weren't far away from their destination.

Over 70% of the demon beasts on their route had been wiped out by Su Tongxiao in advance, so they were naturally able to make very smooth progress.

Tang Chuan was well aware that one of the True Immortal Stage elders that was protecting them in secret had to have been responsible for this sharp decline in demon beast numbers.

Now that he no longer had to worry about his own safety, claiming the top spot in the trial became his new top priority.

With that in mind, Tang Chuan turned and yelled to everyone in his group, "Let's speed up a little more!"

He had to track down and kill a Dark Snow Bear as soon as quickly as possible. As for whether this group of eight would be capable of slaying a Dark Snow Bear, that wasn't something that he was concerned about at all.

There was no way that the True Immortal Stage elder would allow him to be killed by the Dark Snow Bear, so they would have to intervene at some point.

With that in mind, Tang Chuan was brimming with confidence as he sped up even further.

Right at this moment, a sharp screech rang out from afar.

The sound was coming from somewhere very far away, but it was extremely sharp and piercing, causing his eardrums to throb with sharp pain. As a result, he was forced to slow down involuntarily.

The other disciples in the group were all of inferior cultivation base to Tang Chuan, and they couldn't help but let loose pained cries as they clapped their hands over their ears.

"What's that?" Tang Chuan murmured to himself with a fearful expression.

A black dot had appeared in the distant sky to his left, and it was rapidly approaching them, quickly coming into view and revealing itself to be a terrifying demon beast.

It was a terrifying wyrm-like demon beast that was several thousand feet in size. There was a pair of large wings on its back, and every single feather on those wings resembled a sharp sword. Its long tail was riddled with huge bone spikes, and at the end of the tail was a scorpion-like hooked pincer that was glowing with faint blue light, clearly indicating that it was tipped with lethal poison.

Furthermore, the immense aura that the giant beast was giving off indicated that it possessed Body Integration Stage power.

"It's a Body Integration Stage demon beast!"

Tang Chuan immediately fled back in retreat as quickly as he could while frantically looking around, as if he were searching for something.

The fearsome beast didn't give them any time to react as it let loose a thunderous roar, releasing powerful soundwaves that created ripples that were visible even to the naked eye.

Tang Chuan and the others didn't even have a chance to summon any treasures before the soundwaves swept over them, causing them to bleed out of all of their orifices as the blood and magic power in their bodies churned violently.

With a flap of its wings, the giant beast conjured up numerous thick blue ice spikes before sending them flying through the air, hurtling directly toward Tang Chuan and the other disciples.

In this dire situation, an azure figure appeared out of nowhere in front of the eight disciples, then extended a finger forward.

Bursts of dazzling azure light were released from the figure's fingertip, instantly forming a massive light barrier in front of the eight disciples.

The soundwaves were instantly kept out, while the ice spikes shattered upon making contact with the light barrier.

The giant beast stopped cold in its tracks as it stared at the figure that had just appeared before it, and upon sensing the azure figure's enormous aura, it immediately fled into the distance with a panicked look in its eyes.

Meanwhile, the azure figure abruptly vanished from the spot, then appeared directly above the giant beast's head in the next instant.

With a casual flick of his finger, a streak of azure light shot forth before plunging into the giant beast's head.

The giant beast's entire body instantly stiffened, following which its massive head exploded violently.

Immediately thereafter, a series of black balls flew out of the beast's head, and it flew rapidly toward the azure figure with black light flashing erratically over their surfaces.

The azure figure was just about to fly back in retreat upon seeing this when the black balls abruptly exploded into dazzling balls of black light, which connected together to form an enormous black array, within which countless black runes were surging incessantly.

Traces of law powers were emanating from the array, and the air surrounding the array instantly became as hard as iron and steel, trapping the azure figure inside.

"What just happened?"

Tang Chuan and the other disciples were completely dumbfounded by what they were witnessing.

Meanwhile, on the Snow Camel Mountain route.

Qi Huanyu and five other disciples were hiding behind a small mountain with horrified expressions. Most of them were bearing severe injuries, indicating that they had just endured a fierce battle.

In the air beside them were four tiny figures, each of which was roughly two inches tall. They appeared to have been the nascent souls of the other four disciples in the group, all of which had presumably had their physical bodies destroyed.

At this moment, everyone was staring at a giant black array several thousand feet in front of the mountain.

On the ground beneath the array laid the carcass of a giant demon beast, while Su Tongxiao was trapped within the array, struggling with all his might to break free.

However, the black array was clearly no ordinary array, and it was extremely resolute, able to contain even a mid-True Immortal cultivator like Su Tongxiao.

Chapter 230: Wasting Time

Meanwhile.

Sun Ke's group of six had already arrived deep in Pine Fruit Mountain.

Their route was the safest of the three routes, so the demon beasts that they had encountered hadn't been all that powerful, and thanks to the camaraderie that they had built, it had been a relatively smooth journey thus far.

At this moment, Bai Suyuan was flying beside Sun Ke, and her gaze was roaming over the vast snowland as she said, "Senior Martial Brother, according to the map, we'll reach the area where the Snow Dove Beasts are active in about 1,000 more kilometers."

"Those beasts are said to be quite docile, but their power is nothing to be scoffed at, and there have been precedents of such beasts actively attacking cultivators, so we'll have to be careful," Sun Ke said.

As soon as his voice trailed off, Bai Suyuan suddenly stopped in her tracks, then cast a wary gaze toward a forest that was several thousand feet up ahead.

Sun Ke immediately stopped as well, then raised a hand to indicate for everyone else to do the same.

The other four disciples in the group had already split up and summoned their respective treasures.

"I didn't think a bunch of kids like you would be able to detect my presence."

A hoarse voice rang out as a tall and imposing white-robed elderly man slowly rose up into the air from within the forest up ahead.

Bai Suyuan was feeling rather alarmed, but she still put on a respectful demeanor as she asked, "May I ask who you are and why you're hiding here, Senior?"

She was unable to detect the elderly man's cultivation base, and there was no way that she would've been able to sense his presence had it not been for the fact that she was carrying a special treasure. Furthermore, the manner in which he was sneaking around clearly indicated that he didn't harbor any good intentions.

The same thoughts had clearly occurred to Sun Ke and the others as well, and they exchanged a few glances, seemingly trying to decide on how to proceed.

"You don't need to know who I am, Bai Suyuan. What a pretty little flower you are. The Moonlight Immortal Physique truly lives up to its reputation. Come with me, and don't try to put up any futile resistance," the elderly man said.

Bai Suyuan's expression remained unchanged, but her heart clenched up slightly as she warned, "Stay away! The elders of our sect are in the nearby vicinity!"

A mocking sneer appeared on the elderly man's face as he jeered, "Quit trying to bluff me, little girl. The elders arranged to protect all of you in secret have already been diverted away by me, so no one's coming to save you. Now then, are you going to do things the easy way or the hard way?"

Sun Ke and the others were quite alarmed to hear this.

They didn't have any powerful backers in the sect, but seeing as they had managed to secure the right to participate in the trial, all of them naturally had their own information sources, so they were aware that there were going to be inner sect elders protecting them in secret during the trial.

This was like a safety net that instilled within them a sense of reassurance, but now that these elders had apparently been diverted elsewhere, they were naturally feeling a little fearful.

"I've never met you before, so why do you insist that I come with you, Senior?" Bai Suyuan asked.

Instead of answering Bai Suyuan's question, the elderly man smiled and said, "You've always wanted to know what happened to the patriarch of your Bai Clan, right? If you come with me, I'll tell you where he is."

"You know our clan's patriarch?" Bai Suyuan hurriedly asked.

"Of course I'm familiar with Elder Bai Fengyi," the elderly man replied in a casual voice.

A hint of hesitation appeared on Bai Suyuan's face, and even with all her wiles and cunning, she was at a slight loss for what to do.

"Don't listen to him, Junior Martial Sister Bai! He's just saying that to lure you into surrendering yourself over to him!" Sun Ke hurriedly cautioned.

"You're right! If you really do know our clan's patriarch, then show me a token of his!" Bai Suyuan said.

A cold look appeared on the elderly man's face upon hearing this. "I've tried to be nice, but seeing as you insist on testing my patience, you'll have to bear the consequences! I can't afford to waste any more time here!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he abruptly raised a hand, then thrust it forward with his fingers spread apart. A shimmering golden bead instantly shot forth through the air, reaching within 200 feet of Bai Suyuan in the blink of an eye.

In the next instant, dazzling golden light erupted from the bead, and it transformed into a large golden net that descended upon her.

Bai Suyuan immediately shot back in retreat as quickly as she could, but there was simply far too massive a power disparity between the two, and she was unable to evade the attack even though she had reacted right away.

As for Sun Ke and the others, there was no time for them to do anything, and they could only look on helplessly as the golden net began to close in on Bai Suyuan.

Right at this moment, a burst of azure light appeared in the air without any warning, immediately following which a figure emerged in front of Bai Suyuan before sweeping a hand through the air.

A ball of black liquid instantly surged forth, crashing heavily into the golden net.

As soon as the two made contact with one another, the golden net instantly plummeted toward the ground as if something incredibly heavy were weighing down upon it.

"What? How could this be?" the elderly man exclaimed with a surprised expression.

"Elder Li!"

After taking a moment to steady herself, Bai Suyuan was both surprised and elated to find that she had been saved by a familiar figure.

Indeed, the one standing between her and the elderly man was none other than Han Li.

Instead of turning to look at Bai Suyuan, Han Li's gaze remained firmly fixed on the elderly man as he said, "You've already wasted more than enough time here. Also, I've been nearby this entire time, so why are you saying that I left? If these disciples report me to the sect for neglecting my duties, then I'll have merit points deducted."

"No wonder that figure had an identical aura to yours, but it felt like something wasn't quite right with it. In any case, is a mere early-True Immortal cultivator like yourself going to stand against me?" the elderly man chuckled coldly.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he raised a hand to summon a set of seven flying swords, which circled around in the air for a moment before forming a sword array that flew directly toward Han Li.

The runes on the flying swords were glowing brightly as they released bursts of white flames, making the flying swords resemble a massive fire raven with its wings spread open.

Han Li raised both hands in response, and a torrent of heavy water gushed forth, transforming into a black flood dragon that was around 10 feet in length in mid-air before hurtling directly toward the white fire raven.

A string of loud explosions rang out as countless specks of white flames were sent flying in all directions, instantly melting the snow on the ground into water vapor wherever they landed.

The snow on around a dozen of the nearby pine trees quickly melted away, following which the trees themselves erupted into flames as well.

A peculiar look appeared in Sun Ke's eyes at the sight of Han Li, and he approached Bai Suyuan before asking, "Who is this elder, Junior Martial Sister Bai?"

Bai Suyuan's attention was entirely focused on the battle unfolding before her eyes, so she failed to notice the peculiar look on Sun Ke's face as she replied, "He's an inner sect elder by the name of Li Feiyu."

Sun Ke was naturally astonished to hear this.

This Elder Li shared the same name as the man that he had met on the Seafaring Lightning Boat, and most importantly, their auras were very similar.

However, the cultivation base of this Li Feiyu was worlds apart from that of the Li Feiyu from the Seafaring Lightning Boat, and Sun Ke couldn't help but wonder if they were actually the same person.

Right at this moment, the elderly man let loose a loud roar, and the white fire raven formed by his flying swords spread its wings as it pounced at Han Li's black wyrm, forcing the latter back into retreat.

Han Li made a hand seal while chanting an incantation upon seeing this, and a black disk that was around a foot in size with countless fine and complex spirit patterns on its surface suddenly appeared behind him.

The disk was giving off a powerful aura of water laws, and it was none other than this Heavy Water True Axis.

All of a sudden, the Heavy Water True Axis began to rapidly revolve at Han Li's behest before flying rapidly toward the white fire raven.

As it approached the fire raven, the Water Dao Runes on the Heavy Water True Axis began to glow with dazzling blue light, while the water law aura emanating from it became even more potent.

The elderly man's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and with a flick of his wrist, he sent a shimmering golden talisman flying through the air, and the talisman vanished into the fire raven's body right before it was about to clash with the Heavy Water True Axis.

A resounding boom rang out as the golden talisman transformed the white fire raven into a ball of scorching white light before clashing against the Heavy Water True Axis.

Tremendous shockwaves erupted in all directions from the epicenter of the clash, and half of the shockwaves were scorching hot, while the other half were cool and refreshing, but both were extremely destructive and destroyed all of the trees in their path.

Sun Ke and the others hurriedly fled back in retreat, quickly fleeing to several thousand feet away.

A string of loud clangs rang out as the Heavy Water True Axis revolved furiously on the spot as it clashed against the ball of scorching white light, and it seemed that the two had come to an impasse.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, and the heavy water wyrm that had been forced back into retreat earlier rose up into the air once again before hurtling toward the ball of white light.

A dull thump rang out, and the heavy water wyrm was sliced apart by the sharp sword intent emanating from the seven flying swords as soon as it plunged into the ball of white light.

A vast expanse of black heavy water erupted in all directions, but immediately thereafter, the Heavy Water True Axis suddenly began to glow brightly while releasing a burst of peculiar suction force.

All of the nearby heavy water was instantly sucked into the axis as a result, making the Heavy Water True Axis even heavier than before.

Thanks to its increased weight, it was revolving with greater momentum, and the ball of white light was slowly forced back into retreat.

The elderly man's view was obstructed by the ball of light, so he hadn't yet noticed that something was amiss. He had thought that Han Li had injected more magic power into his Heavy Water True Axis, so he hurriedly responded by injecting more magic power into his ball of white light as well.

Meanwhile, with another sweep of his sleeve, an even larger heavy water wyrm was sent flying through the air, but this time, instead of flying into the ball of white light, it plunged straight into the Heavy Water True Axis.

A dull thump rang out, and the heavy water wyrm instantly vanished into the axis without a trace.

Radiant black light erupted from the Heavy Water True Axis, and it expanded by about an inch diameter while becoming even heavier.

All of a sudden, the elderly man felt a burst of mountainous force hurtling toward him, and it was so heavy that he was struck by a sense of asphyxiation.

He hurriedly made a hand seal to support the ball of white light so that it wouldn't be instantly destroyed, and at the same time, he opened his mouth to release a tiny golden wooden puppet.

Chapter 231: The Might of Heavy Water

As soon as the wooden puppet appeared, it instantly vanished on the spot, then appeared directly above Han Li an instant later in a wraith-like manner.

A burst of golden light flashed past as a golden-armored puppet that was over 30 feet tall emerged. The puppet was wielding a vajra pestle, which it swung down directly upon Han Li's head.

Han Li tossed a black ball in the direction of the Heavy Water True Axis, then turned around and raised an arm to combat the descending vajra pestle.

A layer of golden scales appeared over his arm as it clashed against the vajra pestle amid a resounding boom.

A shimmering golden fist struck the vajra pestle with tremendous force, sending a burst of even more powerful shockwaves sweeping through the air.

Before the sound from the clash had completely subsided, a deafening boom rang out from the Heavy Water True Axis as well, originating from the explosion of the ball of Heavy Water Veined Lightning that Han Li had just tossed in that direction.

Violent arcs of silver lightning erupted in all directions, quickly encompassing the entire area within a radius of over 1,000 feet.

The ball of white light formed by the elderly man's flying swords was instantly scattered, while the Heavy Water True Axis remained largely unaffected and continued to plunge forward with unstoppable might.

Immediately thereafter, a string of loud booms rang out as five of the seven flying swords were crushed into dust by the tremendous weight of the Heavy Water True Axis.

The destruction of the elderly man's bonded flying swords instantly caused him to throw up a large mouthful of blood from the resulting backlash.

However, he had no time to wipe the blood from his lips as he turned to Han Li with an incredulous look on his face. There, cracks were beginning to appear on the surface of the golden-armored puppet that he had been nurturing in his body for countless years.

Only then did he realize that he was no match for Han Li, and he immediately fled the scene at an incredible speed, doing so in such a hasty and decisive fashion that he had even abandoned his two remaining bonded flying swords.

Almost at the exact same moment, the golden-armored puppet shattered into pieces.

"Elder Li, he's getting away!" Bai Suyuan yelled in an urgent voice.

Han Li took a glance in the direction that the elderly man had fled in, but wasn't in a hurry to set off in pursuit.

With a wave of his hand, he stowed the Heavy Water True Axis away, then drew the two remaining flying swords and the golden bead that was capable of transforming into that golden net into his storage bracelet as well.

Immediately thereafter, countless arcs of silver lightning appeared over his body, forming a circular lightning array with a diameter in excess of 100 feet in the blink of an eye.

An earth-shattering thunderclap rang out as the silver array vanished on the spot, leaving behind only a few arcs of silver lightning that quickly dissipated as well. Meanwhile, Bai Suyuan and the others were left to gawk at one another with astonished expressions.

A True Immortal cultivator was simply unfathomable in their eyes. The clash between Han Li and the elderly man had only lasted a few seconds, but they were already thoroughly astonished by what they had just witnessed.

High up in the sky close to 100,000 kilometers away, the elderly man had blood dripping down from the corner of his lips as he flew through the air as quickly as he could with a look of intense fear in his eyes.

According to the information that he had gathered before coming here, Han Li was supposed to have been an itinerant early-True Immortal cultivator who had only recently joined the sect, but he was far more powerful than what the elderly man had imagined. Granted, he hadn't unleashed all of his treasures and abilities, but he knew that if the battle had continued, then he would've perished for sure. Thankfully, it seemed that he wasn't being pursued.

Right as this thought crossed his mind, an earth-shattering thunderclap suddenly rang out in the sky above him.

The elderly man looked up to see a bolt of silver lightning that was as thick as a water vat crashing down from the heavens, and within the lightning was a deity-like figure that was descending from above with his long hair dancing all around him.

The figure was holding a black spear with lightning revolving all around it, and the spear was being plunged down viciously from above.

The elderly man was caught completely off guard, and he had no time to take evasive measures, so he could only hurriedly raise his hands and summon a scaled shield to protect himself.

A resounding boom rang out as the heavy water spear pierced straight through the shield, then continued downward and plunged through the elderly man's head.

Right at this moment, a tiny figure that was around three inches tall and was clad in a suit of golden armor suddenly flew out of the top of the elderly man's head in a flash.

Before Han Li had a chance to do anything, a layer of crimson light suddenly appeared over the tiny figure's skin, immediately following which its entire body erupted into a cloud of blood mist that vanished without a trace.

Han Li instantly released his spiritual sense to encompass the surrounding area in a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers, but was ultimately unable to find anything.

He slowly withdrew the heavy water spear that he had impaled through the elderly man's body, then made a grabbing motion with one hand, and the storage bracelet on the elderly man's wrist flew into his grasp.

After securing the storage bracelet, he injected his spiritual sense into it to find that it contained a good collection of items, including several powerful treasures and around a dozen Immortal Origin Stones.

After stowing the storage bracelet away, Han Li flew back the same way he had come from as a streak of azure light, and by the time he returned, he discovered that Bai Suyuan and the others had been taken to a valley near Pine Fruit Mountain by Su Tongxiao.

Fang Yu and the other two groups of disciples were there as well.

Aside from Qi Huanyu's group, out of which four of the disciples had had their physical bodies destroyed, there were no other casualties, but everyone still had looks of lingering fear in their eyes.

At this moment, Su Tongxiao was seated on a giant rock in the valley, and his aura was rather unstable, indicating that he had sustained some injuries.

He immediately approached Han Li upon spotting him, then asked, "Did you manage to catch him, Brother Li?"

It was clear that he had already been made aware of what had just transpired here.

Han Li shook his head in response. "I managed to destroy his physical body, but his nascent soul got away using some type of secret technique."

"Thank heavens you arrived in time to protect the other disciples. I got complacent for a moment on my end and... At the very least, with that man's physical body destroyed, we haven't completely failed in our mission," Su Tongxiao sighed.

"Is there still a need to continue the trial at this point, Brother Su?" Han Li asked.

"An enemy True Immortal cultivator has already appeared, and there's no guarantee that he doesn't have accomplices nearby, so we'll have to conclude the trial as a safety precaution. Let's go back and report to the sect," Su Tongxiao replied.

"That sounds like it's for the best," Han Li replied with a nod.

Su Tongxiao suddenly drew a little closer to Han Li, then pulled out a storage pouch that he stuffed into Han Li's hand as he communicated through voice transmission, "By the way, I owe you my thanks for protecting the other two groups of disciples. You deserve a share of the offerings from the elders."

"You're far too kind, Brother Su."

Han Li raised no objections as he stowed the storage pouch away.

Given his contributions, he was indeed deserving of a share in these offerings.

In order to avoid further mishaps, everyone chose to return the same way they had come on foot rather than flying back.

Following this humbling incident, all of the disciples who regarded themselves as blessed prodigies were a lot more quiet, and even Qi Huanyu and Tang Chuan had become quite sullen and dejected.

Su Tongxiao was leading the way, while the disciples trailed along behind him, and Han Li was bringing up the rear.

Perhaps it was because she had heard about the patriarch of her clan from her assailant, but Bai Suyuan was walking along in an absentminded manner, seemingly with a lot on her mind.

Meanwhile, Sun Ke was dragging his feet as he trudged through the snow, and after some hesitation, he decided to intentionally drop to the rear of the group so that he could arrive by Han Li's side.

Right as he was pondering what he was going to say, he was greeted by the sound of a familiar voice. "Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Sun."

Sun Ke faltered slightly upon hearing this, then hurriedly replied with a respectful expression, "Ah, so it really is you, Brother Li, I mean, Elder Li..."

"I hope you don't mind that I hid my cultivation base from you back on the Seafaring Lightning Boat," Han Li said with a smile.

"I wouldn't dare! I'm just surprised that you're an inner sect elder of the Blaze Dragon Dao. If I had known this sooner, I wouldn't have had to go through the trouble of offering so many treasures to establish connections in order to join the sect. Instead, I would've offered the treasures straight to you," Sun Ke sighed.

"I was also quite surprised to see you here. If I had known you were coming here, I would've accompanied you along the way. I still think about all of the fine wines in your collection, and I've been dying to get a taste of the Fire Drop Wine that you've been sharing with your fellow disciples," Han Li chuckled.

"I still have some Fire Drop Wine left, you can have the rest of it if you'd like, Elder Li," Sun Ke immediately offered without any hesitation.

Instead of replying to Sun Ke's offer, Han Li said, "I have a request for you, Fellow Daoist Sun."

Sun Ke faltered slightly upon hearing this, then prompted, "Please go ahead, Elder Li."

"I want to exchange a spirit treasure for the recipe of your Fire Drop Wine. Is that a trade you're willing to make?" Han Li asked.

A conflicted look appeared on Sun Ke's face upon hearing this request, following which he gritted his teeth as he said, "Truth be told, this wine is different from the other wines in my collection as it's a secret recipe that's been passed down in my clan for generations, and it most likely can't be found anywhere else.

“I did bring it out with me in secret, but giving the recipe to outsiders has always been strictly prohibited. However, you've already saved my life on two occasions, and I'm not an ungrateful person, so I can make an exception and give you the recipe."

"If you're going to give me the recipe, then I must give you a spirit treasure in exchange. Otherwise, people will say that I'm extorting disciples for my own benefit. This sword is quite a powerful treasure, and it's not so easy to use, so you have to practice diligently with it after you've refined it," Han Li said as he flipped a hand over to produce a storage pouch, then offered it to Sun Ke.

The storage pouch contained that golden longsword that he had taken from the Origin Mirage Beast.

An overawed look appeared on Sun Ke's face, but he didn't refuse the storage pouch. At the same time, he offered an ancient piece of paper and an intricate red wine flagon to Han Li in exchange.

Han Li stowed the flagon away, then took a glance at the recipe on the ancient piece of paper before making a copy using a jade slip and returning the original to Sun Ke.

The other disciples noticed this interaction, and upon coming to the realization that he seemed to have been on friendly terms with an inner sect elder, all of them were feeling rather envious of him.

Even though all of them also had True Immortals in their clans, they certainly didn't have the courage to interact with a True Immortal as equals.

In particular, from their perspective, it seemed that Han Li was more powerful than Elder Su, which meant that he most likely had a higher status in the sect as well. After all, Tang Chuan's group hadn't suffered any casualties under his protection, but four of the disciples in Qi Huanyu's group had had their physical bodies destroyed while under Su Tongxiao's protection.

A few of the female cultivators were also taking extra glances at Sun Ke.

Han Li was openly conducting this trade with Sun Ke in front of everyone with the objective of earning Sun Ke more respect from his peers, a fact that Sun ke had already caught onto.

Chapter 232: Dispelling Doubts

After returning to the Blaze Dragon Dao, Su Tongxiao instructed Fang Yu to take the disciples back to the Rising Sun Palace, while he went to deliver a report to the sect's higher-ups. As the supervising elder with the higher cultivation base, he had to give the sect an explanation in the wake of the incident that had taken place during the trial.

In particular, four of the disciples had had their physical bodies destroyed, and having accepted bribes from so many elders, he was unable to escape culpability.

Han Li didn't want to get involved in this matter, so he bade farewell to Su Tongxiao, then went straight to the Cloud Piercing Peak before making his way into the side hall of the High Profound Palace.

The side hall was as deserted as ever, and the door was slightly ajar, while Elder Hu Yan was seated in his chair behind the table with a bored expression.

"Wine is truly a great thing, but it seems I must exercise more moderation. It's only been a few days, yet I'm close to running out again," Elder Hu Yan grumbled to himself as he took a sip out of the red gourd in his hand.

Han Li just so happened to have heard Elder Hu Yan's grumbling as he arrived at the entrance of the side hall, and he paused momentarily before making his way inside.

Elder Hu Yan raised his head to look at Han Li, then said, "Looks like you completed your third mission. You sure are a hard worker. Did any of the girls in the trial catch your eye?"

"Some unforeseen mishaps arose during the trial, so it was terminated halfway. However, most of the disciples emerged unscathed. Does this count as completing the mission?"

Han Li gave Elder Hu Yan a brief recount of what had taken place in the Profound Ice Mountain Range, handing Elder Hu Yan his elder badge as he did so.

"It doesn't concern you whether they've completed their trial or not. As long as you've done your job, the mission will naturally be counted as completed," Elder Hu Yan said as he took Han Li's elder badge from him.

He then quickly deposited the sum of merit points corresponding with the mission into the badge before tossing it back to Han Li.

Han Li didn't say anything as he caught the badge before stowing it away.

He took a glance at Elder Hu Yan, then at the potted spirit plant on the table, and he displayed no intention of departing.

"What do you want? Have you gotten addicted to carrying out missions? Do you want a fourth one?" Elder Hu Yan grumbled.

"Senior Hu Yan, I wanted to discuss our agreement about the Dao Warriors..."

Before Han Li had a chance to finish, Elder Hu Yan raised a hand to cut him off. "I'm gonna stop you right there! Don't bother coming to me unless you've found a good wine recipe. Before then, I'm not going to teach you anything."

Han Li had already anticipated such a reaction from Elder Hu Yan, and he smiled as he said, "Don't be in such a hurry to turn me down, Senior. Now that I've completed my missions, I have nothing to do anyway, so would I be able to have a drink with you?"

Elder Hu Yan's expression immediately darkened upon hearing this, and he hurriedly tucked his red gourd back under his belt as he grumbled, "I've been very busy recently, so I haven't had any time to brew wine, and I don't have much left. I don't even have enough for myself! I let you drink to your heart's content last time, and I was kicking myself after you left! Stop thinking my Dao Warriors and get out of here!"

"I'm not asking for wine from you, Senior. Instead, I'd like to treat you to a cup of wine," Han Li said with a smile.

"You want to treat me to a cup of wine? I'm extremely picky, so if it's just some ordinary spirit wine, then don't bother bringing it out. If you ruin my appetite with a foul-tasting wine, not only will I never impart my knowledge in Dao Warriors onto you, I'll kick you off this Cloud Piercing Peak myself!" Elder Hu Yan said.

Han Li remained unfazed by this threat, reaching out a hand before gently sweeping it over the table before him, upon which a pair of vibrant green jade cups appeared.

The cups were of an extremely even and flawless green color, and there were thin golden lines inside, forming a series of flower-petal-shaped patterns that were quite remarkable to behold.

Elder Hu Yan was just about to say something else when his attention was drawn to the pair of jade cups. "Those are some decent Golden Thread Jade Cups."

Han Li didn't say anything as he flipped a hand over to produce an intricate fire-red wine flagon.

He then raised his other hand and removed the flagon's wooden stopper.

A faint pop rang out, following which an extremely unique and rich wine aroma instantly wafted throughout the entire side hall from within the flagon.

Elder Hu Yan's slightly red nose instantly twitched slightly as his eyes lit up with intrigue.

He leaned forward involuntarily, then stood up from his chair. His entire upper body was sprawled out on the table as he brought his nose closer to the flagon in Han Li's hand before taking a vigorous whiff of its contents.

"Hurry up and pour me a cup! What are you waiting for? My goodness, I'm about to start drooling all over the table!" Elder Hu Yan demanded in an urgent voice as he gulped down the saliva that was accumulating in his mouth.

Han Li didn't dare to make Elder Hu Yan wait, so he leaned forward slightly and filled the pair of Golden Threat Jade Cups on the table with the wine from the flagon.

Elder Hu Yan immediately picked up one of the cups, then began to carefully inspect it right in front of his eye.

The wine in the cup was of a vibrant red color, and it was giving off a fiery red glow. The wine itself was translucent, and with a slight shake of the cup, specks of red light could be seen dancing over the surface of the wine like tiny flames.

Elder Hu Yan eagerly brought the teacup to his lips, then took a small sip, upon which a look of surprise and elation instantly appeared on his face. He then tipped his head back and downed the rest of the wine in the cup in one go.

As soon as the wine entered his belly, it transformed into a surge of warmth that flowed throughout his entire body, and the red coloration of his nose instantly became even more pronounced.

He closed his eyes as he savored the lingering flavor of the wine in his mouth, and a blissful look appeared on his face.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

After returning to his senses, Elder Hu Yan immediately said, "This is truly an extraordinarily exquisite wine. Where did you get this wine from? I've never tasted it before."

"This wine is called the Fire Drop Wine, and it's produced on the Primordial Wave Continent. However, due to the fact that the recipe has already been lost, it's very difficult to find nowadays," Han Li explained.

"What? The recipe has been lost?"

This revelation struck Elder Hu Yan like a bolt of lightning, causing his voice to spike up a few octaves.

However, he then quickly calmed down again as he asked, "If the recipe has already been lost, then how did you get your hands on this wine?"

"I'm afraid that's a question I can't answer. All I want to know is if the recipe for this wine is enough to exchange for your knowledge in Dao Warriors," Han Li said in a direct and straightforward manner.

A hesitant look appeared on Elder Hu Yan's face as he sat back down in his chair, and he appeared to have been quite conflicted.

However, Han Li could see that Elder Hu Yan was constantly glancing at the red wine flagong in his hand out of the corner of his eye, and it was clear that he wanted both the recipe and the flagon of wine.

Sure enough, it didn't take long before Elder Hu Yan caved.

"So be it. You and I get along quite well with each other, so as long as you give me the wine recipe and that flagon of Fire Drop Wine, I can impart my knowledge in Dao Warriors onto you."

"I'm afraid that won't do, Senior. Our prior agreement only concerned a wine recipe, and I only have a single flagon of this Fire Drop Wine, so I can't just give it to you free of charge," Han Li said.

Elder Hu Yan was immediately able to read between the lines, and he glared at Han Li as he asked, "You can't give it to me free of charge, you say? Fine, what else do you want from me?"

"I also wanted to learn from you how to plant spirit plants into pots, like in the case of this one," Han Li replied with a slightly embarrassed smile.

Elder Hu Yan immediately burst into laughter upon hearing this. "That's not a problem at all! I can teach you that."

Han Li was rather surprised by how willing Elder Hu Yan was to impart this knowledge, but after hearing the planting method, he realized why Elder Hu Yan wasn't reluctant at all to give this piece of knowledge away.

As it turned out, this type of planting method wasn't complex at all. What was difficult about it was finding containers suitable for holding spirit plants, as well as spirit fluids that can supply the spirit plants with sufficient spiritual power.

The black pot that Elder Hu Yan was using for the potted plant on the table was a treasure that was capable of absorbing the world's origin qi, and that was why the spirit plant planted within it was able to thrive even though it had been taken from the earth.

Furthermore, this type of planting method was only applicable to an extremely small selection of spirit plants.

"I didn't think there would be so many restrictions. What a pity..." Han Li sighed.

"Now that I've given you what you wanted, you better hand over that flagon of wine and its recipe to me," Elder Hu Yan urged with a pleased smile.

Han Li handed the flagon of wine over to Elder Hu Yan, then flipped a hand over to produce a copy of the wine recipe, which he set down onto the table.

Elder Hu Yan grabbed the flagon, then removed the wooden stopper before taking another whiff. He then began to carefully read through the recipe while murmuring his observations to himself. "As expected, 10,000-year-old Arhat Leaves were used... Oh, and there's Bright Stone Flower as well... I see..."

Han Li could see that Elder Hu Yan was completely absorbed in his reading, so he didn't interrupt him. He reached out to grab the cup of wine on the table that he had poured for himself, only for Elder Hu Yan to immediately slap his hand away.

"All of this wine belongs to me now!"

A grabbed the cup as he spoke before downing its contents in one go, then began smacking his lips in pleasure.

Han Li naturally wasn't offended by this, and he asked, "Can we talk about Dao Warriors now, Senior?"

Elder Hu Yan stowed the flagon and the wine recipe away, following which a serious look appeared on his face as he said, "I didn't think you would actually be able to acquire such an exceptional wine recipe. What do you want to know?"

Han Li paused for a moment, then asked, "These Dao Warriors appear similar to puppets, but are also quite different, and I wanted to know exactly what they were."

Elder Hu Yan considered the question for a moment, then replied, "That's a rather difficult question to answer. Dao Warriors could start off as a number of things, such as cultivators who sold themselves as slaves, powerful demon beasts, puppets refined in special ways, heavenly devils with established contracts, mutated ghosts, artifact spirits... Even spirits born in spirit domains are technically Dao Warriors."

"What category do those Dao Warriors that can sprout from those yellow beans fall into?" Han Li asked.

"Oh, you're talking about Bean Warriors. They're a type of plant Dao Warrior, and they fall under the puppet category. They need to be planted, then refined, and the power of the Bean Warriors will vary depending on how long the beans were nurtured and the potency of the arrays inscribed upon them," Elder Hu Yan explained.

Chapter 233: Planting a Bean Warrior

"I see. Aside from being useful in battle, what else can Dao Warriors be used for?" Han Li asked.

"Depending on where a Dao Warrior came from, it could possess certain special talents, and it'll be absolutely obedient to its owner. If you have a sufficient number of Dao Warriors, you can even use them to assemble various types of arrays, thereby making them powerful allies," Elder Hu Yan replied.

"If there are so many benefits to owning Dao Warriors, then wouldn't everyone try to procure them? Why is it that they seem to be extremely rare?" Han Li asked.

"What do you take Dao Warriors for, kid? How can they be considered to be precious if any ordinary immortal is able to use them? A huge amount of time, energy, and resources are required to develop Dao Warriors, and even then, there's still some luck involved, so not all immortals have the required resources and ability to obtain them.

“Even Bean Warriors, which are considered to be among the lower third grade of Daw Warriors, are extremely rare," Elder Hu Yan explained.

"Thank you for explaining all of this to me, Elder Hu Yan. Would you be able to tell me exactly how these Dao Warriors are refined?" Han Li asked as he cupped his fist toward Elder Hu Yan in a grateful salute.

"Seeing as you were able to bring me such a fantastic wine recipe, I'll pass my knowledge in nurturing Bean Warriors to you. However, make sure you don't give this information to anyone else! Also, I quite like this pair of Golden Thread Jade Cups, so I'll accept them as a gift from you," Elder Hu Yan said as a sly grin appeared on his face.

Before Han Li had a chance to reply, Elder Hu Yan gently swept a sleeve over the table to stow the pair of cups away.

At the same time, a thin yellow paper book appeared on the table.

Han Li was feeling a little exasperated, but he was already familiar with Elder Hu Yan's personality, and he naturally wasn't going to say anything. He picked up the thin book before flipping through a few of its pages, then carefully stowed it away.

The book was completely unremarkable in appearance, but it really did contain information on the method required to plant Bean Warriors, so this was something that he would have to study in further detail once he returned to his cave abode.

"Thank you, Senior," he said as he extended another salute of gratitude.

"Don't worry about it, both of us got what we wanted, so neither of us owe each other anything. I'm really busy right now, so I have no time to entertain you," Elder Hu Yan said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

That was clearly Han Li's cue to depart, and he willingly obliged.

After leaving the High Profound Palace, he returned straight to the Crimson Dawn Peak, where he entered his cave abode and immediately went to the small spirit medicine field.

At this point, quite a few spirit medicines had already been planted here, and the giant ape puppet that was responsible for tending to them was situated nearby.

Han Li made his way to a vacant plot of land in the southwestern corner of the field, then crouched down before using his hands to dig a small hole into the soft and loamy soil. After that, he flipped a hand over to produce a walnut-sized yellow bean, which he tossed into the hole before covering it with soil.

This yellow bean was none other than the primary bean that he had obtained from the golden giant in the Origin Realm Temple of the Spirit Domain Realm.

According to the book that Elder Hu Yan had given to him, after a Bean Warrior was planted, it would require a long time to germinate, but it was impossible to predict exactly how much time it would take.

There were disparities in the time required for Bean Warriors of different varieties and even different specimens from the same variety of Bean Warrior to germinate, and the quality of the Bean Warriors, the soil that they were planted in, and the spirit liquid used to nurture them all played huge roles.

On the subject of spirit liquids, there was most likely no better option than the spirit liquid produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial.

All of the spirit liquid in the vial had already been used up on maturing the spirit medicines planted in this field, so he would have to wait until the next time the vial produced spirit liquid to administer the first dose to the bean.

After doing all of that, Han Li took a glance at the spirit medicines in the field, of which several were already approaching 50,000 years in age.

These spirit medicines were at an age where they could be used, but he had no suitable pill recipe for them.

There were avenues in the sect through which pill recipes could be obtained, but pill refinement was a skill that required practice, and pills that could enhance the cultivation base of True Immortal cultivators had to have been quite difficult to refine. With his skills in pill refinement, he could give it a try, but in all likelihood, he would have to fail numerous times before finding success.

With his current stash of spirit stones and Immortal Origin Stones, he could be considered to have been quite wealthy among early-True Immortal cultivators, but it most likely wasn't going to be enough once he began dabbling in pill refinement.

Having said that, he did have quite a large stash of low and mid-tier treasures, materials, and other things laying around. He would have to plan out how to sell them in batches to fund his future pill refinement endeavors.

However, prior to that, there were a few other things that he had to take care of.

With that in mind, he returned to his secret chamber, and after taking a seat with his legs crossed, he flipped a hand over to produce an intricate storage bracelet, out of which emerged a large collection of different items.

This storage bracelet was the one that he had taken from that elderly man that had appeared in the Profound Ice Mountain Range.

Somehow, the man seemed to have gathered some information on what had happened to Elder Bai Fengyi, and it was unclear what his objectives were for trying to abduct Bai Suyuan.

It was a pity that he was unable to capture the man's nascent soul. Otherwise, he would've been able to perform a soul search technique.

It didn't take long before Han Li had split up the contents of the storage bracelet into different categories in an expert fashion, following which he stowed them away to leave only three items behind, namely a dark golden chunk of metal with some type of pattern all over its surface and a pair of jade boxes.

Both of the jade boxes had white talismans that were glowing with spiritual light adhered to them, clearly indicating that they held very important items inside.

The first thing that he did was pick up the chunk of metal for inspection. It was around the size of a watermelon and was the exact same as those few pieces of metal that he had obtained from the Origin Mirage Beast.

Han Li was rather intrigued at the sight of the chunk of metal.

The Origin Mirage Beast had been collecting this material, and it was also present in the elderly man's storage bracelet, so it had to have some type of special uses.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he stowed the chunk of metal away. Prior to this, he hadn't paid much heed to this material, but it seemed that he would have to find some time to have the material appraised so he could find out exactly what it was.

After that, Han Li picked up one of the jade boxes, and bright azure light began to emanate from his hand as he pointed at the talismans adhered to the box.

The talismans immediately began to glow with dazzling white light in an effort to resist him, but Han Li merely flicked a finger through the air with a cold smile on his face, and several streaks of azure sword qi were released before shredding through the white talismans.

After being severed into pieces, the white talismans were rendered completely useless, and Han Li was able to open the jade box.

Inside, he discovered a palm-sized white badge that had a rather peculiar appearance. It was thin and long, and its edges weren't very even, as if it were something that had been casually crafted out of jade by a child.

Han Li picked up the badge to give it a closer inspection, and he discovered that the material was glittering and translucent, and it was giving off a gentle glow.

It was definitely no ordinary material, but he couldn't identify it. However, it was clear from how carefully it had been stored that this was something that the elderly man had held in high regard.

Han Li then employed several secret techniques to thoroughly inspect both the inside and the outside of the badge, but still wasn't able to discover anything.

With a shake of his head, he placed the badge back into the jade box before stowing it away.

Seeing as he couldn't figure out what it was, he would just have to leave it for another time.

Finally, Han Li picked up the other jade badge before removing the talismans on the outside using the same method as before.

Inside this jade box was a book that was yellow with age, and its pages seemed to have been made from some type of beasthide.

Han Li picked up the book, but after briefly flipping through its pages, he shook his head before placing it back in the jade box.

The book had no cover or name, but judging from the content that it contained, it appeared to have been a book about tool refinement. There were many techniques in the book for refining and enhancing treasures, but it was a little niche.

There were still many other things that he had to take care of for now, so he decided to spend time studying the book for now.

After stowing the second jade box away, Han Li made a hand seal, and the Heavy Water True Axis appeared before him.

Blue light flashed within his eyes as he made a beckoning motion with one hand, and a small ball of heavy water flew out of his True Water Pouch before slowly approaching the Heavy Water True Axis.

At the moment, the axis was revolving on the spot while giving off a faint black glow.

As the ball of heavy water approached the axis, the Water Dao Rune on the latter instantly began to release a watery blue glow, as well as bursts of faint law powers.

The suction force that had emerged during Han Li's battle against the elderly man also appeared once again, and the ball of heavy water was drawn straight into the Heavy Water True Axis, which became slightly heavier as a result.

Han Li was very pleased to see this. Just as he had anticipated, the Heavy Water True Axis really was capable of absorbing more heavy water.

With a flick of his wrist, a volume of heavy water that was enough to fill an entire bucket surged forth before flowing toward the Heavy Water True Axis.

The Water Dao Rune on the Heavy Water True Axis radiated dazzling blue light as it quickly devoured most of the heavy water, but right at this moment, an unexpected turn of events unfolded.

The Water Dao Rune flashed a few more times before suddenly turning dark, and the axis also stopped devouring heavy water.

At the same time, most of Han Li's spiritual connection with the Heavy Water True Axis abruptly faded, and the axis came plummeting down toward the ground.

Thankfully, Han Li was able to react quickly enough to catch the axis before it hit the ground, but his arm sank down involuntarily from its enormous weight.

Having absorbed so much heavy water, the axis had become significantly heavier than before.

What just happened?

Initially, he had only refined the Heavy Water True Axis as a smokescreen to keep his Mantra True Axis hidden, but he had since discovered that it was extremely useful in battle, and he certainly didn't want to lose his spiritual connection to it.

Chapter 234: Monkey Wine

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li stowed the rest of the heavy water away, then injected his spiritual sense into the axis in an attempt to find out what was happening.

However, as soon as his spiritual sense entered the axis, he felt a burst of enormous churning inside like turbulent waves of the sea, and his spiritual sense was forced out.

After that, he spent close to half a day employing several different methods to find out what had changed within the Heavy Water True Axis, but all to no avail, leaving him to stare at the axis with tightly furrowed brows.

Could it be that the axis underwent some type of mutation after absorbing the heavy water?

Back when he refined the Heavy Water True Axis, he had followed the refinement method recorded in the Mantra Axis Scripture, and he hadn't completely familiarized himself with the fundamental principles of the treasure, so it wasn't impossible for it to have undergone some type of mutation.

With that in mind, Han Li was beginning to regret not taking the Heavy Water True Axis more seriously, but those emotions weren't going to help him.

At this point, he had to focus on thinking of a way to save the axis. He certainly didn't have enough time and resources to refine another one.

There was still a faint connection left between himself and the axis, so he pressed the axis against his lower abdomen where his dantian was, then activated this connection with all his might.

A layer of black light appeared over the Heavy Water True Axis, and it entered his dantian in a flash, residing peacefully in there like before.

The fact that Han Li was able to draw the axis back into his dantian meant that he hadn't completely lost it.

He immediately sat up straight and directed all of the immortal spiritual power in his dantian to envelop the Heavy Water True Axis, and his nascent soul also released bursts of nascent flames to encompass the entire axis.

The Water Dao Runes on the Heavy Water True Axis began to glow faintly, while the axis itself began to spin slowly again.

An elated look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he continued this process.

An entire month passed by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, Han Li opened his eyes before sweeping a sleeve through the air, and the Heavy Water True Axis emerged with its spiritual connection to Han Li completely restored.

Not only that, but the color of the Water Dao Rune on its surface seemed to have become slightly darker.

As the axis revolved in mid-air, it released bursts of tremendous force that caused the surrounding space to tremble and quiver.

Han Li was extremely relieved to see this. Not only had the Heavy Water True Axis's weight increased significantly, its power had been given a slight boost as well.

He drew the axis into his grasp, then began to gently stroke its surface.

There were quite a few people in the Blaze Dragon Dao who had cultivated the Mantra Axis Scripture, but never had he heard of anyone creating a faux axis capable of absorbing one of the materials that it had been refined from, and he didn't know if this had something to do with the refinement process, or perhaps it was related to the materials used.

In any case, this was definitely a good thing.

Previously, the Heavy Water True Axis had resembled someone who had consumed too much food at once, resulting in indigestion.

A hint of anticipation coupled with unease appeared in Han Li's eyes as he placed the Heavy Water True Axis in the air in front of himself, then sent a ball of heavy water around the size of a human head drifting toward it.

The Water Dao Rune on the axis began to glow blue once again, and it quickly devoured the entire ball of heavy water.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he clapped his hands together with glee.

He had just confirmed that the Heavy Water True Axis was able to keep absorbing heavy water.

Each intake of heavy water wasn't able to enhance the power of the axis by much, but if he were to repeat this process over and over again, he could envision the axis eventually becoming several times, even over 10 times more powerful than it currently was.

The Heavy Water True Axis was quite formidable to begin with, and once it reached its full potential, it would truly be a force to be reckoned with.

With that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but grow a little excited again.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he brought out another large ball of heavy water that descended onto the axis.

The Water Dao Rune on the axis lit up as it began to devour the heavy water again.

However, only about half of the ball of heavy water had been devoured when the axis suddenly fell dark again, and Han Li's spiritual connection with it was once again severely compromised as it fell out of the air, only to be caught by Han Li.

After these two cycles, Han Li was able to roughly determine that the Heavy Water True Axis was able to absorb roughly a bucket's worth of heavy water per intake.

With that in mind, he stowed the Heavy Water True Axis back into his dantian to be refined with his nascent flame.

Over two years passed by in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes sprang open as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a ball of black light flew out of his body.

It was none other than the Heavy Water True Axis, and as soon as it emerged, the space within the secret chamber instantly began to shudder, while a burst of rumbling that resembled faint thunderclaps rang out.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

During the past two years, he had remained exclusively in his secret chamber, focusing on feeding the Heavy Water True Axis more heavy water while also manifesting crystals to be sent to his Earthly Deity Avatar.

After over 20 more intakes of heavy water, the Heavy Water True Axis had become at least three times more powerful than before.

However, after absorbing so much heavy water, the rate at which the axis was absorbing heavy water was becoming slower, and the volume of each intake was also decreasing.

It was still able to absorb more, but Han Li could sense that it was about to reach its limit.

Even so, the Heavy Water True Axis had already become extremely fearsome.

With that in mind, he stowed the axis away before making his way outside.

The gate of the cave abode opened, and Han Li emerged.

A figure quickly approached him from a nearby room, and it was none other than Sun Buzheng, who appeared to have been waiting for him.

"Sun Buzheng pays his respects to Elder Li."

"Is there something you need to speak to me about?" Han Li asked.

"Elder Li, all of the spirit fields in your territory have already been cleared up, and I wanted to ask which types of spirit plants you wanted to have planted in these fields," Sun Buzheng replied in a respectful manner.

Han Li nodded in response, then flipped a hand over to produce a storage pouch that he handed to Sun Buzheng. "The seeds and the planting methods are all in here. Just do as the instructions say."

"Yes, Elder Li," Sun Buzheng accepted the storage pouch before departing.

Han Li took a few steps forward, then looked down from his vantage point.

Some restrictions had been set up around the spirit fields at the foot of the mountain, and Meng Qianqian and the others were all busy at work, tending to the fields.

Meanwhile, the Two-headed Griffin was soaring through the air nearby, constantly patrolling the area.

Han Li nodded with a pleased expression upon seeing this. He didn't have a large number of servants, but even so, his territory was beginning to look quite prosperous.

A smile appeared on his face, and in the next instant, he abruptly vanished from the spot before reappearing near a waterfall at the foot of the Crimson Dawn Peak.

The weather was becoming even colder, and the entire landscape was covered in snow. Even the water had mostly frozen, reduced to only around a third of its original size.

Thankfully, the spiritual qi around the Crimson Dawn Peak was quite abundant, so the valley was still filled with lush greenery.

After taking a brief glance at his surroundings, Han Li summoned his Heavy Water True Axis, yet before he had a chance to do anything, an elated cry suddenly rang out from nearby.

Han Li turned in that direction, and a smile appeared on his face.

As it turned out, a group of monkeys were playing in the nearby forest, and it seemed that they were the same ones that he had run into last time.

All of a sudden, a large crimson monkey sprang out of the forest, then landed not far away from Han Li, and it was none other than the monkey king.

The monkey king had become more physically imposing since last time, and its crimson fur had also become more vibrant.

Furthermore, it was only very faint, but it was giving off a burst of demonic qi fluctuations.

"Looks like you've made some good progress in your cultivation," Han Li remarked with a smile.

A grateful look appeared in the monkey king's eyes as it knelt down onto the ground before kowtowing respectfully to Han Li.

The other monkeys also jumped down to pay their respects to Han Li.

"I did give you some minor assistance last time we met, but your aptitude is the main reason behind the progress you've been able to make. On top of that, you're residing in a blessed paradise, so even without my help, you would've been able to reach this level with a few more years of cultivation," Han Li said as he clasped his hands behind his back.

The monkey king shook its head as it attempted to communicate something to Han Li, following which it swept an arm through the air.

One of the monkeys behind it immediately jumped forward with a yellow gourd in its hands, which it set down in front of Han Li.

The aroma of wine was wafting out from within the gourd, and Han Li was silent for a moment as he glanced at the gourd on the ground before asking, "Could it be that you've been waiting here for me this entire time?"

The monkey king immediately nodded in response.

Han Li was rather touched by this gesture, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a ball of azure light, which split up into several dozen bursts, each of which surged into one of the monkeys present.

All of the monkeys immediately cried out in elation.

He then produced a pill that he tossed at the monkey king, and the latter immediately caught the pill in its mouth before swallowing it.

A burst of crimson light appeared over its body, and only after a long while did it subside, following which the demonic qi radiating from the monkey king's body became significantly more pronounced. An ecstatic look appeared on its face as he pushed the yellow gourd closer to Han Li's foot.

"Did you brew this wine yourselves? I have previously heard that monkey wine is extremely sweet and delectable, I didn't think I would ever get to taste it," Han Li said with a smile as he picked up the gourd before removing the stopper.

The aroma of the wine inside instantly became 10 times stronger, and it flowed straight into his nostrils as if it had a mind of its own.

A hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face. He had only picked up the gourd as he didn't want to disappoint these thoughtful monkeys, but the fragrance of the monkey wine was unexpectedly delectable, and his eyes immediately lit up as he took a small sip.

Not only was the wine extremely delicious, it had a special aroma, and it wasn't inferior even compared with the immortal wines that Han Li had tried from Elder Hu Yan's collection.

"How are you able to brew such fine wine? Is there some secret?" Han Li asked.

The monkey king scratched its head as a hesitant look appeared on its face.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this. The monkey king's hesitant reaction indicated that they really did have a secret, and it would be extremely useful if he could obtain this secret. Despite how erratic Elder Hu Yan was, it seemed that he was quite an important figure in the sect, and there was a good chance that Han Li would have to interact with him in the future.

Right as he was about to pull out a few pills to offer a deal to the monkey king, it suddenly cried out before turning and rushing away into the distance.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, and the monkey king rushed to over 100 feet away before stopping in its tracks and turning around to call out to Han Li.

Han Li followed along behind the monkey king, and the other monkeys also trailed along behind him.

The monkey king moved as swiftly as the wind, quickly covering close to 10 kilometers before arriving at a mountain stream.

The weather here was warmer, but the landscape was very rocky, and there wasn't much vegetation.

There was an even larger waterfall here, and it was giving off a loud rumbling while water vapor churned all around it, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

The monkey king leaped straight into the waterfall, and Han Li raised an eyebrow before following along.

Upon passing through the waterfall, they arrived in a massive cave.

Chapter 235: An Offering from the Monkey King

The cave appeared to have been formed naturally, and it wasn't special in any way compared with most of the caves on the mountain.

The cave was quite spacious, around 200 to 300 feet in area, and there were several small caves inside that appeared to have been the homes for these monkeys. A tender cry rang out from one of the smaller caves as several small monkeys poked their heads out, only to be immediately pulled back by the arm of another monkey.

Immediately thereafter, a female monkey appeared at the entrance of the cave, looking at Han Li with a cautious expression as it let loose a threatening cry.

The monkey king immediately responded with an authoritative roar, and the female monkey's expression instantly changed as it ducked back into the cave.

The monkey king turned to Han Li to deliver what seemed to have been an apology, then continued onward, quickly reaching the deepest cave.

This was a rather small cave that was only several dozen feet in area, and the entire cave was filled with a rich wine aroma that was coming from a cauldron that was taller than a grown man.

The cauldron was gray in color, and it seemed to have been constructed from some type of unknown rock. It was a round cauldron that was supported by three feet, and there was a lid on the cauldron that was shaped like a conical bamboo hat.

There were eight large runes engraved onto the surface of the cauldron, giving it a remarkable appearance, but the cauldron wasn't giving off even the slightest aura, appearing as if it were nothing more than an ordinary cauldron.

The monkey king cried out a few times as it pointed at the cauldron, then jumped onto it before lifting the lid.

Most of the cauldron was filled with a light red liquid, which was giving off the same aroma as the monkey wine in the gourd.

However, it was clear that the brewing process wasn't yet complete for this batch of wine as it was still looking a little murky.

There were many pieces of fruit skin and cores littered around the cauldron, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

He pointed at the fruit scraps on the ground as he asked, "This is what you used to brew your wine?"

The monkey king immediately nodded in response.

Han Li fell silent as he made his way over to the cauldron, and after inspecting it carefully for some time, his eyes gradually lit up.

All of the fruit scraps on the ground belonged to some common wild fruits in the mountains, but due to the fact that they were growing in the Bell Toll Mountain Range, all of them contained some of the world's origin qi. Even so, they could only have been considered to be the most ordinary of spirit fruits.

The fact that these monkeys were able to brew such exquisite wine with such simple ingredients had to have had something to do with their wine brewing expertise, but the main contributing factor was most likely this mysterious stone cauldron.

Han Li inspected the cauldron for a moment, then pressed his hand against it and slowly injected his immortal spiritual power into it, but the cauldron displayed no reaction.

His brows furrowed slightly as he increased the rate of immortal spiritual power outflow while also simultaneously injecting his spiritual sense into the cauldron as well.

The eight runes on the surface of the cauldron suddenly lit up slightly, but then immediately fell dark again.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes as he withdrew his immortal spiritual power and spiritual sense.

He still wasn't able to uncover exactly what was so special about this stone cauldron, but it was clearly no ordinary cauldron.

"Where did you get this cauldron from?" he asked as he turned to the monkey king.

The monkey king scratched its head for a moment, then pointed at the cave and tried to communicate something to Han Li.

"You're saying it was always here to begin with?" Han Li asked.

The monkey king immediately nodded in response with an elated expression.

Han Li fell silent upon seeing this.

This was a cave that had been formed naturally, so how had such a mysterious stone cauldron appeared here? Could it be that someone had put it here?

In any case, at the very least, this stone cauldron was clearly a brilliant treasure for brewing wine.

At this moment, some other monkeys also entered the cave and began to play. As a result, the quiet cave instantly became quite lively.

Many of the monkeys were looking into the deepest cave, but none of them stepped inside.

Han Li took a glance outside, then quickly withdrew his gaze as he asked, "This stone cauldron is very useful to me. Would you be able to give it to me? Of course, I'm not going to just take it from you. Here, you can have your pick out of these pills and spirit fruits, or anything else you may like."

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a bunch of items as he spoke.

The monkey king's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of the pills and spirit fruits, but it then shook its head vigorously, as if to free itself from temptation.

After refusing Han Li's proposal, it pointed in the direction of the Crimson Dawn Peak in the distance.

"You want me to take you live on the Crimson Dawn Peak?" Han Li asked.

The monkey nodded vigorously in response, following which a thought occurred to it, and it pointed at the monkeys outside.

"You want me to take them with me as well?" Han Li asked.

The monkey king nodded in response as a hopeful look appeared on its eyes.

The monkeys outside also seemed to have sensed that this was an important moment, and all of them instantly fell silent.

"I can do that. The spiritual qi on the Crimson Dawn Peak is far more abundant than it is here, but it's also a lot colder. Will you be able to handle it?" Han Li asked.

The monkey king nodded vigorously as it thumped its own chest.

Han Li stowed his offerings away, then said, "In that case, I'll take all of you to the Crimson Dawn Peak once you're prepared for the move."

The monkey king cried out in excitement, then rushed out of the cave before calling out loudly to its brethren, and it was met with a wave of ecstatic cheers.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he turned to the stone cauldron, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, stowing the cauldron away along with the batch of unfinished monkey wine instead.

A pleased smile appeared on his face as he made his way out of the cave.

Moments later, a streak of azure light shot out of the waterfall before hurtling away into the distance, flying for several thousand feet before stopping to reveal none other than Han Li.

He had arrived in a rather desolate area with sparse vegetation and only a few black mountains, all of which were covered in a thick layer of snow.

He gently exhaled before rubbing his hands together, and his Heavy Water True Axis emerged.

He chanted an incantation as he activated the axis, and much to his surprise, the immortal spiritual power in his body was being sucked away by the Heavy Water True Axis like flood water out of a broken dam.

Before he had a chance to do anything, the Heavy Water True Axis began to glow with dazzling bright light while expanding to several times its original size in the blink of an eye.

A burst of formidable spiritual pressure erupted out of the axis alongside a series of black halos that proliferated outward in all directions, and the sound of crashing waves could be heard as well.

All of the world's origin qi within a radius of thousands of kilometers was swept up into a frenzy, and countless specks of blue light appeared before converging toward a certain spot.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which an elated look appeared in his eyes.

The Heavy Water True Axis had swelled to the size of a house, and it was rapidly revolving while giving off piercing black light. The Water Dao Rune on its surface was also glowing a bright blue, and the blue and black light seemed to have been feeding off one another, becoming brighter and brighter until it was as if there were a black and blue sun hovering in mid-air.

At the same time, bursts of invisible fluctuations surged forth in a frenzy, becoming more powerful with each successive wave. The nearby space also began to tremble violently, while gusts of fierce wind swept through the surrounding air.

After a brief pause, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and the massive Heavy Water True Axis immediately hurtled through the air before crashing toward the ground.

The ground and the sky began to tremble violently in unison, as if doomsday had descended.

Ripples of black and blue light surged through the air in all directions, sweeping up ferocious gusts of wind that swept away the snow on the ground with ease while also stripping away the top layer of earth beneath the snow.

The clouds in the sky were also churning violently as they spread into the distance like turbulent waves.

The Crimson Dawn Peak that was several thousand kilometers away also shuddered as an immeasurable volume of snow came crashing down.

Sun Buzheng and the others, who were tending to the spirit fields at the foot of the mountain, all looked at one another with surprised expressions, and no one knew what had happened.

"Could it be that Elder Li is using some type of cultivation art? But it doesn't feel like the tremors are coming from the mountaintop," someone mused.

"Who else could cause such a massive commotion aside from Elder Li? He only just came out of seclusion, so perhaps he's mastered some cultivation art of unmatched power or has refined a treasure and is testing it out," Sun Buzheng said as he turned to the direction that the tremors were coming from with a hint of longing in his eyes.

Meng Qianqian also turned to that direction with a look of admiration on her face.

Several thousand kilometers away, the earth-shattering tremors finally faded, and the dust settled to reveal the scene down below.

An enormous chasm that was several thousand feet wide had appeared on the ground, and it extended in either direction as far as the eyes could see, as if the entire earth had been split in half.

Furthermore, the chasm was extremely deep, and faint glimmers of fiery red light could be seen at the bottom, indicating that it reached all the way down into the lava beneath the earth.

The nearby mountains had completely vanished, clearly having already been destroyed.

Han Li was standing in mid-air with the Heavy Water True Axis hovering beside him, and it had already reverted back to its original size.

His face was slightly pale, and around a third of all of his immortal spiritual power had been exhausted from unleashing that all-out attack with the Heavy Water True Axis.

However, there was an elated look on his face.

The Heavy Water True Axis had become far more powerful than he anticipated, and if he were to use it in battle, it would be no less powerful than an Acquired Immortal Treasure of a very high caliber.

He took a deep breath, and his complexion quickly returned to normal. He then stowed the Heavy Water True Axis away before flying toward the Crimson Dawn Peak as a streak of azure light.

……

Half a day later, Han Li appeared in a massive cave halfway up the Crimson Dawn Peak.

He inspected his surroundings briefly, then flicked a finger through the air in rapid succession.

Streaks of sword qi erupted in all directions, shredding through the mountain rock like tofu, quickly digging out around a dozen smaller caves with surfaces that were extraordinarily smooth.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, and with a sweep of his sleeve, the monkeys from the foot of the mountain appeared in the cave amid a flash of light.

The monkeys looked around, and ecstatic looks quickly appeared on their faces as they began to explore their new home.

The monkey king was just as ecstatic as its brethren, and it immediately fell to its knees and kowtowed to Han Li over and over again.

"You can all live here from now on. If you encounter any trouble or difficulties, you can go to the mountaintop to seek out my servants," Han Li said.

The monkey king hurriedly nodded in response.

In the next instant, Han Li had already vanished from the spot.

All of the other monkeys rushed over to the monkey king, and after looking at one another for a moment, all of them kowtowed toward the spot where Han Li had been standing just a moment ago.

At this point, Han Li had already returned to his cave abode on the mountaintop, and he placed the stone cauldron down in a room before setting a few restrictions.

After that, he made his way to his secret chamber.

At this point, the three regular elder missions had already been completed, and the Heavy Water True Axis had also become about as powerful as it could be in its current form, so it was time to think about pills.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he sat down with his legs crossed.

Chapter 236: Initial Dabbles in Immortal Pills

Half a month later.

In the central region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range was a very-strange looking lone mountain. The top and bottom of the mountain were round and full, but the middle of the mountain was tapered, thereby giving it the appearance of a giant gourd.

The mountain was fittingly named Gourd Peak, and just like the Imperial Dragon Peak, it was also one of the most important mountains in the entire Blaze Dragon Dao.

The mountain wasn't very precarious, and it was less than 10,000 feet tall. At the foot of the mountain was an extremely fine spirit spring that was sufficient to nurture all of the living beings on the mountain. As a result, all of the plant life on the mountain was green and vibrant all year round.

The entire mountain was enveloped within an extremely secure protective array that was constantly activated. Hence, any elders or disciples who wanted to enter the mountain, regardless of whether they were from the inner or outer sect, could only do so through the teleportation hall at the foot of the mountain.

The reason why this mountain was so tightly guarded was because almost all of the pills in the entire Blaze Dragon Dao came from this mountain, and it was also home to all of the pill refinement masters in the sect.

Of course, earthly pill masters who were capable of refining pills fit for consumption for immortals were the most revered figures on the Gourd Peak.

If an early-True Immortal cultivator were to progress at the normal rate of cultivation, it would take anywhere between centuries to tens of thousands of years to open up a single immortal acupoint, and each successive immortal acupoint was only going to be more difficult to open. However, if they had access to the appropriate pills to aid them in their cultivation, then that timeframe could be severely shortened.

However, in order to refine pills of that caliber, spirit medicines that were tens of thousands of years old had to be used as the main ingredient, and even the supplementary ingredients were extremely rare and precious. To make matters even worse, even a seasoned Earthly Pill Master's pill refinement success rate when it came to refining pills of this caliber was generally pitifully low.

This was why only normally major sects or prominent cultivating powers could afford to nurture Earthly Pill Masters.

At this moment, Han Li was emerging from the teleportation hall near the Gourd Peak, and he arrived at the foot of the mountain before making his way into a golden palace.

The palace was closely connected to the array that encompassed the entirety of Gourd Peak, and it was the only entrance into the mountain.

After having his identity verified, Han Li stepped straight into a teleportation array at the center of the palace, then vanished on the spot amid a flash of white light.

Shortly thereafter, he appeared in a red palace on the mountain summit.

The interior layout of the palace appeared to have been no different from that of a mortal drugstore, with a counter at the front and apothecary cabinets at the back. The only difference was that there were clear restrictions placed upon the cabinet grids that contained earthly pills.

There were very few people in the hall, only a pair of attendant elders and several inner sect elders who had come to purchase pills.

As soon as Han Li came in, he was approached by a friendly-looking middle-aged attendant elder, who said, "My name is Ye Nanfeng, and I'm an attendant here at the Immortal Medicine Pavilion. Can I help you with something, Fellow Daoist?"

"My name is Li Feiyu, and I would like to purchase some pills that can aid me in my cultivation," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"I see. In that case, allow me to recommend a few types of pills to you, Fellow Daoist Li," Ye Nanfeng said with a smile.

"Thank you," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Given your current cultivation base, the most commonly used pill to aid in your cultivation would be this Origin Unifying Pill. Each vial contains 10 pills and only costs 200 merit points. If you want something a bit better, then you can try the Spirit Sign Pill. However, it'll also be a bit more expensive, costing 500 merit points for each vial of 10 pills," Ye Nanfeng introduced.

Han Li had already come into this mentally prepared, but he was still shocked by the prices of the pills.

Even after completing the three regular elder missions, he still hadn't managed to save up 500 merit points, so these pills were truly quite steep in price.

"This Spirit Sign Pill is truly not cheap," Han Li remarked with a wry smile.

"Of course. The only one in our entire sect capable of refining the Spirit Sign Pill is Master Hu Yan, so it's available in only very limited supply," Ye Nanfeng explained with a smile.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear the mention of "Master Hu Yan" in this context.

Could it be that the erratic old drunkard was also a high-grade Earthly Pill Master?

"If neither of those two types of pills are to your liking, then you can try this Spring Rain Pill. It's a little cheaper than the Spirit Sign Pill, but it's more efficacious than the Origin Unifying Pill, giving you the best value for your money," Ye Nanfeng continued.

"Elder Ye, may I ask if any pill recipes are sold in the Immortal Medicine Pavilion?" Han Li suddenly asked.

Ye Nanfeng faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Could it be that you're planning to refine pills for yourself, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"Not at all. I just so happen to know someone who recently became an Earthly Pill Master, and he agreed to refine pills for me as long as I can provide him with the recipes and spirit ingredients," Han Li replied.

Ye Nanfeng clearly wanted to dissuade Han Li from this course of action, but ultimately held his tongue.

Han Li knew that Ye Nanfeng wanted to tell him that as opposed to purchasing pill recipes and ingredients and counting on someone else, it was a much better idea to simply purchase the pills directly.

In the end, Ye Nanfeng decided not to offer any words of advice, and he replied, "Both the recipes for the Origin Unifying Pill and the Spring Rain Pill are available for sale, but sales of the recipe for the Spirit Sign Pill are prohibited without express approval from Master Hu Yan."

"How many merit points will the two pill recipes cost?" Han Li asked.

"The recipe for the Origin Unifying Pill costs 50 merit points, while the recipe for the Spring Rain Pill costs 150," Ye Nanfeng replied.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he was wondering which recipe would be better for him to purchase.

Ye Nanfeng smiled as he reminded in a thoughtful manner, "I suggest you take a look at the ingredients required for the two pills to help you make your decision."

"That does sound like a good idea," Han Li replied with a nod.

Ye Nanfeng swept a sleeve through the air, and a burst of azure light flashed past, following which an azure book appeared.

After flipping briefly through some pages, he handed the book over to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the book and looked down to find that this particular page contained the list of ingredients required to refine the Spring Rain Pill.

"One 50,000-year-old Horned Dragon Herb, three 5,000-year-old Sea Splitting Flowers, a handful of Wind Bucket Sand..."

Han Li silently read out the names of the ingredients to himself one after another, and he discovered that out of the 15 spirit medicines required to refine this pill, the majority of them were high-grade spirit medicines of a very advanced age, with even the youngest of them all required to be at least 3,000 years of age.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li asked, "Elder Ye, may I ask how spirit medicines are sold in the Immortal Medicine Pavilion? Are they sold for merit points as well?"

"No. Aside from certain extremely precious spirit medicines that can only be purchased using Immortal Origin Stones, all of the other spirit medicines can be purchased with Immortal Origin Stones or top-grade spirit stones," Ye Nanfeng replied.

"How many spirit stones would it cost for me to purchase all of the ingredients required for a batch of Spring Rain Pills?" Han Li asked.

"The main ingredient, the Horned Dragon Herb, can only be purchased with Immortal Origin Stones, and the price is seven Immortal Origin Stones. As for all of the other ingredients, they add up to around 2,000 top-grade spirit stones, but of course, you can pay for them using Immortal Origin Stones as well," Ye Nanfeng replied.

Han Li couldn't help but feel a little speechless upon hearing this. Even if he were to exhaust all of his Immortal Origin Stones and top-grade spirit stones, he wouldn't be able to purchase many sets of ingredients required for this pill at all.

With that in mind, he pinched the page of the book that he was currently on between his fingers to flip to the next page, but Ye Nanfeng interjected, "The recipe for the Origin Unifying Pill comes a little earlier in the book. You should be able to find it after flipping back a few pages."

Han Li did as he was told, and sure enough, it didn't take long for him to find the list of ingredients required to refine the Origin Unifying Pill.

As soon as his gaze fell upon the first ingredient, which was "one 50,000-year-old Blaze Tuber Herb", his eyes immediately lit up slightly.

This was the main ingredient required to refine the Origin Unifying Pill, and he just so happened to already have had a few of them planted in the spirit medicine field in his cave abode. Furthermore, all of them had been matured to the required age stipulated in the recipe.

He then directed his gaze to the dozen or so supplementary spirit medicines, but he wasn't as fortunate there, and all of those spirit medicines were ones that he hadn't planted.

"Aside from the Blaze Tuber Herb, how many spirit stones will be required to purchase all of the other spirit medicines?" Han Li asked.

"If we discount the Blaze Tuber Herb, the other spirit medicines will cost 1,200 top-grade spirit stones," Ye Nanfeng replied.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression.

He was only intending to purchase a pill recipe to make his first attempts at refining earthly pills, and he didn't know how many spirit medicines would go to waste during this process, so it definitely wasn't a good idea to pick the Spring Rain Pill, which had more expensive ingredients.

With that in mind, Han Li arrived at a decision. "I'll take the recipe for the Origin Unifying Pill."

"Alright, please give me your badge, Fellow Daoist," Ye Nanfeng requested.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce his elder badge, which he handed to Ye Nanfeng, and 50 merit points were deducted before the badge was returned to him along with a copy of the pill recipe.

After carefully inspecting the pill recipe for a moment, Han Li said, "In addition to the recipe, I'll need 10 batches of all of the spirit medicines required to refine the Origin Unifying Pill with the exception of the Blaze Tuber Herb."

After making this purchase, he would essentially have no spirit stones left.

Following the completion of the transaction, Han Li bade farewell to Ye Nanfeng, then left the Gourd Peak and returned straight to his cave abode.

……

Three months quickly passed by.

During this time, Han Li barely left his secret chamber at all, and he had dedicated all of his time and energy into studying the pill recipe. He carefully pondered every single step in the recipe, simulating the pill refinement process in extreme detail in his mind countless times.

Even though he was already quite a seasoned pill refinement master, all pill recipes carried countless minute differences from one another, and these disparities were often important factors contributing to one's pill refinement failures.

Hence, he wanted to have the pill recipe completely figured out before he attempted any pill refinement.

On this day, he finally made up his mind to attempt his first Origin Unifying Pill refinement.

Inside the secret chamber, there was an incense burner on the table behind the cushion. A stick of lit greenish-gray incense was protruding out of the burner, and smoke was billowing out from its smoldering tip, spreading a calming fragrance throughout the secret chamber.

Han Li's back was facing the table as he sat with his legs crossed on the cushion, and after meditating with his eyes closed for some time, he slowly reopened his eyes, having rid himself of all unnecessary thoughts.

On the ground in front of him was a purple copper cauldron that was around a foot in radius, and the surface of the cauldron was riddled with flame patterns and ancient runes. Beside the cauldron was a piece of azure silken fabric, upon which were placed the dozen or so ingredients required to refine the Origin Unifying Pill.

The cauldron was a treasure that he had obtained from the Origin Mirage Beast's cave abode, and it wasn't a treasure of a particularly high caliber, but it should be enough to refine the Origin Unifying Pill.

Chapter 237: Using Law Powers for Pill Refinement

Han Li gently exhaled as he flipped a palm upward before gently raising it.

The purple copper burner rose up into the air, carried by a burst of invisible force, hovering around three feet above the ground.

Han Li then opened his mouth to release a burst of nascent flames, which resembled a lingering fiery cloud that enveloped the entire cauldron.

All of the ancient runes and flame patterns on the surface of the copper cauldron lit up in unison, and the cauldron itself began to take on a crimson color.

Han Li made a beckoning motion upon seeing this, and the Blaze Tuber Herb rose up into the air before falling into his grasp.

In the next instant, his hand began to glow with bright azure light, and a miniature azure vortex slowly took shape with a faint whistling sound ringing out from within it.

The Blaze Tuber Herb began to rapidly revolve within the vortex, and it was torn to shreds and grinded down into powder as if the vortex were acting as a stone mill.

A faint pop rang out as the lid of the purple copper cauldron was suddenly removed, and the powderized Blaze Tuber Herb immediately flew in.

With a sweep of Han Li's sleeve, the cauldron began to revolve within the nascent flame.

Time slowly passed by, and a rich medicinal fragrance began to waft throughout the secret chamber.

Han Li's attention remained entirely fixed on the pill cauldron, monitoring all of the changes taking place within it. He followed the pill recipe, adding one ingredient after another to the cauldron while simultaneously constantly adjusting the temperature of his nascent flame.

Only after an entire day and night had passed by did the fire in the secret chamber gradually fade away, following which the cauldron descended onto the ground with a faint clang.

Han Li rose to his feet and made his way over to the cauldron, then removed the lid with a sweep of his sleeve, and he was immediately greeted by an extremely rich medicinal aroma.

His brows were slightly furrowed as he peered into the cauldron with a nervous look on his face, and he discovered that the interior of the cauldron was pitch-black, with only a layer of medicine powder at the bottom, and there was not a single pill to be seen.

Unsurprisingly, this first pill refinement attempt had ended in complete failure.

Han Li reached into the cauldron to scoop out some of the medicinal powder, then carefully examined it for a moment on the palm of his hand. After that, he sniffed at the powder a few times, and he began to understand why he had failed.

It seemed that his temperature manipulation had been lacking, and the temperature was too low at the point when the pills should've taken shape, thereby resulting in failure.

After understanding the underlying reason for his failure, Han Li remained unfazed, and after half a day of rest, he commenced his second pill refinement attempt.

……

Around half a month passed by in the blink of an eye.

Inside the secret chamber, there were nine small piles of black powder on the ground in front of Han Li, resembling a row of miniature graves.

All nine of his pill refinement attempts had ended in failure.

Even though he was already prepared for such an outcome, he still couldn't help but feel a little defeated and frustrated in the wake of nine consecutive failures, particularly when almost all of them had been a result of incorrect temperature moderation.

He had thought that all he would have to do was to raise the temperature right as the pills were about to take shape, and that would ensure that the pills would be formed, but as soon as the pills took shape, they would instantly be incinerated into charred powder due to the excessively high temperatures.

Hence, after nine failures, Han Li didn't continue. Instead, he paused to think of a way around this problem.

The window of time during which the pills were supposed to take shape was extremely brief, and it was virtually impossible to master the required temperature manipulation strategy in a short time. At this rate, it would most likely have taken Han Li at least 10 more failures to begin grasping the correct method.

With that in mind, it became understandable why Earthly Pill Masters were considered to be so precious. After all, every single one of them would've taken an astronomical amount of resources to develop.

The problem was that he didn't have such a large supply of ingredients for him to experiment with, and if he were to fail once more, then all of the top-grade spirit stones that he had spent would go to waste, but how could he capitalize on that incredibly brief window of opportunity?

Han Li was massaging his brows with a vexed expression when he was suddenly struck by an idea.

He immediately sprang into action, making a hand seal while chanting an incantation to conjure up his Mantra Treasured Axis behind him.

14 semi-transparent Time Dao Runes were flashing on the axis, giving off peculiar law fluctuations that slowed down the flow of air in the entire secret chamber.

In order to minimize his immortal spiritual power expenditure, Han Li limited the area encompassed within the law fluctuations to only the area within 10 feet in front of him.

He then opened his mouth to release a ball of nascent flames, which lifted up the purple copper cauldron while also causing it to slowly revolve in mid-air.

The movement of the flames around the cauldron had also been slowed down significantly, to the point that Han Li was able to see every single minute flicker that the flames exhibited.

He then began to powderize the spirit medicines before adding them into the cauldron for refinement.

Under the effects of the Mantra Treasured Axis, the entire process was slowed down to less than a third of its normal speed.

At the same time, the changes taking place in the spirit medicines within the cauldron were also slowed down, to the point that Han Li was able to clearly monitor everything that was unfolding inside through the use of his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and some details that had evaded him in the past were now coming to the fore.

After observing the refinement process for a while, Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis. Even though he had limited the area under the axis's influence, constantly maintaining it was still quite taxing on him. He had already mastered the majority of the pill refinement process, so he would only require the Mantra Treasured Axis's services at some crucial junctures.

Time slowly passed by, and the refinement process that had originally only required a day and a night was extended to almost twice its original duration. However, Han Li was able to gain more insight and understanding from this single pill refinement than all of the previous nine attempts combined. In particular, it had become a lot easier for him to control the temperature of his nascent flame during the moments where the pills were about to take shape.

As the flames around the cauldron slowly subsided, Han Li withdrew the Mantra Treasured Axis back into his body once again.

He made a beckoning motion to draw the cauldron to himself, then swept a sleeve through the air to remove its lid. His eyes were filled with both unease and anticipation as he tipped over the cauldron to pour out its contents.

Some black powder fell out of the opening of the cauldron, immediately following which the sound of pills rolling around inside the cauldron rang out.

Han Li was ecstatic to hear this sound, and he tipped the entire cauldron upside-down before reaching out a hand to catch what was inside.

Seven or eight longan-sized golden pills rolled out of the cauldron before falling into his grasp.

According to the pill recipe, a successful batch of Origin Unifying Pills should've been somewhere between 15 to 16 pills, so this still wasn't a complete success.

However, Han Li was still extremely pleased with this outcome. After all, he was treating these 10 pill refinements as an experiment to begin with, so this was already a very favorable outcome.

Furthermore, now that he had developed the idea of using his Mantra Treasured Axis to assist him in the pill refinement process, his success rate going forward was going to be significantly elevated.

He examined the pills in his hand over and over again, then stored them away in a small vial, leaving only one behind, which he devoured before closing his eyes and beginning to cultivate his Mantra Axis Scripture.

Ultimately, these pills had to be put to the test to see if they had actually been correctly refined.

……

Two months later, Han Li appeared in the sky above the Crimson Dawn Peak before descending toward the spirit fields down below.

The pills that he had refined earlier had worked extremely well, and he had spent this entire time cultivating while consuming the pills in his secret chamber. His rate of cultivation progression had clearly improved during this time, and he had only come out of seclusion on this day.

Sun Buzheng and the others were busy at work in the spirit fields, and Meng Yungui was also among them, having recently made his return.

The majority of the spirit fields near the Crimson Dawn Peak had already been arranged into orderly sections, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

Following the recession of the fire miasma, not only had the climate returned to normal, the underground veins had also been restored to their normal state, so they were no longer restricted to just planting fire-attribute spirit plants in the fields.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this. These spirit fields were situated quite close to the main spirit vein of the Crimson Dawn Peak, so any spirit plants planted in these fields would be sure to grow quite quickly.

He had descended in a silent manner, so Meng Yungui and the others initially didn't notice his presence, but he was quickly spotted thereafter.

"Elder Li!"

The servant hurriedly extended a respectful bow.

Everyone else immediately turned around to find Han Li hovering in mid-air, and they hurriedly dropped what they were doing to pay their respects.

"Welcome back, Elder Li."

Having been with Han Li for quite some time, Meng Yungui and the others had developed a rough understanding of Han Li's personality, so they no longer spoke to him in as formal and rigid a manner as before.

"I just came back, and I decided to come down here to take a look. Keep doing what you were doing. Meng Yungui, come with me," Han Li said with a dismissive wave, then flew back toward the mountain with Meng Yungui trailing along behind him.

A short while later, the two of them arrived in Han Li's cave abode.

Han Li wasted no time with idle chatter as he cut straight to the chase. "I've assigned you quite an arduous task, making you travel so extensively in search of spirit plant seeds. How did it go?"

"Please don't say that, Elder Li. It's my honor to be able to serve you, and I didn't find the task grueling or arduous at all. These are the seeds that I've collected during these past years, please take a look," Meng Yungui hurriedly replied as he pulled out a storage treasure that he offered to Han Li in a respectful manner.

Han Li accepted the storage treasure before injecting his spiritual sense into it, and a few moments later, a surprised look appeared on his face as he nodded and praised, "You did quite well."

He had only sent Meng Yungui on a mission to search for spirit plant seeds as a spur-of-the-moment decision, and he hadn't actually harbored any high hopes for him.

After all, with Meng Yungui's limited cultivation base, there was only so much that he could've been expected to do.

However, the rewards that Meng Yungui had reaped went far beyond Han Li's expectations. All of the seeds that he had found were quite remarkable, and many of them were seeds for supplementary spirit medicines required to refine Origin Unifying Pills. If he were to plant all of these seeds, then he would be able to save a huge sum of spirit stones when refining Origin Unifying Pill in the future.

On top of that, he had also discovered several unfamiliar seeds that resembled rocks with granite-like patterns on their surfaces, but clear traces of life could be detected within them.

"You're far too kind, Elder Li. I was simply very fortunate," Meng Yungui said in a humble manner, but it was clear that he was ecstatic to have received such praise from Han Li.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li gave some seeds to Meng Yungui, some of which had been collected by Meng Yungui, while the others were from Han Li's own collection.

"Go and plant these seeds in the spirit fields at the foot of the mountain, and make sure to look after them well," he instructed.

"Yes, Elder Li," Meng Yungui replied as he accepted the seeds.

"Also, continue your search for seeds. You can keep this treasure for your protection," Han Li said as he handed another storage pouch to Meng Yungui.

"Thank you, Elder Li! I'll be sure to do my best!" Meng Yungui immediately replied before turning to depart.

Han Li remained standing on the spot for a moment, then made his way to the medicine garden in his cave abode.

There, he pulled out several seeds, one of which was shaped like a worm, another was as translucent as jade, and a third one resembled a pea-sized lump of soil with a bumpy surface.

These seeds all belonged to supplementary ingredients for refining Origin Unifying Pill and Spring Rain Pills.

Han Li carefully planted the seeds before watering them with spirit liquid, and only after close to half a day did he finally complete the procedure.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he looked at his gradually expanding medicine garden.

After that, he summoned the giant ape puppet, then instructed it to look after these newly planted spirit seeds before departing from the medicine garden.

Chapter 238: Tight Budget

After returning to his cave abode, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed and began to contemplate what to do next.

The half-batch of Origin Unifying Pills that he had refined had worked quite well, allowing him to make close to 10 years worth of cultivation progress in just two months, but it was going to be very expensive to maintain this rate of progression.

Seeing as he was able to use his Mantra Treasured Axis to significantly improve his success rate in pill refinement, he naturally wasn't going to purchase ready-made pills using merit points as they were a very useful form of currency in other areas.

Thus, the top priority for him now was to secure ingredients for pill refinement.

Aside from manifesting crystals to help the Earthly Deity Avatar heavy water, maturing Blaze Tuber Herbs alone was already close to the limits of the Heaven Controlling Vial's capabilities, so it wouldn't be able to mature many other supplementary ingredients on top of that. Hence, he would have to buy the majority of those ingredients, but the problem was that he didn't have many spirit stones left.

He could sell some of the spoils he had collected from his vanquished enemies for spirit stones, but that was only a temporary solution that wasn't going to work out over the long term.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask.

There were many ways to earn spirit stones, but given his current situation, completing Transient Guild missions was the fastest and the most reliable avenue to take.

There were many missions in the sect that offered spirit stones as rewards, but completing too many of those missions would attract too much attention to himself, thereby potentially leading to trouble.

Furthermore, the Transient Guild missions generally offered better rewards anyway.

With that in mind, he put on his mask, and the azure array projection quickly took shape.

He turned to the missions section and quickly tracked down some missions that could be completed near the Blaze Dragon Dao. There were quite a few of these missions, and they were quite diverse, including missions to gather certain spirit materials, pills, or treasures, as well as missions to hunt down certain demon beasts or individuals.

These missions were all quite conventional, and some of the more special missions had also caught Han Li's attention. For example, there was someone gathering several Earthly Pill Masters to refine a certain type of pill.

There was also a mission that called upon a True Immortal adept in the art of restrictions and arrays to break the restriction on a certain set of ruins, and there was even a mission that was gathering a large number of True Immortals to attack a certain mysterious cultivator.

All of a sudden, Han Li's gaze fell upon a certain mission, and a peculiar look appeared on his face.

The mission was to search for the "the number one sword cultivator of Heavenly South", and the reward offered was quite a lofty one. Even those who only provided certain pieces of information would be able to receive decent compensation.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as a faint smile appeared on his face.

Following the trial on that day, everyone had departed quite quickly, so there shouldn't have been anyone that had discovered the message that he had engraved onto the bottom of the fourth Origin Defying Stone Sword. Hence, someone from the Heavenly Sword Peak had to have discovered the message at a later date.

In that case, the person who had released the mission was most likely someone from the Heavenly Sword Peak, and given the Transient Guild's barrier to entry, that person was very likely to have been Xiong Shan himself. After discovering the message, he had most likely deduced that there was a very good chance that this number one sword cultivator of Heavenly South was the one who had foiled his plans, and as it turned out, he was right.

However, Han Li had never revealed to anyone the fact that he had come from the Heavenly South Region of the Mortal Realm, so there was naturally no cause for concern.

Having said that, this mission was an indication that Xiong Shan was most likely also a member of the Transient Guild, and given his cultivation base, he most likely possessed quite a lofty status in the Transient Guild.

Shortly thereafter, Han Li also noticed a mission searching for the whereabouts of Bai Fengyi, and the thought of Bai Suyuan sprang into his mind at the sight of this mission.

However, he then quickly shook his head to rid himself of these irrelevant trains of thought as he began to focus his attention on searching for missions that were suitable for himself.

Moments later, his gaze fell upon a hunting mission: "Travel to the Heavenly Glacial Pond and slay a True Immortal Stage Glacial Blowfish, making sure to recover its carcass. Reward: 4,000 top-grade spirit stones."

Han Li had read from a book in the Blaze Dragon Dao that the Heavenly Glacial Pond was situated in the northernmost region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, even further north than the Profound Ice Mountain Range. It was a notoriously perilous place on the Ancient Cloud Continent, and it was said that many True Immortals had perished in there in the past.

Han Li accepted this mission before rising to his feet.

......

Several months later.

In the northernmost region of the Ancient Cloud Continent, bone-chilling winds were howling incessantly, while the entire sky was concealed behind a swirling flurry of snow.

There were several snow-covered mountains standing on the landscape, silently enduring the flogging of the unforgiving wind.

An azure streak of light shot forth from the distant sky, then descended onto the summit of one of the mountains to reveal a yellow-skinned middle-aged man.

It was none other than Han Li, who had adopted a disguise using his Transient Guild mask.

Casting his gaze forward from the mountain summit, he was greeted by the sight of an enormous lake that stretched as far as the eyes could see. The water in the lake was extremely dark, resembling black ink.

What was particularly strange was that despite the incredibly low temperatures, the lake hadn't frozen at all, and there were clouds of black mist drifting above its surface.

The biting chill being released by this black mist was far colder than even the frosty wind blowing through the surrounding area.

This was the Heavenly Glacial Pond.

Han Li paused momentarily on the mountain summit, then flew toward the Heavenly Glacial Pond as a streak of azure light.

This place appeared to have been completely devoid of life, but that was not actually the case.

There were many natural treasures in the Heavenly Glacial Pond, including certain special and precious materials that were exclusively found in the pond. Otherwise, it wouldn't' have attracted so many people to venture into its depths. Beneath the surface were many powerful demon beasts that were resistant to the cold environment, and those who came here seeking treasures could easily find themselves falling prey to these demon beasts if they weren't careful.

Han Li was flying along at a low altitude above the surface of the water while staring intently at the lake down below, seemingly searching for something.

All of a sudden, the surface of the water over 1,000 feet up ahead erupted, and a demon beast that was 50 to 60 feet in length shot out before pouncing directly at Han Li.

The demon beast resembled a crocodile with its entire body covered in black scales, and it opened its cavernous mouth to reveal rows of sharp white fangs. There was a pair of bloated yellow eyes on the top of its head, giving it a ferocious appearance, and it was attempting to bite Han Li's body into two with a single vicious chomp.

Han Li's expression changed slightly as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of azure light, and the black demon beast's body abruptly stiffened in mid-air.

Han Li continued onward without pause, flying straight through between the two rows of the demon beast's sharp fangs.

A red line appeared all the way from the demon beast's head to the tip of its tail, following which its body abruptly split open, sending an enormous volume of blood interspersed with internal organs plunging into the lake below.

Han Li paid no heed to what was happening behind him as he continued onward, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

After flying for several more hours, he had already reached quite deep into the Heavenly Glacial Pond.

The further one ventured into the pond, the more the air temperature plummeted, and the more powerful the demon beasts lurking in the water became. At this point, there were even demon beasts that possessed Body Integration Stage power that were occasionally attacking Han Li.

However, they naturally posed no threat to him at all, and he was able to take care of them with ease.

All of a sudden, his eyes lit up as he drew to a halt. His gaze was fixed intently on the surface of the lake beneath him, and he swept a sleeve through the air to send a burst of azure light plunging into the water.

Moments later, a black object emerged from the lake, enveloped by a ball of azure light. It was a ball of algae that was giving off a faint fragrance.

This type of algae was known as Black Star Algae, and it was very prevalent on the lakebed here.

Black Star Algae was the Glacial Blowfish's favorite food, and such a large mass of Black Star Algae was sure to attract feeding Glacial Blowfishs.

Han Li tossed the ball of Black Star Algae away, then flipped a hand over to produce a millstone-sized blue object. It appeared to have been an internal organ of a certain type of demon beast, and it was giving off a strong odor.

This was an organ from the Elephant Trunk Beast, and it was very alluring to Glacial Blowfishs. He had purchased the organ from the Transient Guild for a sum of spirit stones prior to setting off on this trip.

He then summoned a white talisman in his other hand, and the talisman flew into the blue organ at his behest as a ball of white light, vanishing without a trace.

After that, Han Li tossed the organ into the water down below.

The organ was instantly enveloped by the bone-chilling glacial qi in the area, and it was frozen into a chunk of black ice in the blink of an eye before plunging into the lake.

Even though it had been frozen, its odor didn't abate in the slightest.

That white talisman was a sensory talisman, and it would immediately alert him if a demon beast devoured the organ.

Instead of remaining on the spot to wait, Han Li continued to fly onward.

The Heavenly Glacial Pond was enormous, so he naturally couldn't place his hopes entirely on one patch of Black Star Algae.

Close to a day later, Han Li found another mass of Black Star Algae, where he left another Elephant Trunk Beast organ with a sensory talisman inside before continuing onward yet again.

Half a month passed by.

During this time, Han Li discovered several dozen masses of Black Star Algae, leaving an Elephant Trunk Beast organ at each one.

From there, Han Li stopped searching for more patches of Black Star Algae and concealed himself at the center of the dozens of patches of Black Star Algae that he had discovered.

This wasn't because he didn't want to find any more, he had simply exhausted his supply of Elephant Trunk Beast organs.

Furthermore, he had already left out a sufficient number of baits, and all that was left to do was to wait.

One day, two months later.

An earth-shattering boom that was audible even several thousands of kilometers away rang out in the Heavenly Glacial Pond.

The surface of the water churned violently as enormous waves that were several thousand feet tall were sent sweeping in all directions, and even the clouds in the sky were stirred up into a frenzy.

At the center of the giant waves was Han Li and a bluish-black blowfish-like demon beast.

The demon beast was only around 200 to 300 feet in length, and its bulging body was riddled with bluish-black bone spikes. Furthermore, its tail resembled a scorpion's stinger, and it was rapidly swinging around like lightning. Dense black qi was swirling all around it, within which projections of different human and beastly faces would occasionally emerge, all of which were extremely twisted and tormented, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

This demon beast was none other than a Glacial Blowfish, and its enormous aura indicated that it had already reached the True Immortal Stage.

The Glacial Blowfish was constantly producing a strange sound that resembled the weeping of a small child as thick pillars of blue light erupted out of its swinging tail before hurtling directly toward Han Li.

Each pillar of blue light was tinged with hints of law powers, and a glacial aura had spread through the entire surrounding area within a radius of several thousand kilometers. Countless icicle spears had appeared in the air, and it seemed that the very space itself had been frozen.

Han Li paid no heed to the glacial qi around him as two thick azure sword projections danced around him like a pair of guardian wyrms, forming a sword net that kept all of the oncoming pillars of blue light at bay.

Chapter 239: Madman

An alarmed look appeared in the Glacial Blowfish's eyes, and its roars became even more urgent.

Its bonded glacial qi was extremely formidable, able to seep into the bodies of its enemies without their detection, and thanks to that, it had never lost a battle, but this human cultivator was somehow completely unaffected by it.

At this moment, the Heavy Water True Axis within Han Li's body was slowly revolving, absorbing all of the glacial qi that was surging into his body.

He made a grabbing motion, and four streaks of azure swordlight instantly appeared before swelling to close to 1,000 feet in size each, intertwining with one another as they flew through the air.

Countless azure sword projections were conjured up, destroying all of the oncoming blue light.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li made a hand seal, and the four massive streaks of swordlight fused as one in the blink of an eye to form an enormous sword that was over 10,000 feet in length, and thick arcs of golden lightning appeared on its surface as it swept viciously toward the Glacial Blowfish.

The Glacial Blowfish shuddered upon seeing this, seemingly extremely fearful of the golden lightning, and it opened its mouth up wide before letting loose a sharp screech.

Ripples that were visible even to the naked eye appeared in the surrounding space, and everything encompassed within the ripples was abruptly rooted to the spot, as if some type of restriction had been placed upon them.

Han Li felt his entire body tighten up, and he was completely unable to move, while his golden lightning sword was also immobilized in mid-air.

The Glacial Blowfish let loose a low roar, and the bone spikes on its body abruptly lit up, while the black mist around it surged through the air, transforming into an enormous black python as it pounced directly toward Han Li.

A hint of surprise initially appeared on Han Li's face, but he then gave a cold harrumph, and a massive axial projection suddenly appeared around him before revolving on the spot, releasing a burst of terrifying power that easily destroyed the restrictive force in the surrounding space.

As a result, the golden lightning sword was instantly freed, and it came crashing down to clash against the giant black python.

Arcs of golden lightning wrapped themselves around the massive black python as a string of resounding booms rang out.

The huge python let loose an anguished wail, and its enormous body exploded into countless plumes of black smoke that spread through the air in all directions.

A fearful look appeared in the Glacial Blowfish's eyes upon seeing this, and bright bluish-black light erupted from its body as it turned to flee.

Right at this moment, a cold harrumph rang out within the Glacial Blowfish's ears, immediately following which it was struck by a burst of excruciating pain directly in its mind, as if a red-hot poker had been plunged into its soul. As a result, it let loose an involuntary cry of agony, and the pain was so severe that it was instantly stopped cold in its tracks.

In the next instant, a golden sword projection flashed past, entering through its mouth before emerging from its rear end. An enormous volume of blue blood instantly came gushing out of the two massive holes, forming a pair of blue blood fountains.

The light in the Glacial Blowfish's quickly faded, and the nascent soul in its body didn't even get a chance to try and escape before it was destroyed by the golden sword projection.

Han Li made a beckoning motion with one hand, and the golden lightning sword circled around before flying back, then reverted back into four flying swords in a flash before vanishing into his body.

Immediately thereafter, he swept his other hand through the air, releasing a burst of blue light to envelop the Glacial Blowfish's carcass.

A layer of blue ice instantly appeared over the surface of the giant carcass, instantly stopping the bleeding.

His mission was to recover this carcass, so he couldn't afford to lose too much blood.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li stowed the Glacial Blowfish carcass away, then flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light without pause.

……

Inside the secret chamber of a secluded residence in a certain city on the Ancient Cloud Continent.

A scholarly-robed middle-aged man with the appearance of a schoolteacher was seated with his legs crossed in front of a crimson pill furnace, making a hand seal with a look of concentration on his face. He was controlling the flame beneath the furnace, seemingly in the process of refining a batch of pills.

All of a sudden, the pill furnace shuddered, and a string of dull explosions rang out, following which a charred smell wafted out from within.

A dark look appeared on the man's face, and he heaved a long sigh.

Right at this moment, a burst of azure light suddenly lit up on his body.

He immediately pulled out an azure fox mask upon seeing this, then placed the mask onto his own face.

The mask released a burst of azure light, which formed a massive light screen in front of him.

Immediately thereafter, light flashed from the center of the screen, and a storage pouch appeared.

"Oh? I didn't think that this mission would be completed so quickly!" the man murmured to himself with a surprised expression, then made a grabbing motion to draw the storage pouch into his grasp while sweeping his other sleeve through the air, and a massive Glacial Blowfish carcass instantly appeared before him.

"What a clean killing blow! I don't think even I would've been able to preserve such a complete carcass if I had gone after this beast on my own. Wyrm 15, eh? I've never heard of this person before, but it appears they're quite a formidable character," the man mused to himself.

……

At the same time.

Inside the cave abode on the Crimson Dawn Peak, Han Li was also wearing his Transient Guild mask, and a storage pouch appeared before him following a flash of light from the light screen up ahead.

He drew the storage pouch into his grasp before emptying its contents, and a pile of top-grade spirit stones instantly spilled out onto the ground.

After counting the spirit stones, a pleased look appeared on his face, and he stowed the spirit stones away again with a sweep of his sleeve before searching for his next mission.

……

Somewhere on the Thunderstorm Sea.

Thick bolts of lightning were flashing incessantly through the dense, dark clouds up above, and occasionally, bolts of lightning would come crashing down onto the sea below.

There were several enormous balls of light near a black island situated somewhere on the Thunderstorm Sea, and they were releasing such a massive commotion that even the sound of the thunderclaps in the area was drowned out.

Different attacks would occasionally be seen hurtling through the air, churning up the sky and the sea down below.

Among the two sides locked in battle, one was a group of five True Immortal cultivators, all of whom were wearing Transient Guild masks, two of which were azure, while the other three were blue.

They were battling a colony of close to 100 lightning bats, each of which was several hundred feet in length with purple lightning revolving around their bodies, and every single one of them was giving off a Grand Ascension Stage aura, blasting thick pillars of lightning out of their mouths in retaliation.

Despite the fact that the five Transient Guild cultivators were severely outnumbered, their superior quality more than made up for their lack of quantity, and they held a clear upper hand over the lightning bats, striking down one bat after another in quick succession.

A black spear pierced into the body of a lightning bat amid a flash of black light, and arcs of silver lightning surged along the length of the spear, flowing into the lightning bat's body through the wound it had inflicted.

The lightning bat instantly exploded, and a glittering and translucent purple bead appeared.

An azure-robed man then shot forth like lightning before catching the purple bead in his grasp.

The man was wearing an azure cow mask with the characters for "Wyrm 15" engraved upon it, and after clinching the purple bead, he did pause even for a moment before plunging back into the fray.

Lightning continued to flash over the length of the black spear in his hand as he pierced it through the body of another lightning bat.

All of the nearby lightning bats began to screech in fury upon seeing this.

Thick bolts of purple lightning came hurtling toward the azure-robed man from all directions, making it impossible for him to take evasive measures.

The man's expression remained completely unchanged as he stowed away the lightning crystal that he had plucked out of the lightning bat's body, and a protective layer of silver lightning appeared around him to keep all of the oncoming attacks at bay.

The silver barrier was trembling incessantly in the face of the oncoming attacks, but it showed no signs of breaking at all.

All of a sudden, the azure-robed man pounced at another lightning bat, with the black spear in his hand releasing a series of spear projections.

He was like a tiger that had broken into a sheep's pen, slaying four or five more lightning bats in the span of just a few breaths.

The other four cultivators were all stunned by his display of power.

The individual attacks from these lightning bats weren't all that formidable, and it wasn't much trouble for them to withstand even four or five attacks at once, but anything beyond that would begin to pose a threat to them. After all, lightning in any significant quantity was not a force to be underestimated.

However, the azure-robed man had no qualms about his own safety at all as he swept through the lightning bats' ranks with ease.

The other four cultivators hurriedly sprang into action as well, hunting down some of the straggling lightning bats.

Close to an hour later, the final lightning bat was slain by a black spear projection.

Its body exploded to reveal a purple bead, which was taken by the azure-robed man.

With that, the entire flock of lightning bats had been slain, and close to half of them had been killed by the azure-robed man.

The azure-robed man gently exhaled, then flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light without even sparing a glance at his companions.

The other four cultivators exchanged a few glances, then also went their separate ways in silence.

Meanwhile, the azure-robed man appeared somewhere above the Thunderstorm Sea amid a flash of silver lightning, and the mask on his face projected an azure light screen.

After casting an incantation seal onto the light screen, a projection of a blurry figure emerged.

"Here are 47 lightning bat crystals," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a small pile of purple lightning beads.

The blurry figure nodded in response. "According to the mission's stipulations, your reward will be 47 Immortal Origin Stones."

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face as he swept a sleeve through the air, and the small pile of lightning bat crystals vanished into the array at the center of the light screen in a flash.

Shortly thereafter, a small pile of Immortal Origin Stones within the array amid a flash of light.

Han Li quickly stowed the Immortal Origin Stones away, then turned to search for his next mission.

……

One day, three years later, on the Crimson Dawn Peak.

A streak of azure light shot forth from afar, landing on the mountain summit in a discrete fashion. The azure light faded to reveal none other than Han Li, and his face was looking slightly pale.

He entered his cave abode without alerting any of his servants, then sat down with his legs crossed in his secret chamber as he pulled out his Transient Guild mask to conjure up the azure light screen.

After that, he pulled out three black badges, each of which had the visage of a menacing black ghost engraved upon it.

He cast an incantation seal to teleport the three badges away using the array, and moments later, around three dozen Immortal Origin Stones were transmitted to him.

He inspected the Immortal Origin Stones briefly with his spiritual sense before stowing them away, but there was a peculiar look in his eyes.

His mission on this occasion had been to kill a group of evil cultivators residing on the border of the Ancient Cloud Continent. They were proficient in various types of arrays and secret techniques that made them quite difficult to deal with, which was why six Transient Guild members had been sent after them, and almost all of them had been high-level azure-masked members.

During the course of the mission, Han Li had made an observation by chance.

Among the Transient Guild members that had completed the mission, the majority of them had been cultivators from the Blaze Dragon Dao. In particular, the leader had unleashed a set of extremely formidable flying swords to slay the mid-True Immortal Stage leader of the evil cultivators with ease.

Han Li had been struck by a sense of familiarity upon seeing this. In particular, that Transient Guild member's flying sword manipulation techniques reminded him greatly of Deputy Dao Lord Xiong Shan.

Even though the man's aura had been concealed by his Transient Guild mask, Han Li was almost certain that he was Xiong Shan.

However, he only pondered this matter for a moment before ridding himself of that rain of thought.

It hardly mattered to him whether that person was Xiong Shan or not.